<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel>
<title>New Free-For-Dev</title>
<description>New Free Resources</description>
<link></link>
<item>
	<title>Add Clappia in the list of Low-code platforms</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/8ec4bc81fbcab85946f3a87837c988a6ea4e1899</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.clappia.com">https://www.clappia.com</a> - A low-code platform designed for building business process applications with customizable mobile and web apps. Offers a drag-and-drop interface, features like Offline Support, real-time location tracking and integration with various third-party services.<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>DNS: Add noit.at.</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/3be6f7331420637520002ca1b4548d196280bf66</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://noip.at/">https://noip.at/</a> - Free DDNS service without registration, tracking, logging or advertising. No limit to domains.<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>DNS: Add Dynv6.</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/5488a9d5727cef536794530b6a290502633c92b7</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://dynv6.com/docs/apis) and management of a lot of dns record types (like CNAME, MX, SPF, SRV, TXT and others">https://dynv6.com/docs/apis) and management of a lot of dns record types (like CNAME, MX, SPF, SRV, TXT and others</a> - Free DDNS service with [API support](https://dynv6.com/docs/apis) and management of a lot of dns record types (like CNAME, MX, SPF, SRV, TXT and others).<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Add OneVM</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/1200bad077bf995504fdb9d8b8ca45dfc8d58f13</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://onevm.uk.to/">https://onevm.uk.to/</a> - KVM VPS, 1 GB RAM, 1 vCore, 15 GB storage, 10 ports + 1 SSH port, 350 mbps ethernet, free 20 hours/day.<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Add TempMailDetector.com</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/915708cbc8a3912b8e01c69177266bb894d13941</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://tempmaildetector.com/">https://tempmaildetector.com/</a> - Verify up to 200 emails a month for free and see if an email is temporary or not.<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Doprax Cloud no longer have free plan</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/1b9487a30a81588fdc4609c017f4043151c9a177</link><description><![CDATA[ ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Koyeb update free plan</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/cbee82cee96461f933b28196a696652e3355638f</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.koyeb.com) - Koyeb is a developer-friendly serverless platform to deploy apps globally. Seamlessly run Docker containers, web apps, and APIs with git-based deployment, native autoscaling, a global edge network, and built-in service mesh and discovery. Free Instance lets you deploy a web service in Frankfurt, Germany or Washington, D.C., US. Free Managed Postgres database available in Frankfurt (Germany), Washington, D.C. (US">https://www.koyeb.com) - Koyeb is a developer-friendly serverless platform to deploy apps globally. Seamlessly run Docker containers, web apps, and APIs with git-based deployment, native autoscaling, a global edge network, and built-in service mesh and discovery. Free Instance lets you deploy a web service in Frankfurt, Germany or Washington, D.C., US. Free Managed Postgres database available in Frankfurt (Germany), Washington, D.C. (US</a> - Koyeb is a developer-friendly serverless platform to deploy apps globally. Seamlessly run Docker containers, web apps, and APIs with git-based deployment, native autoscaling, a global edge network, and built-in service mesh and discovery. Free Instance lets you deploy a web service in Frankfurt, Germany or Washington, D.C., US. Free Managed Postgres database available in Frankfurt (Germany), Washington, D.C. (US), and Singapore. 512MB memory, 2GB storage, and 0.1 CPU. No credit card is required to get started.<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Add Supermaven</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/7509b08c42653d75ff14ceedbecc68c3b1f30b3a</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.supermaven.com/">https://www.supermaven.com/</a> - Supermaven is a fast AI code completion plugin for VSCode, JetBrains, and Neovim. Free tier provides unlimited inline completions.<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>short description</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/f511e4aeeedf10ec4684c6a3c8bc6f7723a41db0</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://askclair.ai/">https://askclair.ai/</a> - Clinical AI Reference. Students have free access to the professional tool suite, which includes Open Search, Clinical Summary, Med Review, Drug Interactions, ICD-10 Codes, and Stewardship. Additionally, a free trial for the professional suite is available.<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>add Clair</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/1ea5d8bd0899adf077fb89f96908d4379079840c</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://askclair.ai/">https://askclair.ai/</a> - Clinical AI Reference. Simply ask and receive. Clair's responses always come with links to original, clinically significant references like FDA Drug Package Inserts, the NIH Clinical Trials Database, the NLM Drug Interactions Database, and Clinical Guidelines. Students have free access to the professional tool suite, which includes Open Search, Clinical Summary, Med Review, Drug Interactions, ICD-10 Codes, and Stewardship. Additionally, a free trial for the professional suite is available.<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Added https://bismuth.cloud</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/fd9effbcf81f91fe0dbb6e9c473f61112ac206b2</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.bismuth.cloud/">https://www.bismuth.cloud/</a> - Our AI will boostrap your Python API on our function runtime and hosted storage, build and host for free in our online editor or locally with your favorite tools.<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>

</channel>
</rss>
