<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel>
<title>New Free-For-Dev</title>
<description>New Free Resources</description>
<link></link>
<item>
	<title>Add Doppio.sh</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/8a9da5551f1378c155195b6c36645760015a831a</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://doppio.sh/">https://doppio.sh/</a> - Managed API to generate and privately store PDFs and Screenshots using top rendering technology. The free plan allows 400 PDFs and Screenshots per month.<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Add Novu.co</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/3dacecfab9a70e29f20a93c48721739f7e8cf82b</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://deployment.io) - Deployment.io helps developers automate deployments on AWS. On our free tier, a developer (single user">https://deployment.io) - Deployment.io helps developers automate deployments on AWS. On our free tier, a developer (single user</a> - Deployment.io helps developers automate deployments on AWS. On our free tier, a developer (single user) can deploy unlimited static sites, web services, and environments. We provide 20 job executions free per month with previews and auto-deploys included in the free tier.<br>
<a href="https://novu.co">https://novu.co</a> - The open-source notification infrastructure for developers. Simple components and APIs for managing all communication channels in one place: Email, SMS, Direct, In-App and Push. The free plan includes 30,000 notifications/month with 90 days of retention.<br>
<a href="https://singlebase.cloud">https://singlebase.cloud</a> - SinglebaseCloud is an AI-powered all-in-one backend platform to accelerate app development. It offers tools like Vector DB, Relational Document DB, Auth, Search, and Storage, aiming to simplify backend development. Free/Starter Plan offers Relational Document DB, Auth, Search, Storage.<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Change dash</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/d7c231b7ebceafbf0e4e3c8dd8b3d31945db7ef5</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://metricswave.com">https://metricswave.com</a> - Privacy-friendly Google Analytics alternative for developers. Free plan allows 20k pageviews per month without credit card.<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Add MetricsWave to Analytics services</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/b1e1f490ef0274b47ebfdae1d29dce2ce10737e1</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://metricswave.com">https://metricswave.com</a> - Privacy-friendly Google Analytics alternative for developers. Free plan allows 20k pageviews per month without credit card.<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Moved engagespot from baas to messaging and streaming</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/a9a1715510ce5486b98bb2a690311841c82e0f34</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://engagespot.co/">https://engagespot.co/</a> - Multi-channel notification infrastructure for developers with a prebuilt in-app inbox and no-code template editor. Free plan includes 10,000 messages/mo.<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Update README.md</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/b7397f31d44b6df655a08fb6cc4efe0a5dc64567</link><description><![CDATA[ ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Add Cody AI</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/be531225a0db13e6c1476112ad39612c06c7cdb4</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://sourcegraph.com/cody) - Cody is a coding AI assistant that uses AI and a deep understanding of your codebase to help you write and understand code faster. Cody gives developers a choice of LLMs (including local inference), has support for various IDEs, supports all popular programming languages, and has a free plan. The free plan gives developers 20 chat messages (using Claude 3 Sonnet as the LLM) and 500 autocompletions (using the Starcoder 16b">https://sourcegraph.com/cody) - Cody is a coding AI assistant that uses AI and a deep understanding of your codebase to help you write and understand code faster. Cody gives developers a choice of LLMs (including local inference), has support for various IDEs, supports all popular programming languages, and has a free plan. The free plan gives developers 20 chat messages (using Claude 3 Sonnet as the LLM) and 500 autocompletions (using the Starcoder 16b</a> - - Cody is a coding AI assistant that uses AI and a deep understanding of your codebase to help you write and understand code faster. Cody gives developers a choice of LLMs (including local inference), has support for various IDEs, supports all popular programming languages, and has a free plan. The free plan gives developers 20 chat messages (using Claude 3 Sonnet as the LLM) and 500 autocompletions (using the Starcoder 16b) each month.<br>
<a href="https://sourcegraph.com/">https://sourcegraph.com/</a> - Java, Go, Python, Node.js, etc., code search/cross-references, free for Open Source<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Add UI Bakery</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/0f12a7a1c49e383a8cb96adb53c1daa616554d8d</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://uibakery.io">https://uibakery.io</a> - — Low-code platform that enables faster building of custom web applications. Supports building UI using drag and drop with a high level of customization through JavaScript, Python, and SQL. Available as both cloud and self-hosted solutions. Free for up to 5 users.<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Add EMQX Serverless</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/dc212d92a1ada802e8bbdaa8cc9889a82094afbc</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.emqx.com/en/cloud/serverless-mqtt) - Scalable and secure serverless MQTT broker you can get in seconds. 1M session minutes/month free forever (no credit card required">https://www.emqx.com/en/cloud/serverless-mqtt) - Scalable and secure serverless MQTT broker you can get in seconds. 1M session minutes/month free forever (no credit card required</a> - - Scalable and secure serverless MQTT broker you can get in seconds. 1M session minutes/month free forever (no credit card required).<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Add Sweego to Email category</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/e08f87175b80b40a94406a4366821c19de54bd4a</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.sweego.io/">https://www.sweego.io/</a> - European transactional emails API for developers. 500 emails/day free.<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Add Teaminal</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/4cb3d9d8d5117bce8210a3a769e7f726bc37ebcc</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.teaminal.com">https://www.teaminal.com</a> - Standup, retro, and sprint planning tool for remote teams. Free for up to 15 users.<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>

</channel>
</rss>
