<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel>
<title>New Free-For-Dev</title>
<description>New Free Resources</description>
<link></link>
<item>
	<title>Update README.md</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/f7af2f69bc82dded16f44468d7312bec23a44600</link><description><![CDATA[ ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Add more information</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/386866a2389c9bfd64a246a1a9fe0b68ed526c3f</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://datelist.io">https://datelist.io</a> - Online booking / appointment scheduling system. Free up to 5 bookings per month, includes 1 calendar<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Update README.md</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/c47a2c840d14446e58cbe3161b24a033d09ace28</link><description><![CDATA[ ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Update README.md</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/4b791664a16b17c462fc0af4c15e5dae00f0d729</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://nextdns.io">https://nextdns.io</a> - DNS based firewall, 300K free queries monthly<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Merge branch 'master' into patch-1</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/842a3280dbd5601218b4c7e1bef6382a3b616191</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://botfront.net/#pricing">https://botfront.net/#pricing</a> - Free CDN and DDoS protection<br>
<a href="https://botfront.net/">https://botfront.net/</a> - Free CDN and DDoS protection for one domain and three subdomains<br>
<a href="https://www.000webhost.com/">https://www.000webhost.com/</a> - Zero cost website hosting with Apache, PHP, MySQL, cPanel with ads on the bottom of each pages!<br>
<a href="https://www.divio.com/">https://www.divio.com/</a> - A platform to manage cloud application deploying only using Docker. Available free subscription for development projects.<br>
<a href="https://prepros.io/">https://prepros.io/</a> - Prepros can compile Sass, Less, Stylus, Pug/Jade, Haml, Slim, CoffeeScript and TypeScript out of the box, reloads your browsers and makes it really easy to develop & test your websites so you can focus on making them perfect. You can also add your own tools with just a few clicks.<br>
<a href="https://freedb.tech">https://freedb.tech</a> - Free MySQL cloud database with remote access up to 100Mb in Database Storage with PhpMyAdmin available and unlimited simultaneous connections.<br>
<a href="https://freedb.tech">https://freedb.tech</a> - Free MySQL cloud database with remote access with PhpMyAdmin available. Free tier allows a database up to 100Mb in Database Storage. **If the database exceeding 100Mb will be deleted without any warning.**<br>
<a href="https://ide.cs50.io/">https://ide.cs50.io/</a> - A free IDE powered by AWS Cloud9 by Harvard University.<br>
<a href="https://form2channel.com">https://form2channel.com</a> - Place a static html form on your website and receive submissions directly to Google Sheets, Email, Slack, Telegram or Http. No coding necessary.<br>
<a href="https://about.gitlab.com/product/pages/">https://about.gitlab.com/product/pages/</a> - — Hosting static site directly from GitLab repository<br>
<a href="https://bip.sh">https://bip.sh</a> - Bip provides zero downtime deployment, a global CDN, SSL, and more for static websites. Free plan only for 7days.<br>
<a href="https://bip.sh">https://bip.sh</a> - Bip provides zero downtime deployment, a global CDN, SSL, and more for static websites. Free plan only for 7 days.<br>
<a href="https://shtab.app/">https://shtab.app/</a> - Project management service that makes collaboration in the office and remotely transparent with tracker based on AI.<br>
<a href="https://simplelogin.io/) – Open source, self-hostable email alias/forwarding solution. Free 5 Aliases, unlimited bandwith, unlimited reply/send. Free for educational staffs (student, researcher, etc">https://simplelogin.io/) – Open source, self-hostable email alias/forwarding solution. Free 5 Aliases, unlimited bandwith, unlimited reply/send. Free for educational staffs (student, researcher, etc</a> - Open source, self-hostable email alias/forwarding solution. Free 5 Aliases, unlimited bandwith, unlimited reply/send. Free for educational staffs (student, researcher, etc)<br>
<a href="https://mailbluster.com/) – Email marketing solution (with a free plan of Unlimited subscribers & 62k emails at $0/month">https://mailbluster.com/) – Email marketing solution (with a free plan of Unlimited subscribers & 62k emails at $0/month</a> - Email marketing solution (with a free plan of Unlimited subscribers & 62k emails at $0/month).<br>
<a href="https://simplelogin.io/) – Open source, self-hostable email alias/forwarding solution. Free 5 Aliases, unlimited bandwith, unlimited reply/send. Free for educational staffs (student, researcher, etc">https://simplelogin.io/) – Open source, self-hostable email alias/forwarding solution. Free 5 Aliases, unlimited bandwith, unlimited reply/send. Free for educational staffs (student, researcher, etc</a> - Open source, self-hostable email alias/forwarding solution. Free 5 Aliases, unlimited bandwith, unlimited reply/send. Free for educational staffs (student, researcher, etc).<br>
<a href="https://unixtime.co.za">https://unixtime.co.za</a> - Free API to convert Unixtime to DateTime and vice versa.<br>
<a href="https://testtls.com">https://testtls.com</a> - Test a SSL/TLS service for secure server configuration, certificates, chains etc. Not limited to HTTPS.<br>
<a href="https://www.easyretro.io/">https://www.easyretro.io/</a> - Free simple and intuitive sprint retrospective tool<br>
<a href="https://postale.io/) — Free domain email addresses for up to 2 users per domain, one domain (per account">https://postale.io/) — Free domain email addresses for up to 2 users per domain, one domain (per account</a> - Free domain email addresses for up to 2 users per domain, one domain (per account), POP3/IMAP enabled, no ads<br>
<a href="https://erratic.host">https://erratic.host</a> - — 1.5 GB storage, unlimited bandwidth, PHP 8, DNS Manager, cPanel, Software Installer, E-Mail Accounts. Run your own website without any questions<br>
<a href="https://formspree.io/">https://formspree.io/</a> - Send email using an HTTP POST request. Free tier limits to 50 submissions per form per month.<br>
<a href="https://web3forms.com">https://web3forms.com</a> - Contact forms for Static & JAMStack Websites without writing backend code. Free plan allows Unlimited Forms, Unlimited Domains & 250 Submissions per month.<br>
<a href="https://localazy.com">https://localazy.com</a> - Free for 1000 source language strings, unlimited languages, unlimited contributors, startup and open source deals<br>
<a href="https://ubiqsecurity.com/">https://ubiqsecurity.com/</a> - — Encrypt and decrypt data with 3 lines of code and automatic key management. Free for 1 application and up to 1,000,000 encryptions per month.<br>
<a href="https://codekeep.io">https://codekeep.io</a> - Google Keep for Code Snippets. Organize,Discover and share code snippets, featuring a powerful code screenshot tool with preset templates and linking feature.<br>
<a href="https://etf-data.com/">https://etf-data.com/</a> - API](https://etf-data.com/) - Quality European ETF, ETN and ETC data, updated daily. The API offers complete overview including sector, country, factor, dividend yield and valuations. Additionally basic information such as domicile, followed index, asset class, fee, currency, replication method, distribution type and frequency. 50 free API calls per day.<br>
<a href="https://www.scraperapi.com/">https://www.scraperapi.com/</a> - — Cloud based web scraping API handles proxies, browsers, and CAPTCHAs. Scrape any web page with a simple API call. Get started with 1000 free API calls/month.<br>
<a href="https://unixtime.co.za">https://unixtime.co.za</a> - Free API to convert Unixtime to DateTime and vice versa.<br>
<a href="https://www.stackhawk.com/">https://www.stackhawk.com/</a> - application scanning throughout your pipeline to find and fix security bugs before they hit production. Unlimited scans and environments for a single app.<br>
<a href="https://testtls.com">https://testtls.com</a> - Test a SSL/TLS service for secure server configuration, certificates, chains etc. Not limited to HTTPS.<br>
<a href="https://www.deta.sh">https://www.deta.sh</a> - Deploy unlimited number of Node.js and Python apps for free up to 50k requests/month. Includes free DBs, Auth and email.<br>
<a href="https://theendlessweb.com/">https://theendlessweb.com/</a> - — 300 MB storage, Free SSL, PHP, MySQL, FTP, free sub-domains, E-Mail, DNS, beatiful panel UI. One of the best!<br>
<a href="https://fosshost.org/">https://fosshost.org/</a> - Free open source hosting VPS, web, storage and mirror hosting<br>
<a href="https://www.cloudamqp.com/">https://www.cloudamqp.com/</a> - RabbitMQ as a Service, up to 1M messages/month and 20 connections free<br>
<a href="https://grapedrop.com/">https://grapedrop.com/</a> - Responsive, powerful, SEO optimized web page builder based on GrapesJS Framework. Free for first 5 pages, unlimited custom domains, all features and simple usage.<br>
<a href="https://graphcomment.com/">https://graphcomment.com/</a> - GraphComment is a comments platform that helps you build an active community from website’s audience.<br>
<a href="https://form2channel.com">https://form2channel.com</a> - Place a static html form on your website and receive submissions directly to Google Sheets, Email, Slack, Telegram or Http. No coding necessary.<br>
<a href="https://github.com/tvvocold/FOSS-for-Dev">https://github.com/tvvocold/FOSS-for-Dev</a> - FOSS for Dev](https://github.com/tvvocold/FOSS-for-Dev) — A hub of free and Open Source software for developers<br>
<a href="https://about.gitlab.com/product/continuous-integration/">https://about.gitlab.com/product/continuous-integration/</a> - Create pipelines directly from Git repositories using GitLab's CI service. 400 mins/mo per top-level group<br>
<a href="https://graphcms.com/">https://graphcms.com/</a> - Offers free tier for small projects. GraphQL first API. Move away from legacy solutions to the GraphQL native Headless CMS - and deliver omnichannel content API first.<br>
<a href="https://quickmocker.com/) — Manage online fake API endpoints under your own subdomain, forward requests to localhost URL for webhooks development and testing, use RegExp and multiple HTTP methods for URL path, prioritize endpoints, more than 100 shortcodes (dynamic or fake response values) for response templating, import from OpenAPI (Swagger">https://quickmocker.com/) — Manage online fake API endpoints under your own subdomain, forward requests to localhost URL for webhooks development and testing, use RegExp and multiple HTTP methods for URL path, prioritize endpoints, more than 100 shortcodes (dynamic or fake response values) for response templating, import from OpenAPI (Swagger</a> - Manage online fake API endpoints under your own subdomain, forward requests to localhost URL for webhooks development and testing, use RegExp and multiple HTTP methods for URL path, prioritize endpoints, more than 100 shortcodes (dynamic or fake response values) for response templating, import from OpenAPI (Swagger) Specifications in JSON format, proxy requests, restrict endpoint by IP address and authorization header. Free account provides 1 random subdomain, 10 endpoints, 5 RegExp URL paths, 50 shortcodes per endpoint, 100 requests per day, 50 history records in requests log.<br>
<a href="https://grafana.com/products/cloud/) - Grafana Cloud. Free: 3 users, 10 dashboards, 100 alerts, metrics storage in Prometheus and Graphite (10,000 series, 14 days retention), logs storage in Loki (50 GB of logs, 14 days retention">https://grafana.com/products/cloud/) - Grafana Cloud. Free: 3 users, 10 dashboards, 100 alerts, metrics storage in Prometheus and Graphite (10,000 series, 14 days retention), logs storage in Loki (50 GB of logs, 14 days retention</a> - - Grafana Cloud. Free: 3 users, 10 dashboards, 100 alerts, metrics storage in Prometheus and Graphite (10,000 series, 14 days retention), logs storage in Loki (50 GB of logs, 14 days retention)<br>
<a href="https://grafana.com/products/cloud/) - Grafana Cloud is a composable observability platform, integrating metrics and logs with Grafana. Free: 3 users, 10 dashboards, 100 alerts, metrics storage in Prometheus and Graphite (10,000 series, 14 days retention), logs storage in Loki (50 GB of logs, 14 days retention">https://grafana.com/products/cloud/) - Grafana Cloud is a composable observability platform, integrating metrics and logs with Grafana. Free: 3 users, 10 dashboards, 100 alerts, metrics storage in Prometheus and Graphite (10,000 series, 14 days retention), logs storage in Loki (50 GB of logs, 14 days retention</a> - - Grafana Cloud is a composable observability platform, integrating metrics and logs with Grafana. Free: 3 users, 10 dashboards, 100 alerts, metrics storage in Prometheus and Graphite (10,000 series, 14 days retention), logs storage in Loki (50 GB of logs, 14 days retention)<br>
<a href="https://www.molasses.app">https://www.molasses.app</a> - Powerful feature flags and A/B testing. Free up to 3 environments with 5 feature flags each.<br>
<a href="https://zeet.co/">https://zeet.co/</a> - Zeet is the easiest and fastest way to deploy and scale your code. It supports both code from GitHub or any public Docker image. Only one project is free.<br>
<a href="https://www.24browser.com">https://www.24browser.com</a> - Capture beautifully rendered website screenshots at scale with powerful API.<br>
<a href="https://form.taxi/">https://form.taxi/</a> - Endpoint for HTML forms submissions. With notifications, spam blocker and GDPR-compliant data processing. Free plan for basic usage.<br>
<a href="https://mailazy.com/">https://mailazy.com/</a> - 250 emails/day free<br>
<a href="https://indicative.com/">https://indicative.com/</a> - Customer analytics platform to optimize customer engagement, increase conversion, and improve retention. Free up to 50M events/month.<br>
<a href="https://indicative.com/">https://indicative.com/</a> - Customer analytics platform to optimize customer engagement, increase conversion, and improve retention.<br>
<a href="https://indicative.com/">https://indicative.com/</a> - Customer analytics platform to optimize customer engagement, increase conversion, and improve retention. Free up to 50M events/month.<br>
<a href="https://bump.email/">https://bump.email/</a> - Free 10 Bump email addresses, 1 custom domain<br>
<a href="https://temp-mail.io">https://temp-mail.io</a> - Free disposable temporary email service with multiple emails at once and forwarding<br>
<a href="https://atomist.com/">https://atomist.com/</a> - A quicker and more convenient way to automate a variety of development tasks. Now in beta.<br>
<a href="https://cronhooks.io/">https://cronhooks.io/</a> - Schedule one time or recurring webhooks using api and web app. Free plan allows 1 webhook schedule<br>
<a href="https://cronhooks.io/">https://cronhooks.io/</a> - Schedule one time or recurring webhooks using api and web app. Free plan allows 1 webhook schedule.<br>
<a href="https://www.ably.com/">https://www.ably.com/</a> - Realtime messaging service with presence, persistence and guaranteed delivery. Free plan includes 3m messages per month, 100 peak connections and 100 peak channels.<br>
<a href="https://forwardemail.net) — Free email forwarding for custom domains. Create and forward an unlimited amount of email addresses with your domain name (**note**: You must pay if you use .casa, .cf, .click, .email, .fit, .ga, .gdn, .gq, .loan, .london, .men, .ml, .pl, .rest, .ru, .tk, .top, .work TLDs due to spam">https://forwardemail.net) — Free email forwarding for custom domains. Create and forward an unlimited amount of email addresses with your domain name (**note**: You must pay if you use .casa, .cf, .click, .email, .fit, .ga, .gdn, .gq, .loan, .london, .men, .ml, .pl, .rest, .ru, .tk, .top, .work TLDs due to spam</a> - Free email forwarding for custom domains. Create and forward an unlimited amount of email addresses with your domain name (**note**: You must pay if you use .casa, .cf, .click, .email, .fit, .ga, .gdn, .gq, .loan, .london, .men, .ml, .pl, .rest, .ru, .tk, .top, .work TLDs due to spam)<br>
<a href="https://roboflow.com">https://roboflow.com</a> - create and deploy a custom computer vision model with no prior machine learning experience required. Free tier includes up to 1,000 free source images.<br>
<a href="https://glitchtip.com/">https://glitchtip.com/</a> - Simple, open source error tracking. Compatible with open-source Sentry SDKs. 1000 events per month for free, or can self-host with no limits<br>
<a href="https://www.loadmill.com/">https://www.loadmill.com/</a> - Automatically create API and load tests by analyzing network traffic. Simulate up to 50 concurrent users for up to 60 minutes for free every month.<br>
<a href="https://glitchtip.com/">https://glitchtip.com/</a> - Simple, open source error tracking. Compatible with open-source Sentry SDKs. 1000 events per month for free, or can self-host with no limits<br>
<a href="https://logdna.com">https://logdna.com</a> - Free for a single user, no retention, unlimited hosts and sources<br>
<a href="https://kitemaker.co">https://kitemaker.co</a> - Collaborate through all phases of the product development process and keep track of work across Slack, Discord, Figma, and Github. Unlimited users, unlimited spaces. Free plan up to 250 work items.<br>
<a href="https://www.pubnub.com/">https://www.pubnub.com/</a> - Swift, Kotlin and React messaging at 1 million transactions each month. Transactions may contain multiple messages.<br>
<a href="https://kitemaker.co">https://kitemaker.co</a> - Collaborate through all phases of the product development process and keep track of work across Slack, Discord, Figma, and Github. Unlimited users, unlimited spaces. Free plan up to 250 work items.<br>
<a href="https://darklang.com/">https://darklang.com/</a> - Hosted editor/language/infrastructure<br>
<a href="https://darklang.com/">https://darklang.com/</a> - Hosted editor/language/infrastructure<br>
<a href="https://darklang.com/">https://darklang.com/</a> - Hosted editor/language/infrastructure<br>
<a href="https://www.courier.com/">https://www.courier.com/</a> - Single API for push, in-app, email, chat, SMS, and other messaging channels with template management and other features. Free plan includes 10,000 messages/mo.<br>
<a href="https://www.goatcounter.com/) — GoatCounter is an open source web analytics platform available as a hosted service (free for non-commercial use">https://www.goatcounter.com/) — GoatCounter is an open source web analytics platform available as a hosted service (free for non-commercial use</a> - GoatCounter is an open source web analytics platform available as a hosted service (free for non-commercial use) or self-hosted app. It aims to offer easy to use and meaningful privacy-friendly web analytics as an alternative to Google Analytics or Matomo. Free tier is for non-commerical use and includes unlimited number of sites, 6 months of data retention, and 100k pageviews/month.<br>
<a href="https://redirection.io/">https://redirection.io/</a> - SaaS tool for managing HTTP redirections for businesses, marketing and SEO.<br>
<a href="#other-free-resources">#other-free-resources</a> - Resources](#other-free-resources)<br>
<a href="https://mixpanel.com/">https://mixpanel.com/</a> - 100,000 monthly tracked users, unlimited data history and seats, US or EU data residency<br>
<a href="https://darklang.com/">https://darklang.com/</a> - Hosted language combined with editor and infrastructure. Free during the beta, generous free tier planned after beta.<br>
<a href="https://analytics.ao.gl/">https://analytics.ao.gl/</a> - — Forever FREE Customer Analytics for ALL your websites, with Unlimited Events per month<br>
<a href="https://workspaces.openshift.com/">https://workspaces.openshift.com/</a> - - Web based and Kubernetes-Native IDE for Developer Teams with multi-language support. Open Source and community driven. A online instance hosted by Red Hat is available at [workspaces.openshift.com](https://workspaces.openshift.com/).<br>
<a href="https://newsapi.org">https://newsapi.org</a> - — Search news on the web with code, get JSON results. Developers get 3,000 queries free each month.<br>
<a href="https://smartcar.com">https://smartcar.com</a> - - An API for cars to locate, get fuel tank, battery levels, odometer, unlock/lock doors, etc.<br>
<a href="https://PhantomJsCloud.com">https://PhantomJsCloud.com</a> - Browser automation and page rendering. Free Tier offers up to 500 pages/day. Free Tier since 2017.<br>
<a href="https://pagure.io">https://pagure.io</a> - Pagure.io is a free and open source software code collaboration platform for FOSS-licensed projects, Git-based<br>
<a href="https://issueembed.dev/">https://issueembed.dev/</a> - - A bug reporting tool for websites to go directly into your Github Issues. Free plan for personal repositories with up to 500 issues/month and 10,000 page views/month.<br>
<a href="https://simplelocalize.io/">https://simplelocalize.io/</a> - Free up to 100 translation keys, unlimited strings, unlimited languages, startup deals<br>
<a href="https://efemarai.com">https://efemarai.com</a> - Testing and debugging platform for ML models and data. Visualize any computational graph. Free 30 debugging sessions per month for developers.<br>
<a href="https://cmd.com/">https://cmd.com/</a> - Security platform providing real-time access control and dynamic policy enforcement on every Linux instance in your cloud or datacenter<br>
<a href="https://www.logrocket.com">https://www.logrocket.com</a> - 1,000 sessions/month with 30 day retention, error tracking, live mode<br>
<a href="https://www.wormhol.org/">https://www.wormhol.org/</a> - Straightforward file sharing service. Share unlimited files up to 5GB to as many peers as you want.<br>
<a href="https://cloudinary.com/">https://cloudinary.com/</a> - Image upload, powerful manipulations, storage and delivery for sites and apps, with libraries for Ruby, Python, Java, PHP, Objective-C and more. Free tier includes 25 monthly credits. 1 credit is equal to 1,000 image transformations, 1 GB of storage, or 1 GB of CDN usage.<br>
<a href="https://www.newrelic.com">https://www.newrelic.com</a> - New Relic observability platform built to help engineers create more perfect software. From monoliths to serverless, you can instrument everything, then analyze, troubleshoot, and optimize your entire software stack. Free tier offers 100GB/month of free data ingest, 1 free full access user, and unlimited free basic users.<br>
<a href="https://developers.arcgis.com">https://developers.arcgis.com</a> - APIs and SDKs for maps, geospatial data storage, analysis, geocoding, routing, and more across web, desktop, and mobile. 2,000,000 free basemap tiles, 20,000 non-stored geocodes, 20,000 simple routes, 5,000 drive time calculations, 5GB free tile+data storage per month.<br>
<a href="https://ipapi.co/) - IP Address Location API by Kloudend, Inc - A reliable geolocation API, built on AWS, trusted by Fortune 500. Free tier offers 30k lookups/month (1k/day">https://ipapi.co/) - IP Address Location API by Kloudend, Inc - A reliable geolocation API, built on AWS, trusted by Fortune 500. Free tier offers 30k lookups/month (1k/day</a> - IP Address Location API by Kloudend, Inc - A reliable geolocation API, built on AWS, trusted by Fortune 500. Free tier offers 30k lookups/month (1k/day) without signup. Contact us for a higher limit trial plan.<br>
<a href="https://doppler.com/">https://doppler.com/</a> - Universal Secrets Manager for application secrets and config, with support for syncing to various cloud providers. Free for unlimited users with basic access controls.<br>
<a href="https://octopus.com">https://octopus.com</a> - - Automated deployment and release-management. Free for <= 10 deployment targets.<br>
<a href="https://www.thundra.io/apm">https://www.thundra.io/apm</a> - Application monitoring and debugging. Has a free tier up to 250k monthly invocations.<br>
<a href="https://ploi.io/">https://ploi.io/</a> - Server management tool to easily manage and deploy your servers & sites. Free for 1 server.<br>
<a href="https://updrafts.app">https://updrafts.app</a> - WYSIWYG web site builder for tailwindcss based designs. Free for non-commercial usage.<br>
<a href="https://3v4l.org/">https://3v4l.org/</a> - Free online PHP shell and snippet sharing site, runs your code in 300+ PHP versions<br>
<a href="https://avo.app/">https://avo.app/</a> - Simplified analytics release workflow. Single-source-of-truth tracking plan, type safe analytics tracking library, in-app debuggers, data observability to catch all data issues before you release. Free for 2 workspace members and 1 hour data observability lookback.<br>
<a href="https://holistic.dev/">https://holistic.dev/</a> - The #1 static code analyzer for Postgresql optimization. Performance, security, and architect database issues automatic detection service<br>
<a href="https://parsers.dev/">https://parsers.dev/</a> - Abstract syntax tree parsers and intermediate representation compilers as a service<br>
<a href="https://seatable.io/">https://seatable.io/</a> - Flexible, Spreadsheet-like Database built by Seafile team. unlimited tables, 2,000 lines, 1-month versioning, up to 25 team members.<br>
<a href="https://linear.app/) — Issue tracker with streamlined interface. Free for unlimited members, up to 10MB file upload size, 250 issues (excluding Archive">https://linear.app/) — Issue tracker with streamlined interface. Free for unlimited members, up to 10MB file upload size, 250 issues (excluding Archive</a> - Issue tracker with streamlined interface. Free for unlimited members, up to 10MB file upload size, 250 issues (excluding Archive)<br>
<a href="https://tara.ai/">https://tara.ai/</a> - — Simple sprint management service. Free plan has unlimited tasks, sprints and workspaces, with no user limits.<br>
<a href="https://fibery.io/">https://fibery.io/</a> - Connected workspace platform. Free for single user, up to 2 GB disk space.<br>
<a href="https://www.yodiz.com/">https://www.yodiz.com/</a> - Agile development and issue tracking. Free up to 3 users, unlimited projects.<br>
<a href="https://teamwork.com/">https://teamwork.com/</a> - Project management & Team Chat. Free for 5 users and 2 projects. Premium plans available.<br>
<a href="https://foss.heptapod.net/">https://foss.heptapod.net/</a> - Heptapod is a friendly fork of GitLab Community Edition providing support for Mercurial<br>
<a href="https://zulip.com/">https://zulip.com/</a> - Real-time chat with unique email-like threading model. Free plan includes 10,000 messages of search history and File storage up to 5 GB. also it provides self-hostable open-source version.<br>
<a href="https://www.braidchat.com/">https://www.braidchat.com/</a> - Chat app designed for teams. Free for public access group, unlimited users, history, and integrations. also it provide self-hostable open-source version.<br>
<a href="https://www.meistertask.com/">https://www.meistertask.com/</a> - Online task management for teams. Free up to 3 projects, unlimited project members.<br>
<a href="https://www.honeybadger.io) - Exception, uptime, and cron monitoring. Free for small teams and open-source projects (12,000 errors/month">https://www.honeybadger.io) - Exception, uptime, and cron monitoring. Free for small teams and open-source projects (12,000 errors/month</a> - Exception, uptime, and cron monitoring. Free for small teams and open-source projects (12,000 errors/month).<br>
<a href="https://www.hookrelay.dev/">https://www.hookrelay.dev/</a> - - Add webhook support to your app without the hassles: done-for-you queueing, retries with backoff, and logging.<br>
<a href="https://www.hookrelay.dev/">https://www.hookrelay.dev/</a> - - Add webhook support to your app without the hassles: done-for-you queueing, retries with backoff, and logging. The free plan has 100 deliveries per day, 14-day retention, and 3 hook endpoints.<br>
<a href="https://kreya.app">https://kreya.app</a> - Free gRPC GUI client to call and test gRPC APIs. Can import gRPC APIs via server reflection.<br>
<a href="https://www.revenuecat.com/) — Hosted backend for in-app purchases and subscriptions (iOS and Android">https://www.revenuecat.com/) — Hosted backend for in-app purchases and subscriptions (iOS and Android</a> - Hosted backend for in-app purchases and subscriptions (iOS and Android). Free up to $10k/mo in tracked revenue.<br>
<a href="https://upstash.com/">https://upstash.com/</a> - Serverless Redis with free tier up to 10,000 requests per day, 256MB max database size, and 20 concurrent connections<br>
<a href="https://www.borgbase.com/">https://www.borgbase.com/</a> - Simple and secure offsite backup hosting for Borg Backup. 10 GB free backup space and 2 repositories.<br>
<a href="https://efemarai.com">https://efemarai.com</a> - Testing and debugging platform for ML models and data. Visualize any computational graph. Free 30 debugging sessions per month for developers.<br>
<a href="https://newsapi.org">https://newsapi.org</a> - — Search news on the web with code, get JSON results. Developers get 3,000 queries free each month.<br>
<a href="https://applitools.com/) — Smart visual validation for web, native mobile and desktop apps. Integrates with almost all automation solutions (like Selenium and Karma) and remote runners (Sauce Labs, Browser Stack">https://applitools.com/) — Smart visual validation for web, native mobile and desktop apps. Integrates with almost all automation solutions (like Selenium and Karma) and remote runners (Sauce Labs, Browser Stack</a> - Smart visual validation for web, native mobile and desktop apps. Integrates with almost all automation solutions (like Selenium and Karma) and remote runners (Sauce Labs, Browser Stack). free for open source. A free tier for a single user with limited checkpoints per week.<br>
<a href="https://webhook.site">https://webhook.site</a> - Verify webhooks, outbound HTTP requests, or emails with a custom URL. Temporary URL and email address is always free.<br>
<a href="https://www.tiny.cloud">https://www.tiny.cloud</a> - rich text editing API. Core features free for unlimited usage.<br>
<a href="https://hostman.com">https://hostman.com</a> - Deploy up to 3 static sites from your GitHub repository for free.<br>
<a href="https://translation.io">https://translation.io</a> - Free for Open Source<br>
<a href="https://www.plasmic.app/">https://www.plasmic.app/</a> - A fast, easy to use, powerful web design tool and page builder that integrates into your codebase. Build responsive pages or complex components; optionally extend with code; and publish to production sites and apps.<br>
<a href="https://www.netlify.com/">https://www.netlify.com/</a> - Builds, deploy and hosts static site/app free for, 100 GB data and 100 GB/month bandwidth.<br>
<a href="https://checklyhq.com">https://checklyhq.com</a> - Open source E2E / Synthetic monitoring and deep API monitoring for developers. Free plan with 5 users and 50k+ check runs.<br>
<a href="https://updrafts.app">https://updrafts.app</a> - WYSIWYG web site builder for tailwindcss based designs. Free for non-commercial usage.<br>
<a href="https://www.contentful.com/">https://www.contentful.com/</a> - Headless CMS. Content management and delivery APIs in the cloud. Comes with one free Community space that includes 5 users, 25K records, 48 Content Types, 2 locales.<br>
<a href="https://www.qovery.com">https://www.qovery.com</a> - Qovery is the simplest way to deploy your full-stack apps on AWS, GCP and Azure. It is free web hosting for developers with Database, SSL, a global CDN, and auto deploys from Git.<br>
<a href="https://connectycube.com">https://connectycube.com</a> - Unlimited chat messages, p2p voice & video calls, files attachments and push notifications. Free for apps up to 20K MAU.<br>
<a href="https://connectycube.com">https://connectycube.com</a> - APIs for realtime messaging, voice & video calling, push notifications, files storage and users management. Free for apps up to 20K MAU.<br>
<a href="https://www.xirsys.com">https://www.xirsys.com</a> - Global network of STUN / TURN servers with a generous free tier.<br>
<a href="https://www.cloudmailin.com/">https://www.cloudmailin.com/</a> - Incoming email via HTTP POST and transactional outbound - 10,000 free emails/month<br>
<a href="https://authy.com) - Two-factor authentication (2FA">https://authy.com) - Two-factor authentication (2FA</a> - Two-factor authentication (2FA) on multiple devices, with backups. Drop-in replacement for Google Authenticator.<br>
<a href="https://authy.com) - Two-factor authentication (2FA">https://authy.com) - Two-factor authentication (2FA</a> - Two-factor authentication (2FA) on multiple devices, with backups. Drop-in replacement for Google Authenticator. Free for up to 100 successful authentications.<br>
<a href="https://www.20i.com/">https://www.20i.com/</a> - Free global CDN with no restrictions and 1 Tbps+ DDoS protection available on all web hosting, including free hosting.<br>
<a href="https://www.20i.com/">https://www.20i.com/</a> - Free web hosting with no ads, on the same platform as paid plans. Includes a free CDN, 100 email addresses, SSL and over 80 one-click installs.<br>
<a href="https://updrafts.app">https://updrafts.app</a> - WYSIWYG web site builder for tailwindcss based designs. Free for non-commercial usage.<br>
<a href="https://products.office.com/microsoft-teams/free">https://products.office.com/microsoft-teams/free</a> - — Microsoft Teams is a chat-based digital hub that brings conversations, content, and apps together in one place all from a single experience. Free for up to 50k users.<br>
<a href="https://drv.tw">https://drv.tw</a> - Web](https://drv.tw) — Host directly to the web from Google Drive & OneDrive. Static sites only. Free forever. One site per Google/Microsoft account.<br>
<a href="https://discordapp.com/">https://discordapp.com/</a> - Chat with public/private rooms. Markdown text, voice, video, and screen sharing capabilities. Free for unlimited users.<br>
<a href="https://products.office.com/microsoft-teams/free">https://products.office.com/microsoft-teams/free</a> - — Microsoft Teams is a chat-based digital hub that brings conversations, content, and apps together in one place all from a single experience. Free for up to 500k users.<br>
<a href="https://esper.io">https://esper.io</a> - MDM and MAM for Android Devices with DevOps. 100 devices free with 1 user license and 25 MB Application Storage.<br>
<a href="https://openode.io">https://openode.io</a> - Free Node.js hosting for Open Source projects. 100 GB Bandwidth/month with 100 MB memory & 1000 MB storage. Deploy using CLI or existing Git repository.<br>
<a href="https://github.com/tvvocold/FOSS-for-Dev">https://github.com/tvvocold/FOSS-for-Dev</a> - FOSS for Dev](https://github.com/tvvocold/FOSS-for-Dev) — A hub of free and Open Source software for developers.<br>
<a href="https://developers.redhat.com">https://developers.redhat.com</a> - Developers](https://developers.redhat.com) — Free access to Red Hat products including RHEL,OpenShift,CodeReady etc exclusively for developers. Individual plan only. Free e-Books also offered for reference.<br>
<a href="https://encore.dev/">https://encore.dev/</a> - Backend framework using static analysis to provide automatic infrastructure, boilerplate free code, and more. Includes free cloud hosting for hobby projects.<br>
<a href="https://gitgud.io">https://gitgud.io</a> - Unlimited private and public repositories. Free forever. Powered by GitLab & Sapphire. CI/CD not provided.<br>
<a href="https://getjsonip.com">https://getjsonip.com</a> - — Returns the Public IP address of the client it is requested from. No registration required for free tier. Using CORS data can be requested using client side JS directly from browser. Useful for services monitoring change in client and server IPs.<br>
<a href="https://getjsonip.com">https://getjsonip.com</a> - — Returns the Public IP address of the client it is requested from. No registration required for free tier. Using CORS data can be requested using client side JS directly from browser. Useful for services monitoring change in client and server IPs. Unlimited Requests.<br>
<a href="https://appetize.io">https://appetize.io</a> - Test your Android & iOS apps on this Cloud Based service. Free tier includes 1 concurrent session with 100 minutes usage per month. No app size limit.<br>
<a href="https://appetize.io">https://appetize.io</a> - Test your Android & iOS apps on this Cloud Based Android Phone/Tablets emulators and iPhone/iPad simulators directly in your browser. Free tier includes 1 concurrent session with 100 minutes usage per month. No limit on app size.<br>
<a href="https://d.android.com/studio">https://d.android.com/studio</a> - — Android Studio provides the fastest tools for building apps on every type of Android device. Open Source IDE and the best to develop Android apps. Available for Windows,Mac,Linux and even ChromeOS!<br>
<a href="https://d.android.com/studio">https://d.android.com/studio</a> - — Android Studio provides the fastest tools for building apps on every type of Android device. Open Source IDE, free for everyone and the best to develop Android apps. Available for Windows,Mac,Linux and even ChromeOS!<br>
<a href="https://0hi.me/">https://0hi.me/</a> - Free PHP & MySQL Web Hosting for your small project. SSL/TLS and CDN also available for free.<br>
<a href="https://www.microsoft.com/microsoft-365/enterprise/e5) (Windows excluded) which is renewable. It is renewed if you're active in development(measured using telemetry data & algorithms">https://www.microsoft.com/microsoft-365/enterprise/e5) (Windows excluded) which is renewable. It is renewed if you're active in development(measured using telemetry data & algorithms</a> - Developer Program](https://developer.microsoft.com/microsoft-365/dev-program) — Get a free sandbox, tools, and other resources you need to build solutions for the Microsoft 365 platform. The subscription is a 90-day [Microsoft 365 E5 Subscription](https://www.microsoft.com/microsoft-365/enterprise/e5) (Windows excluded) which is renewable. It is renewed if you're active in development(measured using telemetry data & algorithms).<br>
<a href="https://code.sololearn.com">https://code.sololearn.com</a> - A cloud programming playground well-suited for running code snippets. Supports various programming languages. No registration required for running code but required when you need to save code on their platform. Also offers free courses for begginers and intermediate level coders.<br>
<a href="https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev">https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev</a> - the result of Pull Requests, reviews, ideas and work done by 900+ people. You too can help by sending [Pull Requests](https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev) to add more services or by remove ones whose offerings have changed or been retired.<br>
<a href="https://protectumus.com) - Free website security check, site antivirus and server firewall (WAF">https://protectumus.com) - Free website security check, site antivirus and server firewall (WAF</a> - Free website security check, site antivirus and server firewall (WAF) for PHP. Email notifications for registered users in free tier.<br>
<a href="https://www.mendix.com/">https://www.mendix.com/</a> - Rapid Application Development for Enterprises, unlimited number of free sandbox environments supporting unlimited users, 0.5 GB storage and 1 GB RAM per app. Also Studio and Studio Pro IDEs are allowed in free tier.<br>
<a href="https://qualtrics.com/free-account">https://qualtrics.com/free-account</a> - — Create professional forms & survey using this first class tool. 50+ expert-designed survey templates. Free Account has limit of 1 active survey, 100 responses/survey & 8 response types.<br>
<a href="https://curlhub.io">https://curlhub.io</a> - Proxy service for inspecting and debugging API calls. Free plan includes 10,000 requests per month.<br>
<a href="https://hookbin.com/) - Create unique (public or private">https://hookbin.com/) - Create unique (public or private</a> - Create unique (public or private) endpoints to collect, parse, and inspect HTTP requests. Inspect headers, body, query strings, cookies, uploaded files, etc. Useful for testing/inspecting webhook. Similar to RequestBin, and Webhook.site.<br>
<a href="https://freedns.afraid.org/domain/registry/">https://freedns.afraid.org/domain/registry/</a> - Free DNS hosting. Also provide free subdomain based on numerous public user [contributed domains](https://freedns.afraid.org/domain/registry/). Get free subdomains from "Subdomains" menu after signing up.<br>
<a href="https://www.tableau.com/developer">https://www.tableau.com/developer</a> - Program](https://www.tableau.com/developer) — Innovate, create, and make Tableau work perfectly for your organization. Free developer program gives a personal development sandbox license for Tableau Online. The version is the latest pre-release version so Data Devs can test each & every feature of this superb platform.<br>
<a href="https://continuousphp.com/">https://continuousphp.com/</a> - — continuousphp is the first and only PHP-centric Platform to build, package, test and deploy applications in the same workflow. Free for Community Projects i.e. OSS, Public & Educational projects.<br>
<a href="#file-converters">#file-converters</a> - <br>
<a href="https://conversiontools.io/) - Online File Converter for documents, images, video, audio, eBooks. REST API is available. Libraries for Node.js, PHP, Python. Support files up to 50 GB (for paid plans">https://conversiontools.io/) - Online File Converter for documents, images, video, audio, eBooks. REST API is available. Libraries for Node.js, PHP, Python. Support files up to 50 GB (for paid plans</a> - - Online File Converter for documents, images, video, audio, eBooks. REST API is available. Libraries for Node.js, PHP, Python. Support files up to 50 GB (for paid plans). Free tier is limited by file size and number of conversions per day.<br>
<a href="https://conversiontools.io/) - Online File Converter for documents, images, video, audio, eBooks. REST API is available. Libraries for Node.js, PHP, Python. Support files up to 50 GB (for paid plans">https://conversiontools.io/) - Online File Converter for documents, images, video, audio, eBooks. REST API is available. Libraries for Node.js, PHP, Python. Support files up to 50 GB (for paid plans</a> - - Online File Converter for documents, images, video, audio, eBooks. REST API is available. Libraries for Node.js, PHP, Python. Support files up to 50 GB (for paid plans). Free tier is limited by file size and number of conversions per day.<br>
<a href="https://conversiontools.io/) - Online File Converter for documents, images, video, audio, eBooks. REST API is available. Libraries for Node.js, PHP, Python. Support files up to 50 GB (for paid plans">https://conversiontools.io/) - Online File Converter for documents, images, video, audio, eBooks. REST API is available. Libraries for Node.js, PHP, Python. Support files up to 50 GB (for paid plans</a> - - Online File Converter for documents, images, video, audio, eBooks. REST API is available. Libraries for Node.js, PHP, Python. Support files up to 50 GB (for paid plans). Free tier is limited by file size and number of conversions per day.<br>
<a href="https://continuousphp.com/">https://continuousphp.com/</a> - — continuousphp is the first and only PHP-centric Platform to build, package, test and deploy applications in the same workflow. Free for Community Projects i.e. OSS/Public/Educational projects.<br>
<a href="https://imagekit.io">https://imagekit.io</a> - Image CDN with automatic optimization, real-time transformation, and storage that you can integrate with existing setup in minutes. Free plan includes up to 20GB bandwidth per month.<br>
<a href="https://github.com/) — Unlimited public repositories and unlimited private repositories (with unlimited collaborators). Apart from this some other free services(there are much more but we list the main ones here">https://github.com/) — Unlimited public repositories and unlimited private repositories (with unlimited collaborators). Apart from this some other free services(there are much more but we list the main ones here</a> - Unlimited public repositories and unlimited private repositories (with unlimited collaborators). Apart from this some other free services(there are much more but we list the main ones here) provided are :<br>
<a href="https://github.com/features/actions)(Free for Public Repos, 2000 min/month for private repos free">https://github.com/features/actions)(Free for Public Repos, 2000 min/month for private repos free</a> - Public Repos, 2000 min/month for private repos free)<br>
<a href="https://pages.github.com) (Free for Public Repos">https://pages.github.com) (Free for Public Repos</a> - Hosting](https://pages.github.com) (Free for Public Repos)<br>
<a href="https://github.com/features/packages) (Free for public repos,500 MB storage & 1GB bandwidth outside CI/CD free for private repos">https://github.com/features/packages) (Free for public repos,500 MB storage & 1GB bandwidth outside CI/CD free for private repos</a> - & Container Registry](https://github.com/features/packages) (Free for public repos,500 MB storage & 1GB bandwidth outside CI/CD free for private repos)<br>
<a href="https://about.gitlab.com/">https://about.gitlab.com/</a> - Unlimited public and private Git repos with unlimited collaborators. Also offers the following features :<br>
<a href="https://appflux.io">https://appflux.io</a> - Project Management tool with Log Management & Issues. Take your team onboard & forget management through emails.<br>
<a href="https://about.gitlab.com/product/continuous-integration) (Free for Public Repos, 400 mins/month for private repos">https://about.gitlab.com/product/continuous-integration) (Free for Public Repos, 400 mins/month for private repos</a> - for Public Repos, 400 mins/month for private repos)<br>
<a href="https://about.gitlab.com/product/pages">https://about.gitlab.com/product/pages</a> - with [GitLab Pages](https://about.gitlab.com/product/pages).<br>
<a href="https://penpot.app">https://penpot.app</a> - Web based, open source design and prototyping tool. Supports SVG. Completely free.<br>
<a href="https://apitemplate.io">https://apitemplate.io</a> - Auto-generate social images and PDF documents with a simple API or automation tools like Zapier & Airtable. No CSS/HTML required.<br>
<a href="https://webshrinker.com">https://webshrinker.com</a> - Web Shrinker provides web site screenshot and domain intelligence API services. Free 100 requests/month.<br>
<a href="https://catchjs.com/">https://catchjs.com/</a> - JavaScript error tracking with screenshots and click trails. Free for open source projects.<br>
<a href="https://apitemplate.io">https://apitemplate.io</a> - Auto-generate images and PDF documents with a simple API or automation tools like Zapier & Airtable. No CSS/HTML required. Free plan comes with 50 images/month and 3 templates.<br>
<a href="https://sider.review">https://sider.review</a> - Code review platform for many languages. Supports integration with GitHub. Free for public repositories with unlimited users.<br>
<a href="https://formspark.io/">https://formspark.io/</a> - Form to Email service, free plan allows unlimited forms, 250 submissions per month, support by Customer assistance team.<br>
<a href="https://getform.io/">https://getform.io/</a> - Form backend platform for designers and developers, 1 form, 50 submissions, Single file upload, 100MB file storage.<br>
<a href="https://pageclip.co/">https://pageclip.co/</a> - Free plan allows one site, one form, 1,000 submissions per month.<br>
<a href="https://smartforms.dev/">https://smartforms.dev/</a> - Powerful and easy form backend for your website, forever free plan allows 50 submissions per month, 250MB file storage, Zapier integration, CSV/JSON export, custom redirect, custom response page, Telegram & Slack bot, single email notifications.<br>
<a href="https://www.zoho.com/forms/">https://www.zoho.com/forms/</a> - - with 40+ field types, customizable themes, situation-specific templates, and a simple user interface, helps you create beautiful, functional forms for all your needs. Free plan allows 3 forms, 500 submissions/month, 200 MB File storage.<br>
<a href="https://layerci.com">https://layerci.com</a> - CI for full stack projects. 1 full stack preview environment with 5GB memory & 3 CPUs .<br>
<a href="https://developer.suse.com">https://developer.suse.com</a> - Program](https://developer.suse.com) — Experience cloud native productivity for free. Get hands-on with the SUSE Cloud Application Platform with your own Developer Sandbox. 1 Free Application. Free subdomain provided along with API for CLI. Storage & Memory Quota of 1 GB.<br>
<a href="https://developer.salesforce.com/signup">https://developer.salesforce.com/signup</a> - Program](https://developer.salesforce.com/signup) — Build apps Lightning fast with drag and drop tools. Customize your data model with clicks. Go further with Apex code. Integrate with anything using powerful APIs. Stay protected with enterprise-grade security. Customize UI with clicks or any leading-edge web framework. Free Developer Program gives access to the full Lightining Platform.<br>
<a href="https://developers.bmc.com/site/global/bmc_helix_platform/program/overview/index.gsp">https://developers.bmc.com/site/global/bmc_helix_platform/program/overview/index.gsp</a> - Program](https://developers.bmc.com/site/global/bmc_helix_platform/program/overview/index.gsp) — The BMC Developer Program provides documentation and resources to build and deploy digital innovations for your enterprise. Access to a comprehensive, personal sandbox which includes the platform, SDK, and a library of components that can be used to build and tailor apps.<br>
<a href="https://developer.servicenow.com/">https://developer.servicenow.com/</a> - Program](https://developer.servicenow.com/) — Rapidly build, test, and deploy applications that make work better for your organization. Free Instance & access early previews.<br>
<a href="https://pinata.cloud">https://pinata.cloud</a> - — Pinata is the simplest way to upload and manage files on IPFS. Our friendly user interface combined with our IPFS API makes Pinata the easiest IPFS pinning service for platforms, creators, and collectors. 1 GB storage free along with access to API.<br>
<a href="https://kritika.io/">https://kritika.io/</a> - Static Code Analysis for Perl with integration for GitHub. Free for unlimited public repositories.<br>
<a href="https://vaadin.com">https://vaadin.com</a> - Build scalable UIs in Java or TypeScript, and use the integrated tooling, components and design system to iterate faster, design better and simplify the development process. Unlimited Projects with 5 years free maintenance.<br>
<a href="https://codebeat.co">https://codebeat.co</a> - Automated Code Review Platform available for many languages. Free forever for public repositories with Slack & E-mail integration.<br>
<a href="https://icons8.com">https://icons8.com</a> - Icons, illustrations, photos, music, and design tools. Free Plan offers Limited formats in lower resolution. Link to Icons8 when you use our assets.<br>
<a href="https://rive.app">https://rive.app</a> - Create and ship beautiful animations to any platform. Free forever for Individuals. The service is a editor which hosts all the graphics on their servers as well. They also provide runtimes for many platforms to run graphics made using Rive.<br>
<a href="https://smartmockups.com/">https://smartmockups.com/</a> - Create product mockups, 200 free mockups.<br>
<a href="https://percy.io">https://percy.io</a> - Add visual testing to any web app, static site, style guide, or component library. Unlimited team members, Demo app and unlimited projects, 5,000 snapshots / month.<br>
<a href="https://www.zoho.com">https://www.zoho.com</a> - Started as an e-mail provider but now provides a suite of services out of which some of them have free plans. List of services having free plans :<br>
<a href="https://zoho.com/mail">https://zoho.com/mail</a> - for 5 users. 5GB/user & 25 MB attachment limit, 1 domain.<br>
<a href="https://zoho.com/sprints">https://zoho.com/sprints</a> - for 5 users,5 Projects & 500MB storage.<br>
<a href="https://zoho.com/docs) — Free for 5 users with 1 GB upload limit & 5GB storage. Zoho Office Suite (Writer,Sheets & Show">https://zoho.com/docs) — Free for 5 users with 1 GB upload limit & 5GB storage. Zoho Office Suite (Writer,Sheets & Show</a> - Free for 5 users with 1 GB upload limit & 5GB storage. Zoho Office Suite (Writer,Sheets & Show) comes bundled with it.<br>
<a href="https://zoho.com/bugtracker">https://zoho.com/bugtracker</a> - Free for 3 users, 2 projects & 10 MB attachment limit. Same plan applies to [Bugtracker](https://zoho.com/bugtracker).<br>
<a href="https://zoho.com/connect">https://zoho.com/connect</a> - Team Collaboration free for 25 users with 3 groups, 3 custom apps, 3 Boards, 3 Manuals, 10 Integrations along with channels,events & forums.<br>
<a href="https://zoho.com/meeting">https://zoho.com/meeting</a> - Meetings with upto 3 meeting participants & 10 Webinar attendees.<br>
<a href="https://zoho.com/vault">https://zoho.com/vault</a> - Password Management free for Individuals.<br>
<a href="https://zoho.com/showtime">https://zoho.com/showtime</a> - Yet another Meeting software for training for a remote session upto 5 attendees.<br>
<a href="https://zoho.com/notebook">https://zoho.com/notebook</a> - A free alternative to Evernote.<br>
<a href="https://zoho.com/wiki">https://zoho.com/wiki</a> - Free for 3 users with 50 MB storage, unlimited pages, zip backups, RSS & Atom feed, access controls & customisable CSS.<br>
<a href="https://zoho.com/subscriptions">https://zoho.com/subscriptions</a> - Recurring Billing management free for 20 customers/subscriptions & 1 user with all the payment hosting done by Zoho themselves. Last 40 subscription metrics are stored<br>
<a href="https://zoho.com/checkout">https://zoho.com/checkout</a> - Product Billing management with 3 pages & up to 50 payments.<br>
<a href="https://zoho.com/assist">https://zoho.com/assist</a> - Customer Support management with 3 agents and private knowledge base, email tickets. Integrates with [Assist](https://zoho.com/assist) for 1 remote technician & 5 unattended computers.<br>
<a href="https://zoho.com/cliq">https://zoho.com/cliq</a> - Team chat software with 100 GB storage, unlimited users, 100 users per channel & SSO.<br>
<a href="https://zoho.com/campaigns">https://zoho.com/campaigns</a> - <br>
<a href="https://zoho.com/forms">https://zoho.com/forms</a> - <br>
<a href="https:/zoho.com/sign">https:/zoho.com/sign</a> - <br>
<a href="https://zoho.com/surveys">https://zoho.com/surveys</a> - <br>
<a href="https://zoho.com/bookings">https://zoho.com/bookings</a> - <br>
<a href="https://zoho.com/analytics">https://zoho.com/analytics</a> - <br>
<a href="https://zube.io">https://zube.io</a> - Project management with free plan for 4 Projects & 4 users. GitHub integration available.<br>
<a href="https://codeblocks.org">https://codeblocks.org</a> - Free Fortran & C/C++ IDE. Open Source and runs on Windows,macOS & Linux.<br>
<a href="https://elementor.com">https://elementor.com</a> - WordPress website builder. Free plan available with 40+ Basic Widgets.<br>
<a href="https://www.birdeatsbug.com/) — Report bugs faster (and better">https://www.birdeatsbug.com/) — Report bugs faster (and better</a> - Bug](https://www.birdeatsbug.com/) — Report bugs faster (and better). Record your screen with Bird browser extension, it will auto-capture technical data that engineers need to debug. Free tier suitable for small teams.<br>
<a href="https://stackby.com/">https://stackby.com/</a> - One tool that brings together flexibility of spreadsheets, power of databases and built-in integrations with your favorite business apps. Free plan includes unlimited users, 10 stacks, 2GB attachment per stack.<br>
<a href="https://clicky.com">https://clicky.com</a> - Website Analytics Platform. Free Plan for 1 website with 3000 views analytics.<br>
<a href="https://blynk.io">https://blynk.io</a> - A SaaS with API to control, build & evaluate IoT devices. Free Developer Plan with 5 devices,Free Cloud & data storage. Mobile Apps also available.<br>
<a href="https://clicky.com">https://clicky.com</a> - Website Analytics Platform. Free Plan for 1 website with 3000 views analytics.<br>
<a href="https://blynk.io">https://blynk.io</a> - A SaaS with API to control, build & evaluate IoT devices. Free Developer Plan with 5 devices,Free Cloud & data storage. Mobile Apps also available.<br>
<a href="https://mergify.io">https://mergify.io</a> - workflow automation and merge queue for GitHub — Free for public GitHub repositories<br>
<a href="https://www.namiml.com/">https://www.namiml.com/</a> - Complete platform for in-app purchases and subscriptions on iOS and Android, including no-code paywalls, CRM, and analytics. Free for all base features to run an IAP business.<br>
<a href="https://analytics.google.com/">https://analytics.google.com/</a> - — Google Analytics<br>
<a href="https://hotjar.com) — Website Analytics and Reports . Free Plan allows 2000 pageviews/day. 100 snapshots/day (max capacity: 300">https://hotjar.com) — Website Analytics and Reports . Free Plan allows 2000 pageviews/day. 100 snapshots/day (max capacity: 300</a> - Website Analytics and Reports . Free Plan allows 2000 pageviews/day. 100 snapshots/day (max capacity: 300). 3 snapshot heatmaps which can be stored for 365 days. Unlimited Team Members.<br>
<a href="https://statcounter.com/">https://statcounter.com/</a> - Website Viewer Analytics. Free plan for analytics of 500 most recent visitors.<br>
<a href="https://www.abstractapi.com/ip-geolocation-api">https://www.abstractapi.com/ip-geolocation-api</a> - API](https://www.abstractapi.com/ip-geolocation-api) — IP Geolocation API from Abstract - Extensive free plan allowing 200,000 requests per month.<br>
<a href="https://codegiant.io">https://codegiant.io</a> - Project Management with Repository hosting & CI/CD. Free Plan Offers Unlimited Repositories,Projects & Documents with 5 Team Members. 500 CI/CD minutes per month. 30000 Serverless Code Run minutes per month.1GB repository storage.<br>
<a href="https://powerbi.com">https://powerbi.com</a> - — Business Insights & Analytics by Microsoft. Free Plan offers limited use with 1 Million User licenses.<br>
<a href="https://www.manageengine.com/cloud-log-management">https://www.manageengine.com/cloud-log-management</a> - Cloud](https://www.manageengine.com/cloud-log-management) — Log Management service powered by Manage Engine. Free Plan offers 50 GB storage with 1 Month retention.<br>
<a href="https://arvancloud.com/) — Offers cloud related services (CDN,Cloud DNS, PaaS, Security etc.">https://arvancloud.com/) — Offers cloud related services (CDN,Cloud DNS, PaaS, Security etc.</a> - — Offers cloud related services (CDN,Cloud DNS, PaaS, Security etc.). Free plan offers :<br>
<a href="https://rocketgit.com">https://rocketgit.com</a> - Repository Hosting based on Git. Unlimited Public & Private repositories.<br>
<a href="https://similarweb.com">https://similarweb.com</a> - — Analytics for Web & Mobile Apps. Free Plan offers 5 results per metric, 1 month of mobile app data & 3 months of website data.<br>
<a href="https://snapshooter.com/">https://snapshooter.com/</a> - Backup solution for DigitalOcean, AWS, LightSail, Hetzner and Exoscale, with support for direct database, file system and application backups to s3 based storage. Provides a free plan with daily backups for one resource.<br>
<a href="https://miradore.com">https://miradore.com</a> - Management service. Stay up-to-date with your device fleet and secure an unlimited number of devices for free. Free plan offers basic features.<br>
<a href="https://bluej.org">https://bluej.org</a> - A free Java Development Environment designed for beginners, used by millions worldwide. Powered by Oracle & simple GUI to help beginners.<br>
<a href="https://automate.io">https://automate.io</a> - Simple and complex automation workflow tool with over 200+ app integrations. 300 monthly actions and 5 bots are free<br>
<a href="https://developer.deepar.ai) — Augmented reality face filters for any platform with one SDK. Free plan provides up to 10 monthly active users (MAU">https://developer.deepar.ai) — Augmented reality face filters for any platform with one SDK. Free plan provides up to 10 monthly active users (MAU</a> - Augmented reality face filters for any platform with one SDK. Free plan provides up to 10 monthly active users (MAU) and tracking up to 4 faces<br>
<a href="https://miradore.com">https://miradore.com</a> - Device Management service. Stay up-to-date with your device fleet and secure an unlimited number of devices for free. Free plan offers basic features.<br>
<a href="https://branch.io">https://branch.io</a> - Mobile Analytics Platform. Free Tier offers upto 10K Mobile App Users with deep-linking & other services.<br>
<a href="https://www.koyeb.com">https://www.koyeb.com</a> - Koyeb is a developer-friendly serverless platform to deploy apps globally. Seamlessly run Docker containers, web apps, and APIs with git-based deployment, native autoscaling, a global edge network, and built-in service mesh and discovery. Koyeb provides two nano services to run your apps with its forever-free tier and also sponsors open-source projects with free resources.<br>
<a href="https://freecurrencyapi.net/">https://freecurrencyapi.net/</a> - Free currency conversion and exchange rate data API. 10 requests/hour without an API key, 50 000 requests per month when you register for free.<br>
<a href="http://maps.stamen.com/">http://maps.stamen.com/</a> - Free map tiles and tile hosting.<br>
<a href="https://robocorp.com">https://robocorp.com</a> - Open-source stack for powering Automation Ops. Try out Cloud features and implement simple automations for free. Robot work 240 min/month, 10 Assistant runs, Storage of 100 MB.<br>
<a href="https://treescale.com/">https://treescale.com/</a> - Host and manage container images with group permissions. Free tier offers 1 GB storage for private repositories.<br>
<a href="https://www.lazarus-ide.org/">https://www.lazarus-ide.org/</a> - Lazarus is a Delphi compatible cross-platform IDE for Rapid Application Development.<br>
<a href="https://www.lazarus-ide.org/">https://www.lazarus-ide.org/</a> - Lazarus is a Delphi compatible cross-platform IDE for Rapid Application Development.<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>alphabetical order</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/98cf740e2a0fe6b0f7eb724292ec1f0b0313af39</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.lazarus-ide.org/">https://www.lazarus-ide.org/</a> - Lazarus is a Delphi compatible cross-platform IDE for Rapid Application Development.<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Add Lazarus IDE</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/ddbfc56cde99ffda2e4f6ffa4f720f17440f129c</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.lazarus-ide.org/">https://www.lazarus-ide.org/</a> - Lazarus is a Delphi compatible cross-platform IDE for Rapid Application Development.<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>adding treescale.com</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/d2493c9c718ac904491a89f9a473523bf2bee8f9</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://treescale.com/">https://treescale.com/</a> - Host and manage container images with group permissions. Free tier offers 1 GB storage for private repositories.<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Remove unreachable site</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/40d8097a7aa83961076c91048d2d9b37ca5264ac</link><description><![CDATA[ ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Remove ghostinspector</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/d04b807f9f1b552653eb2717ea809fc3628357e1</link><description><![CDATA[ ]]></description>
</item>

</channel>
</rss>
