<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel>
<title>New Free-For-Dev</title>
<description>New Free Resources</description>
<link></link>
<item>
	<title>Bumping 2 GB to 10 GB</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/293c6f9bd9c055a4b13c435bf253c3f054eca438</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://internxt.com">https://internxt.com</a> - Internxt Drive is a zero-knowledge file storage service that's based on absolute privacy and uncompromising security. Sign up and get 10 GB for free, forever!<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>remove disposable email services without contact details</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/c4f9519f269b9be39c3a751ca1b5c9ca1c4737ba</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://okso.app) - Minimalistic online drawing app. Allows creating fast sketches and visual notes. Exports sketches to PNG, JPG, SVG, and WEBP. Also installable as PWA. Free to use for everyone (no registration is needed">https://okso.app) - Minimalistic online drawing app. Allows creating fast sketches and visual notes. Exports sketches to PNG, JPG, SVG, and WEBP. Also installable as PWA. Free to use for everyone (no registration is needed</a> - Minimalistic online drawing app. Allows creating fast sketches and visual notes. Exports sketches to PNG, JPG, SVG, and WEBP. Also installable as PWA. Free to use for everyone (no registration is needed).<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Expanded description for Microtica</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/64d46dd7fa5ce7482dd517175131306affcefd74</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://microtica.com/">https://microtica.com/</a> - Spin up environments with ready-made infrastructure components, deploy apps on Kubernetes for free and support your production workloads. Free tier includes 2 services, 100 build minutes/month and 20 deployments/month on a shared Kubernetes Cluster provided by us.<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Update README.md</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/c033c1a0d7940de09b8d7b6f2a9b2f45ac24d8bc</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://easyvectors.com/">https://easyvectors.com/</a> - EasyVectors.com is a stock of quality free SVG vector art. Download best vector graphics absolutely for free.<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>added tldraw under Tools for Teams and Collaboration</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/81d87e028ea3ea57d145c779a3dc1cea84b37f8b</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://tldraw.com">https://tldraw.com</a> - Free open source white-boarding and diagramming tool with features such as smart arrows, snapping, sticky notes, and SVG export. Multiplayer mode for collaborative editing. Free official VS Code extension available as well.<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>summaryzing description</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/fc6951a8f2aeaf0517b7a93db3982ad8ef601386</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://rocket.chat/">https://rocket.chat/</a> - Open-source communication platform with Omnichannel features, Matrix Federation, Bridge with others apps, Unlimited messaging and Full messaging history.<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>improving RC description</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/d604c9d23a20e7d16fe46fa14a9aab6befada602</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://rocket.chat/">https://rocket.chat/</a> - Open-source, secure, and compliant communications platform includes features like: Apps Marketplace, White labeling, Omnichannel features and apps, Matrix Federation, Bridge to Slack, Teams, and others, End-to-end encryption, Unlimited 1:1 and group messaging, Full messaging history, and much more! Free Tier includes several listed features as Unlimited 1:1 and group messaging and Full messaging history.<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Add Cauldron.io</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/e7033f0ec2502205bd05b8fdc964dad954587a42</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://cauldron.io) — Analytics open source solution that allows users to aggregate information from multiple collaboration platforms as different types of data sources (Git, Github, Gitlab...">https://cauldron.io) — Analytics open source solution that allows users to aggregate information from multiple collaboration platforms as different types of data sources (Git, Github, Gitlab...</a> - Analytics open source solution that allows users to aggregate information from multiple collaboration platforms as different types of data sources (Git, Github, Gitlab...). Free tier includes unlimited number of reports.<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Add other Free Resources</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/09fec84abba3a269a5b1c8bea50ada0ad431a15c</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://utils.fun/en">https://utils.fun/en</a> - All offline daily and development tools based on the browser's computing power, including watermark generation, screen recording, encoding and decoding, encryption and decryption and code formatting, are completely free and do not upload any data to the cloud for processing.<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Add Microtica as a CI/CD tool</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/145d93caa1329f9873db161df67a2315aa17e3ff</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://microtica.com/">https://microtica.com/</a> - Spin up environments with ready-made infrastructure components, deploy apps on Kubernetes for free and support your production workloads<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Typo</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/69b8c09bfdd6d7be4a83301a2ce86c1d52d9f486</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://screenshotson.click">https://screenshotson.click</a> - Your API for Screenshots. With highly customizable options for capture. Free 100 screenshots/month.<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>

</channel>
</rss>
