<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel>
<title>New Free-For-Dev</title>
<description>New Free Resources</description>
<link></link>
<item>
	<title>Add Zuplo to API category</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/6d47e10e5ca191c517fcb8832eff8c053f30e0fa</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://zuplo.com/">https://zuplo.com/</a> - Add API Key authentication, rate limiting and developer documentation to any API in minutes. The free plan offers up to 10 projects, unlimited production edge environments, up to 250 API keys, 100K requests per month, 1GB egress per month.<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Update README.md</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/d2e7dfef56db23f9e0058c4cb75b169bc6ab3de6</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://onlineornot.com/">https://onlineornot.com/</a> - OnlineOrNot provides uptime monitoring for websites and APIs, monitoring for cron jobs and scheduled tasks. Also provides status pages. First 5 checks with a 3-minute interval are free. Free tier sends alerts via Slack, Discord, and Email.<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>docs: remove Scaleway. free 75GB storage not available anymore</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/c1b9bfc2bd3049b3258ebae28b8e6484d5fa632c</link><description><![CDATA[ ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Add deco.cx — edge app platform for instant ecommerce frontends</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/033131ca739fd0cbb073ed07b9d4785576b3bf0e</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.deco.cx/en/dev">https://www.deco.cx/en/dev</a> - Edge-native frontend platform with a visual CMS auto-generated from TypeScript code. Built-in A/B testing, content segmentation and realtime analytics. Perfect for content-heavy and Enterprise ecommerce websites. Free up to 5k pageviews/month or open-source/personal projects.<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>add: Platformatic</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/6e83be85c2b2880ced7d996838eaa095f6ca6970</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://platformatic.cloud/">https://platformatic.cloud/</a> - - Platformatic offers many open-source packages to wrap your Fastify application and deploy it in the Platformatic Cloud. Built in CD with a GitHub Action. [Free plan](https://platformatic.dev/pricing/) for hobbyists with a simple [GitHub login](https://platformatic.cloud/).<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Remove CometLLM and change Comet website</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/eff978dc3a3a3312f67446453eaadcfded3f6bd8</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.comet.com/site/">https://www.comet.com/site/</a> - The MLOps platform for experiment tracking, model production management, model registry, and full data lineage, covering your workflow from training straight through to production. Free for individuals and academics.<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>chore: improve sentence formation</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/d0098ee1d8ec040413a6c9403115e19dab8b7ad8</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://github.com/features/actions)(Free for Public Repos, 2000 min/month free for private repos">https://github.com/features/actions)(Free for Public Repos, 2000 min/month free for private repos</a> - Public Repos, 2000 min/month free for private repos)<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Add Comet</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/394835c43fce7fcec1efa2f11806a4e3ba38f5b7</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://github.com/comet-ml/comet-llm">https://github.com/comet-ml/comet-llm</a> - Log, visualize, organize, and search your prompt, prompt templates, prompt variables, prompt chains and other metadata in one convenient UI. We're now open-source!<br>
<a href="https://github.com/comet-ml/comet-examples">https://github.com/comet-ml/comet-examples</a> - The MLOps platform for experiment tracking, model production management, model registry, and full data lineage, covering your workflow from training straight through to production. Free for individuals and academics.<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>added Webstudio in Design & UI</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/22d2bd3969e06f3983f085695834fa7257fa7b9e</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://webstudio.is/">https://webstudio.is/</a> - Open-source alternative to Webflow. Free plan offers unlimited websites on their domain. 5 websites with custom domain. 10,000 page views/month. 2 GB asset storage.<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Update README.md</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/a9b963a0cddf9578e69c25be0d3b0244551d09cc</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev">https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev</a> - from Pull Requests, reviews, ideas, and work done by 1100+ people. You too can help by sending [Pull Requests](https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev) to add more services or by removing ones whose offerings have changed or been retired.<br>
<a href="#analytics-events-and-statistics">#analytics-events-and-statistics</a> - and Statistics](#analytics-events-and-statistics)<br>
<a href="#authentication-authorization-and-user-management">#authentication-authorization-and-user-management</a> - and User Management](#authentication-authorization-and-user-management)<br>
<a href="https://aws.amazon.com/codecommit/">https://aws.amazon.com/codecommit/</a> - 5 active users,50GB storage and 10000 requests per month<br>
<a href="https://azure.microsoft.com/services/app-service/) - 10 web, mobile or API apps (60 CPU minutes/day">https://azure.microsoft.com/services/app-service/) - 10 web, mobile or API apps (60 CPU minutes/day</a> - - 10 web, mobile or API apps (60 CPU minutes/day)<br>
<a href="https://azure.microsoft.com/services/load-balancer/) - 1 free public load-balanced IP (VIP">https://azure.microsoft.com/services/load-balancer/) - 1 free public load-balanced IP (VIP</a> - - 1 free public load-balanced IP (VIP)<br>
<a href="https://azure.microsoft.com/pricing/details/app-service/static/">https://azure.microsoft.com/pricing/details/app-service/static/</a> - Apps](https://azure.microsoft.com/pricing/details/app-service/static/) — Build, deploy, and host static apps and serverless functions with free SSL, Authentication/Authorization, and custom domains<br>
<a href="https://scalr.com/) - Scalr is a Terraform Automation and COllaboration (TACO">https://scalr.com/) - Scalr is a Terraform Automation and COllaboration (TACO</a> - Scalr is a Terraform Automation and COllaboration (TACO) product used to better collaboration and automation on infrastructure and configurations managed by Terraform. Full support of Terraform CLI, integration with OPA and a hierarchical configuration model. No SSO tax. All features are included. Use up to 50 runs/month for free.<br>
<a href="https://github.com/) — Unlimited public repositories and unlimited private repositories (with unlimited collaborators). Apart from this, some other free services(there are much more, but we list the main ones here">https://github.com/) — Unlimited public repositories and unlimited private repositories (with unlimited collaborators). Apart from this, some other free services(there are much more, but we list the main ones here</a> - Unlimited public repositories and unlimited private repositories (with unlimited collaborators). Apart from this, some other free services(there are much more, but we list the main ones here) provided are :<br>
<a href="https://ionicframework.com/appflow">https://ionicframework.com/appflow</a> - Repo and tools to develop applications with Ionic; also you have an ionic repo<br>
<a href="https://rocketgit.com">https://rocketgit.com</a> - Repository Hosting based on Git. Unlimited Public and private repositories.<br>
<a href="https://ip.city">https://ip.city</a> - 100 Free IP geolocation requests per day<br>
<a href="https://apitemplate.io">https://apitemplate.io</a> - Auto-generate images and PDF documents with a simple API or automation tools like Zapier & Airtable. No CSS/HTML is required. The free plan comes with 50 images/month and 3 templates.<br>
<a href="https://apitoolkit.io">https://apitoolkit.io</a> - All the tools you need to fully understand what's going on in your APIs and Backends. With automatic API contract validation and monitoring. The free plan covers servers with up to 20,000 requests per month.<br>
<a href="https://calendarific.com">https://calendarific.com</a> - Enterprise-grade Public holiday API service for over 200 countries. The free plan includes 1000 calls per month.<br>
<a href="https://www.canopyapi.co/">https://www.canopyapi.co/</a> - GraphQL API for Amazon.com product, search, and category data. The free plan includes 100 calls per month.<br>
<a href="https://www.clarifai.com">https://www.clarifai.com</a> - Image API for custom face recognition and detection. Able to train AI models. The free plan has 5000 calls per month.<br>
<a href="https://collect2.com">https://collect2.com</a> - Create an API endpoint to test, automate, and connect webhooks. The free plan allows for two datasets, 2000 records, 1 forwarder, and 1 alert.<br>
<a href="https://commercelayer.io">https://commercelayer.io</a> - - Composable commerce API that can build, place, and manage orders from any front end. The developer plan allows 100 orders per month and up to 1,000 SKUs for free.<br>
<a href="https://conversiontools.io/) - Online File Converter for documents, images, video, audio, and eBooks. REST API is available. Libraries for Node.js, PHP, Python. Support files up to 50 GB (for paid plans">https://conversiontools.io/) - Online File Converter for documents, images, video, audio, and eBooks. REST API is available. Libraries for Node.js, PHP, Python. Support files up to 50 GB (for paid plans</a> - - Online File Converter for documents, images, video, audio, and eBooks. REST API is available. Libraries for Node.js, PHP, Python. Support files up to 50 GB (for paid plans). The free tier is limited by file size and number of conversions per day.<br>
<a href="https://gchq.github.io/CyberChef/">https://gchq.github.io/CyberChef/</a> - A simple, intuitive web app for analyzing and decoding/encoding data without having to deal with complex tools or programming languages. Like a Swiss army knife of cryptography & encryption. All features are free to use, with no limit. Open source if you wish to self-host.<br>
<a href="https://dependabot.com/) Automated dependency updates for Ruby, JavaScript, Python, PHP, Elixir, Rust, Java (Maven and Gradle">https://dependabot.com/) Automated dependency updates for Ruby, JavaScript, Python, PHP, Elixir, Rust, Java (Maven and Gradle</a> - dependency updates for Ruby, JavaScript, Python, PHP, Elixir, Rust, Java (Maven and Gradle), .NET, Go, Elm, Docker, Terraform, Git Submodules, and GitHub Actions.<br>
<a href="https://djcheckup.com">https://djcheckup.com</a> - — Scan your Django site for security flaws with this free, automated checkup tool. Forked from the Pony Checkup site.<br>
<a href="https://www.meterian.io/">https://www.meterian.io/</a> - Monitor Java, Javascript, .NET, Scala, Ruby, and NodeJS projects for security vulnerabilities in dependencies. Free for one private project, unlimited projects for open source.<br>
<a href="https://openapi.security/">https://openapi.security/</a> - Free tool to quickly check the security of any OpenAPI / Swagger-based API. No signup is required.<br>
<a href="https://pixee.ai">https://pixee.ai</a> - Automated Product Security Engineer as a free GitHub bot that submits PRs to your Java code base to automatically resolve vulnerabilities. Other languages coming soon!<br>
<a href="https://recaptchame.com/">https://recaptchame.com/</a> - free reCAPTCHA and hCAPTCHA backend service. No Server-Side coding is needed. Works for static websites.<br>
<a href="https://ringcaptcha.com/">https://ringcaptcha.com/</a> - Tools to use the phone number as id, available for free<br>
<a href="https://account.seclookup.com/">https://account.seclookup.com/</a> - Seclookup APIs can enrich domain threat indicators in SIEM, provide comprehensive information on domain names, and improve threat detection & response. Get 50K lookups free [here](https://account.seclookup.com/).<br>
<a href="https://snyk.io">https://snyk.io</a> - Can find and fix known security vulnerabilities in your open-source dependencies. Unlimited tests and remediation for open-source projects. Limited to 200 tests/month for your private projects.<br>
<a href="https://soos.io">https://soos.io</a> - Free, unlimited SCA scans for open-source projects. Detect and fix security threats before release. Protect your projects with a simple and effective solution.<br>
<a href="https://protectumus.com) - Free website security check, site antivirus, and server firewall (WAF">https://protectumus.com) - Free website security check, site antivirus, and server firewall (WAF</a> - Free website security check, site antivirus, and server firewall (WAF) for PHP. Email notifications for registered users in the free tier.<br>
<a href="https://testtls.com">https://testtls.com</a> - Test an SSL/TLS service for secure server configuration, certificates, chains, etc. Not limited to HTTPS.<br>
<a href="https://threatconnect.com">https://threatconnect.com</a> - Threat intelligence: It is designed for individual researchers, analysts, and organizations who are starting to learn about cyber threat intelligence. Free up to 3 Users<br>
<a href="https://www.tinfoilsecurity.com/">https://www.tinfoilsecurity.com/</a> - Automated vulnerability scanning. The free plan allows weekly XSS scans<br>
<a href="https://virgilsecurity.com/">https://virgilsecurity.com/</a> - — Tools and services for implementing end-to-end encryption, database protection, IoT security, and more in your digital solution. Free for applications with up to 250 users.<br>
<a href="https://virushee.com/">https://virushee.com/</a> - Privacy-oriented file/data scanning powered by hybrid heuristic and AI-assisted engine. It is possible to use internal dynamic sandbox analysis. Limited to 50MB per file upload<br>
<a href="https://authress.io/">https://authress.io/</a> - Authentication login and access control, unlimited identity providers for any project. Facebook, Google, Twitter and more. The first 1000 API calls are free.<br>
<a href="https://www.logintc.com/) — Two-factor authentication (2FA">https://www.logintc.com/) — Two-factor authentication (2FA</a> - Two-factor authentication (2FA) by push notifications, free for 10 users, VPN, Websites, and SSH<br>
<a href="https://mojoauth.com/">https://mojoauth.com/</a> - MojoAuth makes it easy to implement Passwordless authentication on your web, mobile, or any application in minutes.<br>
<a href="https://www.onelogin.com/) — Identity as a Service (IDaaS">https://www.onelogin.com/) — Identity as a Service (IDaaS</a> - Identity as a Service (IDaaS), Single Sign-On Identity Provider, Cloud SSO IdP, 3 company apps, and 5 personal apps, unlimited users<br>
<a href="https://zitadel.com) — A turnkey user and access management that works for you and supports multi-tenant (B2B) use cases. Free for up to 25,000 authenticated requests, with all security features (no paywall for OTP, Passwordless, Policies, and so on">https://zitadel.com) — A turnkey user and access management that works for you and supports multi-tenant (B2B) use cases. Free for up to 25,000 authenticated requests, with all security features (no paywall for OTP, Passwordless, Policies, and so on</a> - — A turnkey user and access management that works for you and supports multi-tenant (B2B) use cases. Free for up to 25,000 authenticated requests, with all security features (no paywall for OTP, Passwordless, Policies, and so on).<br>
<a href="https://testapp.io">https://testapp.io</a> - Your go-to platform for making sure your mobile apps work as they should. Free plan: one app, analytics, unlimited versions & installs, and feedback collection.<br>
<a href="https://www.getupdraft.com">https://www.getupdraft.com</a> - Distribute mobile apps for testing. The free plan includes 1 app project, 3 app versions, 500 MB storage, and 100 app installations per month.<br>
<a href="https://appho.st">https://appho.st</a> - Mobile app hosting platform. The free plan includes 5 apps, 50 monthly downloads, and a maximum file size of 100MB.<br>
<a href="https://miradore.com">https://miradore.com</a> - Device Management service. Stay up-to-date with your device fleet and secure an unlimited number of devices for free. The free plan offers basic features.<br>
<a href="https://www.ably.com/">https://www.ably.com/</a> - Realtime messaging service with presence, persistence and guaranteed delivery. The free plan includes 3m messages per month, 100 peak connections, and 100 peak channels.<br>
<a href="https://www.courier.com/">https://www.courier.com/</a> - Single API for push, in-app, email, chat, SMS, and other messaging channels with template management and other features. The free plan includes 10,000 messages/mo.<br>
<a href="https://knock.app">https://knock.app</a> - Notifications infrastructure for developers. Send to multiple channels like in-app, email, SMS, Slack, and push with a single API call. The free plan includes 10,000 messages/mo.<br>
<a href="https://nats.io">https://nats.io</a> - [NATS.io](https://nats.io) as a service. Global, AWS, GCP, and Azure. Free forever with 4k msg size, 50 active connections, and 5GB of data per month.<br>
<a href="https://www.pubnub.com/">https://www.pubnub.com/</a> - Swift, Kotlin, and React messaging at 1 million transactions each month. Transactions may contain multiple messages.<br>
<a href="https://apiservice.eyeson.com/api-pricing">https://apiservice.eyeson.com/api-pricing</a> - - A video communication API service based on WebRTC (SFU, MCU) to build video platforms. Allows real-time data Injection, Video Layouts, Recordings, a fully featured hosted web UI (quickstart) or packages for custom UIs. Has a [free tier for developers](https://apiservice.eyeson.com/api-pricing) with 1000 meeting minutes a month.<br>
<a href="https://upstash.com/kafka">https://upstash.com/kafka</a> - - Serverless Kafka Cloud offering with per-request-pricing. It has a free tier with a maximum of 10,000 messages per day.<br>
<a href="https://logflare.app/">https://logflare.app/</a> - Free for up to 12,960,000 entries per app per month, 3 days retention<br>
<a href="https://logzab.com/">https://logzab.com/</a> - Audit trail management system. Free 1,000 user activity logs per month, 1-month retention, for up to 5 projects.<br>
<a href="https://crowdin.com/">https://crowdin.com/</a> - Unlimited projects, unlimited strings, and collaborators for Open Source<br>
<a href="https://lecto.ai/) - Machine Translation API with Free tier (30 free requests, 1000 translated characters per request">https://lecto.ai/) - Machine Translation API with Free tier (30 free requests, 1000 translated characters per request</a> - Machine Translation API with Free tier (30 free requests, 1000 translated characters per request). Integrated with the Loco Translate Wordpress plugin.<br>
<a href="https://tolgee.io">https://tolgee.io</a> - Free SaaS offering with limited translations, forever-free self-hosted version<br>
<a href="https://weblate.org/">https://weblate.org/</a> - It's free for libre projects with up to 10,000 string sources for the free tier and Unlimited Self-hosted on-premises.<br>
<a href="https://pingmeter.com/">https://pingmeter.com/</a> - 5 uptime monitors with 10-minute interval. Monitor SSH, HTTP, HTTPS, and any custom TCP ports.<br>
<a href="https://www.appdynamics.com/">https://www.appdynamics.com/</a> - Free for 24-hour metrics, application performance management agents limited to one Java, one .NET, one PHP, and one Node.js<br>
<a href="https://appspector.com/) - Mission control for remote iOS/Android/Flutter debugging. Free for small traffic usage (64MB of logs">https://appspector.com/) - Mission control for remote iOS/Android/Flutter debugging. Free for small traffic usage (64MB of logs</a> - Mission control for remote iOS/Android/Flutter debugging. Free for small traffic usage (64MB of logs).<br>
<a href="https://cronitor.io/">https://cronitor.io/</a> - Performance insights and uptime monitoring for cron jobs, websites, APIs and more. A free tier with 5 monitors.<br>
<a href="https://downtimemonkey.com/">https://downtimemonkey.com/</a> - 60 uptime monitors, 5-minute interval. Email, Slack alerts.<br>
<a href="https://economize.cloud">https://economize.cloud</a> - Economize helps demystify cloud infrastructure costs by organizing cloud resources to optimize and report the same. Free for up to $ 5,000 spent on Google Cloud Platform every month.<br>
<a href="https://www.elastic.co/solutions/apm">https://www.elastic.co/solutions/apm</a> - Instant performance insights for JS developers. Free with 24-hour data retention<br>
<a href="https://grafana.com/products/cloud/) - Grafana Cloud is a composable observability platform that integrates metrics and logs with Grafana. Free: 3 users, 10 dashboards, 100 alerts, metrics storage in Prometheus and Graphite (10,000 series, 14 days retention), logs storage in Loki (50 GB of logs, 14 days retention">https://grafana.com/products/cloud/) - Grafana Cloud is a composable observability platform that integrates metrics and logs with Grafana. Free: 3 users, 10 dashboards, 100 alerts, metrics storage in Prometheus and Graphite (10,000 series, 14 days retention), logs storage in Loki (50 GB of logs, 14 days retention</a> - - Grafana Cloud is a composable observability platform that integrates metrics and logs with Grafana. Free: 3 users, 10 dashboards, 100 alerts, metrics storage in Prometheus and Graphite (10,000 series, 14 days retention), logs storage in Loki (50 GB of logs, 14 days retention)<br>
<a href="https://www.inspector.dev">https://www.inspector.dev</a> - A complete Real-Time monitoring dashboard in less than one minute with a free forever tier.<br>
<a href="https://www.netdata.cloud/">https://www.netdata.cloud/</a> - Netdata is an open-source tool designed to collect real-time metrics. It's a growing product, and it can also be found on GitHub!<br>
<a href="https://www.newrelic.com">https://www.newrelic.com</a> - New Relic observability platform built to help engineers create more perfect software. From monoliths to serverless, you can instrument everything and then analyze, troubleshoot, and optimize your entire software stack. The free tier offers 100GB/month of free data ingest, 1 free full-access user, and unlimited free basic users.<br>
<a href="https://middleware.io/">https://middleware.io/</a> - Middleware observability platform provides complete visibility into your apps & stack, so you can monitor & diagnose issues at scale. They have a free forever plan for Dev community use that allows Log monitoring for up to 1M log events, Infrastructure monitoring & APM for up to 2 hosts.<br>
<a href="https://nixstats.com">https://nixstats.com</a> - Free for one server. E-Mail Notifications, public status page, 60-second interval, and more.<br>
<a href="https://onlineornot.com/) - OnlineOrNot is a reliable uptime monitor for both JS-based web apps and websites. 5 uptime checks (for static websites and APIs) with a 5-minute interval, 1 browser check with a 15-minute interval. Also provides automated public status pages (with support coming for 3rd party uptime monitoring">https://onlineornot.com/) - OnlineOrNot is a reliable uptime monitor for both JS-based web apps and websites. 5 uptime checks (for static websites and APIs) with a 5-minute interval, 1 browser check with a 15-minute interval. Also provides automated public status pages (with support coming for 3rd party uptime monitoring</a> - OnlineOrNot is a reliable uptime monitor for both JS-based web apps and websites. 5 uptime checks (for static websites and APIs) with a 5-minute interval, 1 browser check with a 15-minute interval. Also provides automated public status pages (with support coming for 3rd party uptime monitoring). Free for up to 3 users, alerts via Slack, Discord, and Email.<br>
<a href="https://syagent.com/">https://syagent.com/</a> - Noncommercial free server monitoring service, alerts and metrics.<br>
<a href="https://pagerly.io/) -  Manage on-calls on Slack  (integrates with Pagerduty, OpsGenie). Free up to 1 team (one team refers to one on call">https://pagerly.io/) -  Manage on-calls on Slack  (integrates with Pagerduty, OpsGenie). Free up to 1 team (one team refers to one on call</a> - Manage on-calls on Slack (integrates with Pagerduty, OpsGenie). Free up to 1 team (one team refers to one on call)<br>
<a href="https://pingbreak.com/">https://pingbreak.com/</a> - Modern uptime monitoring service. Check unlimited URLs and get downtime notifications via Discord, Slack, or email.<br>
<a href="https://pingpong.one/">https://pingpong.one/</a> - Advanced status page platform with monitoring. The free tier includes one public customizable status page with an SSL subdomain. Pro plan is offered to open-source projects and non-profits free of charge.<br>
<a href="https://home.robusta.dev/">https://home.robusta.dev/</a> - Powerful Kubernetes monitoring based on Prometheus. Bring your own Prometheus or install the all-in-one bundle. The free tier includes up to 20 Kubernetes nodes. Alerts via Slack, Microsoft Teams, Discord, and more. Integrations with PagerDuty, OpsGenie, VictorOps, DataDog, and many other tools.<br>
<a href="https://sematext.com/">https://sematext.com/</a> - Free for 24-hour metrics, unlimited number of servers, 10 custom metrics, 500,000 custom metrics data points, unlimited dashboards, users, etc.<br>
<a href="https://uptimetoolbox.com/">https://uptimetoolbox.com/</a> - Free monitoring for 5 websites, 60-second intervals, public statuspage.<br>
<a href="https://www.zenduty.com/">https://www.zenduty.com/</a> - End-to-end incident management, alerting, on-call management, and response orchestration platform for network operations, site reliability engineering, and DevOps teams. Free for up to 5 users.<br>
<a href="https://robomiri.com/">https://robomiri.com/</a> - RoboMiri is a stable uptime monitor that offers a wide range of monitors: cronjob, keyword, website, port, ping. 25 uptime checks with 3-minute interval checks for free. Alerts via Phone Call, SMS, Email, and Webhooks.<br>
<a href="https://betterstack.com/better-uptime">https://betterstack.com/better-uptime</a> - - Uptime monitoring, incident management, on-call scheduling/alerting, and status pages in a single product. 10 monitors with 3 min check frequency and status pages are included on the free plan.<br>
<a href="https://pulsetic.com">https://pulsetic.com</a> - 10 monitors, 6 Months of historical Uptime/Logs, unlimited status pages, and custom domains included! For unlimited time and unlimited email alerts for free. No credit card is required.<br>
<a href="https://catchjs.com/">https://catchjs.com/</a> - JavaScript error tracking with screenshots and click trails. Free for open-source projects.<br>
<a href="https://elmah.io/">https://elmah.io/</a> - Error logging and uptime monitoring for web developers. Free Small Business subscription for open-source projects.<br>
<a href="https://embrace.io/">https://embrace.io/</a> - Mobile app monitoring. Free for small teams with up to 1 million user sessions per year.<br>
<a href="https://exceptionless.com">https://exceptionless.com</a> - Real-time error, feature, log reporting, and more. Free for 3k events per month/1 user. Open source and easy to self-host for unlimited use.<br>
<a href="https://glitchtip.com/">https://glitchtip.com/</a> - Simple, open-source error tracking. Compatible with open-source Sentry SDKs. 1000 events per month for free, or can self-host with no limits<br>
<a href="https://sentry.io/">https://sentry.io/</a> - Sentry tracks app exceptions in real time and has a small free plan. Free for 5k errors per month/ 1 user, unrestricted use if self-hosted<br>
<a href="https://axiom.co/">https://axiom.co/</a> - Store up to 0.5 TB of logs with 30-day retention. Includes integrations with platforms like Vercel and advanced data querying with email/Discord notifiers.<br>
<a href="https://docsearch.algolia.com/">https://docsearch.algolia.com/</a> - Hosted search solution with typo-tolerance, relevance, and UI libraries to easily create search experiences. The free "Build" plan includes 1M documents and 10K searches/month. Also offers [developer documentation search](https://docsearch.algolia.com/) for free.<br>
<a href="https://www.commandbar.com/">https://www.commandbar.com/</a> - Unified Search Bar as-a-service, web-based UI widget/plugin that allows your users to search contents, navigations, features, etc. within your product, which helps discoverability. Free for up to 1,000 Monthly Active Users, unlimited commands.<br>
<a href="https://magny.io) - SaaS service that helps implement command palettes (e.g. in-app search">https://magny.io) - SaaS service that helps implement command palettes (e.g. in-app search</a> - SaaS service that helps implement command palettes (e.g. in-app search), which significantly decreases the time users find anything in an app, leveraging the user experience and efficiency.<br>
<a href="https://pagedart.com/">https://pagedart.com/</a> - AI search as a service the free tier includes 1,000 Documents and 50,000 searches. Larger free tiers are possible for worthwhile projects.<br>
<a href="https://www.meilisearch.com/">https://www.meilisearch.com/</a> - An open-source, lightning-fast, and hyper-relevant search engine that fits effortlessly into your apps, websites, and workflow. The free plan includes 100K documents and 10K searches/month.<br>
<a href="https://www.antideo.com">https://www.antideo.com</a> - 10 API requests per hour for email verification, IP, and phone number validation in the free tier. No Credit Cards are required.<br>
<a href="https://burnermail.io/">https://burnermail.io/</a> - Free 5 Burner Email Addresses, 1 Mailbox, 7-day Mailbox History<br>
<a href="https://contact.do/) — Contact form in a link (bitly for contact forms">https://contact.do/) — Contact form in a link (bitly for contact forms</a> - Contact form in a link (bitly for contact forms)<br>
<a href="https://www.emailjs.com/">https://www.emailjs.com/</a> - This is not a full email server; this is just an email client that you can use to send emails right from the client without exposing your credentials, the free tier has 200 monthly requests, 2 email templates, Requests up to 50Kb, Limited contacts history.<br>
<a href="https://fakermail.com/">https://fakermail.com/</a> - Free, temporary email for testing with the last 100 email accounts stored.<br>
<a href="https://inboxkitten.com/">https://inboxkitten.com/</a> - Free temporary/disposable email inbox, with up-to 3-day email auto-deletes. Open source and can be self-hosted.<br>
<a href="https://www.mail-tester.com">https://www.mail-tester.com</a> - Test if the email's DNS/SPF/DKIM/DMARC settings are correct, 20 free/month<br>
<a href="https://dkimvalidator.com/">https://dkimvalidator.com/</a> - Test if the email's DNS/SPF/DKIM/DMARC settings are correct, free service by roundsphere.com<br>
<a href="https://www.mailinator.com/">https://www.mailinator.com/</a> - Free, public email system where you can use any inbox you want<br>
<a href="https://mailtie.com/">https://mailtie.com/</a> - Free Email Forwarding for Your Domain. No registration is required. Free Forever.<br>
<a href="https://queuemail.dev) — Reliable email delivery API. Free tier (10,000 emails/per month">https://queuemail.dev) — Reliable email delivery API. Free tier (10,000 emails/per month</a> - Reliable email delivery API. Free tier (10,000 emails/per month). Send asynchronously. Use several SMTP servers. Blacklists, Logging, Tracking, Webhooks, and more...<br>
<a href="https://quickemailverification.com">https://quickemailverification.com</a> - Verify 100 emails daily for free on a free tier along with other free APIs like DEA Detector, DNS Lookup, SPF Detector, and more.<br>
<a href="https://simplelogin.io/) – Open source, self-hostable email alias/forwarding solution. Free 5 Aliases, unlimited bandwidth, unlimited reply/send. Free for educational staff (student, researcher, etc.">https://simplelogin.io/) – Open source, self-hostable email alias/forwarding solution. Free 5 Aliases, unlimited bandwidth, unlimited reply/send. Free for educational staff (student, researcher, etc.</a> - Open source, self-hostable email alias/forwarding solution. Free 5 Aliases, unlimited bandwidth, unlimited reply/send. Free for educational staff (student, researcher, etc.).<br>
<a href="https://skiff.com/">https://skiff.com/</a> - source, end-to-end encrypted anonymous email service, no additional details asked at signup, free 10GB drive storage, 1 custom domain for your own website, free 4 aliases for your email address per account. Additional Crypto Wallet support for the E2EE environment.<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>

</channel>
</rss>
