<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel>
<title>New Free-For-Dev</title>
<description>New Free Resources</description>
<link></link>
<item>
	<title>Add Molasses</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/9cfc01fbae0c6f923f5433760fa47769ec37681c</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.molasses.app">https://www.molasses.app</a> - Powerful feature flags and A/B testing. Free up to 3 environments with 5 feature flags each.<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Fix grafana cloud description</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/12da2e5d091b9d0710b6a7dd3db315e112681e2f</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://grafana.com/products/cloud/) - Grafana Cloud is a composable observability platform, integrating metrics and logs with Grafana. Free: 3 users, 10 dashboards, 100 alerts, metrics storage in Prometheus and Graphite (10,000 series, 14 days retention), logs storage in Loki (50 GB of logs, 14 days retention">https://grafana.com/products/cloud/) - Grafana Cloud is a composable observability platform, integrating metrics and logs with Grafana. Free: 3 users, 10 dashboards, 100 alerts, metrics storage in Prometheus and Graphite (10,000 series, 14 days retention), logs storage in Loki (50 GB of logs, 14 days retention</a> - - Grafana Cloud is a composable observability platform, integrating metrics and logs with Grafana. Free: 3 users, 10 dashboards, 100 alerts, metrics storage in Prometheus and Graphite (10,000 series, 14 days retention), logs storage in Loki (50 GB of logs, 14 days retention)<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Add Grafana Cloud Free plan</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/3e153735294797921ad69b5597d369abe04a2d0a</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://grafana.com/products/cloud/) - Grafana Cloud. Free: 3 users, 10 dashboards, 100 alerts, metrics storage in Prometheus and Graphite (10,000 series, 14 days retention), logs storage in Loki (50 GB of logs, 14 days retention">https://grafana.com/products/cloud/) - Grafana Cloud. Free: 3 users, 10 dashboards, 100 alerts, metrics storage in Prometheus and Graphite (10,000 series, 14 days retention), logs storage in Loki (50 GB of logs, 14 days retention</a> - - Grafana Cloud. Free: 3 users, 10 dashboards, 100 alerts, metrics storage in Prometheus and Graphite (10,000 series, 14 days retention), logs storage in Loki (50 GB of logs, 14 days retention)<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Update README.md</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/a197e9cf782d1f9f936f861c37b767d49cfde199</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://quickmocker.com/) — Manage online fake API endpoints under your own subdomain, forward requests to localhost URL for webhooks development and testing, use RegExp and multiple HTTP methods for URL path, prioritize endpoints, more than 100 shortcodes (dynamic or fake response values) for response templating, import from OpenAPI (Swagger">https://quickmocker.com/) — Manage online fake API endpoints under your own subdomain, forward requests to localhost URL for webhooks development and testing, use RegExp and multiple HTTP methods for URL path, prioritize endpoints, more than 100 shortcodes (dynamic or fake response values) for response templating, import from OpenAPI (Swagger</a> - Manage online fake API endpoints under your own subdomain, forward requests to localhost URL for webhooks development and testing, use RegExp and multiple HTTP methods for URL path, prioritize endpoints, more than 100 shortcodes (dynamic or fake response values) for response templating, import from OpenAPI (Swagger) Specifications in JSON format, proxy requests, restrict endpoint by IP address and authorization header. Free account provides 1 random subdomain, 10 endpoints, 5 RegExp URL paths, 50 shortcodes per endpoint, 100 requests per day, 50 history records in requests log.<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>added graph cms</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/16be8b61a9b577e9814ac2065f1ce3716227a87c</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://graphcms.com/">https://graphcms.com/</a> - Offers free tier for small projects. GraphQL first API. Move away from legacy solutions to the GraphQL native Headless CMS - and deliver omnichannel content API first.<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Remove Postale.io</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/c6f103baa559c66cb786150292610a5203117045</link><description><![CDATA[ ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>docs: changes in gitlab ci free plan</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/f7918ab06b8bb52f5109821ba54daa6fbc28dd3a</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://about.gitlab.com/product/continuous-integration/">https://about.gitlab.com/product/continuous-integration/</a> - Create pipelines directly from Git repositories using GitLab's CI service. 400 mins/mo per top-level group<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Add StackHawk</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/dfd020c82a48ac721bf93d027b2adbd79fd3e72d</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://etf-data.com/">https://etf-data.com/</a> - API](https://etf-data.com/) - Quality European ETF, ETN and ETC data, updated daily. The API offers complete overview including sector, country, factor, dividend yield and valuations. Additionally basic information such as domicile, followed index, asset class, fee, currency, replication method, distribution type and frequency. 50 free API calls per day.<br>
<a href="https://www.scraperapi.com/">https://www.scraperapi.com/</a> - — Cloud based web scraping API handles proxies, browsers, and CAPTCHAs. Scrape any web page with a simple API call. Get started with 1000 free API calls/month.<br>
<a href="https://unixtime.co.za">https://unixtime.co.za</a> - Free API to convert Unixtime to DateTime and vice versa.<br>
<a href="https://www.stackhawk.com/">https://www.stackhawk.com/</a> - application scanning throughout your pipeline to find and fix security bugs before they hit production. Unlimited scans and environments for a single app.<br>
<a href="https://testtls.com">https://testtls.com</a> - Test a SSL/TLS service for secure server configuration, certificates, chains etc. Not limited to HTTPS.<br>
<a href="https://www.deta.sh">https://www.deta.sh</a> - Deploy unlimited number of Node.js and Python apps for free up to 50k requests/month. Includes free DBs, Auth and email.<br>
<a href="https://theendlessweb.com/">https://theendlessweb.com/</a> - — 300 MB storage, Free SSL, PHP, MySQL, FTP, free sub-domains, E-Mail, DNS, beatiful panel UI. One of the best!<br>
<a href="https://fosshost.org/">https://fosshost.org/</a> - Free open source hosting VPS, web, storage and mirror hosting<br>
<a href="https://www.cloudamqp.com/">https://www.cloudamqp.com/</a> - RabbitMQ as a Service, up to 1M messages/month and 20 connections free<br>
<a href="https://grapedrop.com/">https://grapedrop.com/</a> - Responsive, powerful, SEO optimized web page builder based on GrapesJS Framework. Free for first 5 pages, unlimited custom domains, all features and simple usage.<br>
<a href="https://graphcomment.com/">https://graphcomment.com/</a> - GraphComment is a comments platform that helps you build an active community from website’s audience.<br>
<a href="https://form2channel.com">https://form2channel.com</a> - Place a static html form on your website and receive submissions directly to Google Sheets, Email, Slack, Telegram or Http. No coding necessary.<br>
<a href="https://github.com/tvvocold/FOSS-for-Dev">https://github.com/tvvocold/FOSS-for-Dev</a> - FOSS for Dev](https://github.com/tvvocold/FOSS-for-Dev) — A hub of free and Open Source software for developers<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Added CodeKeep</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/79ddc9d01cf90cfa8fe2a13f1112ac7c860d04f1</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://codekeep.io">https://codekeep.io</a> - Google Keep for Code Snippets. Organize,Discover and share code snippets, featuring a powerful code screenshot tool with preset templates and linking feature.<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>add Ubiq Security</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/00bd79b7a020dd4946f44a096ab4993f072a92e4</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://ubiqsecurity.com/">https://ubiqsecurity.com/</a> - — Encrypt and decrypt data with 3 lines of code and automatic key management. Free for 1 application and up to 1,000,000 encryptions per month.<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>

</channel>
</rss>
