<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel>
<title>New Free-For-Dev</title>
<description>New Free Resources</description>
<link></link>
<item>
	<title>Grammer changes!</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/0f93853b63fc6edcadbd12ed4c6fd024f7f69d7e</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.make.com/en">https://www.make.com/en</a> - Workflow automation tool that lets you connect apps and automate workflows using UI. It supports many apps and the most popular APIs. Free for public GitHub repositories, and free tier with 100 Mb, 1000 Operations and 15 minutes of minimum interval.<br>
<a href="https://microtica.com/) - Start up environments with ready-made infrastructure components, deploy apps on AWS for free, and support your production workloads. The free tier includes 1 Environment (on your AWS account">https://microtica.com/) - Start up environments with ready-made infrastructure components, deploy apps on AWS for free, and support your production workloads. The free tier includes 1 Environment (on your AWS account</a> - Start up environments with ready-made infrastructure components, deploy apps on AWS for free, and support your production workloads. The free tier includes 1 Environment (on your AWS account), 2 Kubernetes Services, 100 build minutes per month, and 20 monthly deployments.<br>
<a href="https://appetize.io">https://appetize.io</a> - Test your Android & iOS apps on this Cloud Based Android Phone / Tablets emulator and iPhone/iPad simulators directly in your browser. The free tier includes one concurrent session with 100 minutes of usage per month. No limit on app size.<br>
<a href="https://apptim.com) — A mobile testing tool that enables people without performance engineering skills to evaluate an app's performance and user experience (UX">https://apptim.com) — A mobile testing tool that enables people without performance engineering skills to evaluate an app's performance and user experience (UX</a> - A mobile testing tool that enables people without performance engineering skills to evaluate an app's performance and user experience (UX). A desktop version using your own device is 100% FREE with unlimited tests on both iOS and Android.<br>
<a href="https://bencher.dev/">https://bencher.dev/</a> - A continuous benchmarking tool suite designed to catch CI performance regressions. Free for all public projects.<br>
<a href="https://bugbug.io/">https://bugbug.io/</a> - Lightweight test automation tool for web applications. It is easy to learn and doesn't require coding. You can run unlimited tests on your own computer for free. For an additional monthly fee, you also get cloud monitoring and CI/CD integration.<br>
<a href="https://www.lambdatest.com/open-source-cross-browser-testing-tool">https://www.lambdatest.com/open-source-cross-browser-testing-tool</a> - Manual, visual, screenshot, and automated browser testing on selenium and cypress, [free for Open Source](https://www.lambdatest.com/open-source-cross-browser-testing-tool)<br>
<a href="https://www.cypress.io/">https://www.cypress.io/</a> - Fast, easy and reliable testing for anything that runs in a browser. Cypress Test Runner is always free and open-source with no restrictions and limitations. Cypress Dashboard is free for open-source projects for up to 5 users.<br>
<a href="https://cypress.preflight.com/">https://cypress.preflight.com/</a> - by Preflight](https://cypress.preflight.com/) - Create AI-powered Cypress Tests/POM models on your browser. It's open-source, except for the AI part. It's free for 5 monthly test creations with Self-healing scripts, Email, and Visual testing.<br>
<a href="https://www.gremlin.com/gremlin-free-software">https://www.gremlin.com/gremlin-free-software</a> - Gremlin's Chaos Engineering tools allow you to safely and securely inject failure into your systems to find weaknesses before they cause customer-facing issues. Gremlin Free provides access to Shutdown and CPU attacks on up to 5 hosts or containers.<br>
<a href="https://www.gridlastic.com/">https://www.gridlastic.com/</a> - Selenium Grid testing with a free plan of up to 4 simultaneous selenium nodes/10 grid starts/4,000 test minutes/month<br>
<a href="https://katalon.com) - Provides a testing platform that can help teams of all sizes at different levels of testing maturity, including  Katalon Studio, TestOps (+ Visual Testing free">https://katalon.com) - Provides a testing platform that can help teams of all sizes at different levels of testing maturity, including  Katalon Studio, TestOps (+ Visual Testing free</a> - Provides a testing platform that can help teams of all sizes at different levels of testing maturity, including Katalon Studio, TestOps (+ Visual Testing free), TestCloud and Katalon Recorder.<br>
<a href="https://keploy.io/) - Keploy is a functional testing toolkit for developers. By recording API calls, it generates E2E tests for APIs (KTests) and mocks or stubs(KMocks">https://keploy.io/) - Keploy is a functional testing toolkit for developers. By recording API calls, it generates E2E tests for APIs (KTests) and mocks or stubs(KMocks</a> - Keploy is a functional testing toolkit for developers. By recording API calls, it generates E2E tests for APIs (KTests) and mocks or stubs(KMocks). It is free for Open Source projects.<br>
<a href="https://www.loadmill.com/">https://www.loadmill.com/</a> - Automatically create API and load tests by analyzing network traffic. Simulate up to 50 concurrent users for up to 60 minutes for free monthly.<br>
<a href="https://preflight.com">https://preflight.com</a> - No-code automated web testing. Record tests on your browser that are resilient to UI changes and run them on Windows machines. Could you integrate with your CI/CD? The free plan includes 50 monthly test runs with video, HTML sessions, and more.<br>
<a href="https://percy.io">https://percy.io</a> - Add visual testing to any web app, static site, style guide, or component library. Unlimited team members, Demo app, and unlimited projects, 5,000 snapshots/month.<br>
<a href="https://opensource.saucelabs.com/">https://opensource.saucelabs.com/</a> - Cross-browser, Selenium, and mobile testing. The free plan includes 2000 credits per week. They also provide free licenses for selected open-source projects, which can be requested [here](https://opensource.saucelabs.com/).<br>
<a href="https://snippets.uilicious.com">https://snippets.uilicious.com</a> - It's like CodePen but for cross-browser testing. UI-licious lets you write tests like user stories and offers a free platform - UI-licious Snippets - that allows you to run unlimited tests on Chrome with no sign-up required for up to 3 minutes per test run. Found a bug? You can copy the unique URL to your test to show your devs exactly how to reproduce the bug.<br>
<a href="https://github.com/marketplace/testspace-com">https://github.com/marketplace/testspace-com</a> - A Dashboard for publishing automated test results and a Framework for implementing manual tests as code using GitHub. The service is [free for Open Source](https://github.com/marketplace/testspace-com) and accounts for 450 monthly results.<br>
<a href="https://www.tesults.com">https://www.tesults.com</a> - Test results reporting and test case management. Integrates with popular test frameworks. Open Source software developers, individuals, educators, and small teams getting started can request discounted and free offerings beyond basic free projects.<br>
<a href="https://qase.io">https://qase.io</a> - Test management system for Dev and QA teams. Manage test cases, compose test runs, perform tests, track defects, and measure impact. The free tier includes all core features, with 500MB available for attachments and up to 3 users.<br>
<a href="https://knapsackpro.com">https://knapsackpro.com</a> - Speed up your tests with optimal test suite parallelization on any CI provider. Split Ruby, JavaScript tests on parallel CI nodes to save time. Free plan for up to 10 minutes of test files and free unlimited plan for Open Source projects.<br>
<a href="https://webhook.site">https://webhook.site</a> - Verify webhooks, outbound HTTP requests, or emails with a custom URL. A temporary URL and email address are always free.<br>
<a href="https://vaadin.com">https://vaadin.com</a> - Build scalable UIs in Java or TypeScript, and use the integrated tooling, components, and design system to iterate faster, design better, and simplify the development process. Unlimited Projects with five years free maintenance.<br>
<a href="https://webhook-test.com">https://webhook-test.com</a> - Debug and inspect webhooks and HTTP requests with a unique URL during integration. Completely free, you can create an unlimited number of URLs and receive requests.<br>
<a href="https://atomist.com/">https://atomist.com/</a> - A quicker and more convenient way to automate various development tasks. Now in beta.<br>
<a href="https://www.codenotary.io/">https://www.codenotary.io/</a> - Open Source platform with indelible proof to notarize code, files, directories, or container<br>
<a href="https://gchq.github.io/CyberChef/">https://gchq.github.io/CyberChef/</a> - A simple, intuitive web app for analyzing and decoding/encoding data without dealing with complex tools or programming languages. Like a Swiss army knife of cryptography & encryption. All features are free to use, with no limit. Open source if you wish to self-host.<br>
<a href="https://doppler.com/">https://doppler.com/</a> - Universal Secrets Manager for application secrets and config, with support for syncing to various cloud providers. Free for five users with basic access controls.<br>
<a href="https://www.ssllabs.com/ssltest/">https://www.ssllabs.com/ssltest/</a> - Intense analysis of the configuration of any SSL web server<br>
<a href="https://ubiqsecurity.com/">https://ubiqsecurity.com/</a> - — Encrypt and decrypt data with three lines of code and automatic key management. Free for one application and up to 1,000,000 encryptions per month.<br>
<a href="https://auth0.com/">https://auth0.com/</a> - Hosted SSO. Up to 7000 active users and two social identity providers.<br>
<a href="https://www.cloud-iam.com/">https://www.cloud-iam.com/</a> - Keycloak Identity and Access Management as a Service. Free up to 100 users and one realm.<br>
<a href="https://duo.com/) — Two-factor authentication (2FA">https://duo.com/) — Two-factor authentication (2FA</a> - Two-factor authentication (2FA) for website or app. Free for ten users, all authentication methods, unlimited, integrations, hardware tokens.<br>
<a href="https://kinde.com/">https://kinde.com/</a> - Simple, robust authentication you can integrate with your product in minutes. Everything you need to get started with 7,500 free MAU.<br>
<a href="https://www.logintc.com/) — Two-factor authentication (2FA">https://www.logintc.com/) — Two-factor authentication (2FA</a> - Two-factor authentication (2FA) by push notifications, free for ten users, VPN, Websites, and SSH<br>
<a href="https://www.onelogin.com/) — Identity as a Service (IDaaS">https://www.onelogin.com/) — Identity as a Service (IDaaS</a> - Identity as a Service (IDaaS), Single Sign-On Identity Provider, Cloud SSO IdP, three company apps, and five personal apps, unlimited users<br>
<a href="https://warrant.dev/">https://warrant.dev/</a> - Hosted enterprise-grade authorization and access control service for your apps. The free tier includes 1 million monthly API requests and 1,000 authz rules.<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Add Zuplo to API category</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/6d47e10e5ca191c517fcb8832eff8c053f30e0fa</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://zuplo.com/">https://zuplo.com/</a> - Add API Key authentication, rate limiting and developer documentation to any API in minutes. The free plan offers up to 10 projects, unlimited production edge environments, up to 250 API keys, 100K requests per month, 1GB egress per month.<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Update README.md</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/d2e7dfef56db23f9e0058c4cb75b169bc6ab3de6</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://onlineornot.com/">https://onlineornot.com/</a> - OnlineOrNot provides uptime monitoring for websites and APIs, monitoring for cron jobs and scheduled tasks. Also provides status pages. First 5 checks with a 3-minute interval are free. Free tier sends alerts via Slack, Discord, and Email.<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>docs: remove Scaleway. free 75GB storage not available anymore</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/c1b9bfc2bd3049b3258ebae28b8e6484d5fa632c</link><description><![CDATA[ ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Add deco.cx — edge app platform for instant ecommerce frontends</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/033131ca739fd0cbb073ed07b9d4785576b3bf0e</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.deco.cx/en/dev">https://www.deco.cx/en/dev</a> - Edge-native frontend platform with a visual CMS auto-generated from TypeScript code. Built-in A/B testing, content segmentation and realtime analytics. Perfect for content-heavy and Enterprise ecommerce websites. Free up to 5k pageviews/month or open-source/personal projects.<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>add: Platformatic</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/6e83be85c2b2880ced7d996838eaa095f6ca6970</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://platformatic.cloud/">https://platformatic.cloud/</a> - - Platformatic offers many open-source packages to wrap your Fastify application and deploy it in the Platformatic Cloud. Built in CD with a GitHub Action. [Free plan](https://platformatic.dev/pricing/) for hobbyists with a simple [GitHub login](https://platformatic.cloud/).<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Remove CometLLM and change Comet website</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/eff978dc3a3a3312f67446453eaadcfded3f6bd8</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.comet.com/site/">https://www.comet.com/site/</a> - The MLOps platform for experiment tracking, model production management, model registry, and full data lineage, covering your workflow from training straight through to production. Free for individuals and academics.<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>chore: improve sentence formation</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/d0098ee1d8ec040413a6c9403115e19dab8b7ad8</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://github.com/features/actions)(Free for Public Repos, 2000 min/month free for private repos">https://github.com/features/actions)(Free for Public Repos, 2000 min/month free for private repos</a> - Public Repos, 2000 min/month free for private repos)<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Add Comet</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/394835c43fce7fcec1efa2f11806a4e3ba38f5b7</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://github.com/comet-ml/comet-llm">https://github.com/comet-ml/comet-llm</a> - Log, visualize, organize, and search your prompt, prompt templates, prompt variables, prompt chains and other metadata in one convenient UI. We're now open-source!<br>
<a href="https://github.com/comet-ml/comet-examples">https://github.com/comet-ml/comet-examples</a> - The MLOps platform for experiment tracking, model production management, model registry, and full data lineage, covering your workflow from training straight through to production. Free for individuals and academics.<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>added Webstudio in Design & UI</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/22d2bd3969e06f3983f085695834fa7257fa7b9e</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://webstudio.is/">https://webstudio.is/</a> - Open-source alternative to Webflow. Free plan offers unlimited websites on their domain. 5 websites with custom domain. 10,000 page views/month. 2 GB asset storage.<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>

</channel>
</rss>
