<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel>
<title>New Free-For-Dev</title>
<description>New Free Resources</description>
<link></link>
<item>
	<title>Update README.md</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/38f47e3540cbacc9486d4dabcc0262b77a33c80c</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://github.com/willin/js.cool">https://github.com/willin/js.cool</a> - Free js.cool subdomains for GitHub Pages and Vercel.<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>add domain js.cool</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/c6e4c49d2389f829deb7ab49ebadc39893fb9715</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://github.com/willin/js-cool">https://github.com/willin/js-cool</a> - Free js.cool subdomains for GitHub Pages and Vercel.<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Add Orchest</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/846abc8647ff06bf14d3e643c01b89ea21b33064</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://orchest.io">https://orchest.io</a> - Visual pipeline editor and workflow orchestrator for data science, 1 instance for free, open source version available.<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>chore(): update cronhooks description</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/6e96e96c08a19ae5a92ab872feb1e0326c0d07d0</link><description><![CDATA[ ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>chore(): update cronhooks description</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/e090bf903e384e61f21b6e981fdbb3bb0afbf023</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://datelist.io">https://datelist.io</a> - Online booking system for your website<br>
<a href="https://tempmailo.com/">https://tempmailo.com/</a> - Unlimited free temp email addresses. Autoexpire in two days.<br>
<a href="https://shtab.app/">https://shtab.app/</a> - Project management service that makes collaboration in the office and remotely transparent with tracker based on AI.<br>
<a href="https://atomist.com/">https://atomist.com/</a> - A quicker and more convenient way to automate a variety of development tasks. Now in beta.<br>
<a href="https://www.ably.com/">https://www.ably.com/</a> - Realtime messaging service with presence, persistence and guaranteed delivery. Free plan includes 3m messages per month, 100 peak connections and 100 peak channels.<br>
<a href="https://forwardemail.net) — Free email forwarding for custom domains. Create and forward an unlimited amount of email addresses with your domain name (**note**: You must pay if you use .casa, .cf, .click, .email, .fit, .ga, .gdn, .gq, .loan, .london, .men, .ml, .pl, .rest, .ru, .tk, .top, .work TLDs due to spam">https://forwardemail.net) — Free email forwarding for custom domains. Create and forward an unlimited amount of email addresses with your domain name (**note**: You must pay if you use .casa, .cf, .click, .email, .fit, .ga, .gdn, .gq, .loan, .london, .men, .ml, .pl, .rest, .ru, .tk, .top, .work TLDs due to spam</a> - Free email forwarding for custom domains. Create and forward an unlimited amount of email addresses with your domain name (**note**: You must pay if you use .casa, .cf, .click, .email, .fit, .ga, .gdn, .gq, .loan, .london, .men, .ml, .pl, .rest, .ru, .tk, .top, .work TLDs due to spam)<br>
<a href="https://roboflow.com">https://roboflow.com</a> - create and deploy a custom computer vision model with no prior machine learning experience required. Free tier includes up to 1,000 free source images.<br>
<a href="https://glitchtip.com/">https://glitchtip.com/</a> - Simple, open source error tracking. Compatible with open-source Sentry SDKs. 1000 events per month for free, or can self-host with no limits<br>
<a href="https://www.loadmill.com/">https://www.loadmill.com/</a> - Automatically create API and load tests by analyzing network traffic. Simulate up to 50 concurrent users for up to 60 minutes for free every month.<br>
<a href="https://glitchtip.com/">https://glitchtip.com/</a> - Simple, open source error tracking. Compatible with open-source Sentry SDKs. 1000 events per month for free, or can self-host with no limits<br>
<a href="https://logdna.com">https://logdna.com</a> - Free for a single user, no retention, unlimited hosts and sources<br>
<a href="https://kitemaker.co">https://kitemaker.co</a> - Collaborate through all phases of the product development process and keep track of work across Slack, Discord, Figma, and Github. Unlimited users, unlimited spaces. Free plan up to 250 work items.<br>
<a href="https://www.pubnub.com/">https://www.pubnub.com/</a> - Swift, Kotlin and React messaging at 1 million transactions each month. Transactions may contain multiple messages.<br>
<a href="https://kitemaker.co">https://kitemaker.co</a> - Collaborate through all phases of the product development process and keep track of work across Slack, Discord, Figma, and Github. Unlimited users, unlimited spaces. Free plan up to 250 work items.<br>
<a href="https://darklang.com/">https://darklang.com/</a> - Hosted editor/language/infrastructure<br>
<a href="https://darklang.com/">https://darklang.com/</a> - Hosted editor/language/infrastructure<br>
<a href="https://darklang.com/">https://darklang.com/</a> - Hosted editor/language/infrastructure<br>
<a href="https://www.courier.com/">https://www.courier.com/</a> - Single API for push, in-app, email, chat, SMS, and other messaging channels with template management and other features. Free plan includes 10,000 messages/mo.<br>
<a href="https://www.goatcounter.com/) — GoatCounter is an open source web analytics platform available as a hosted service (free for non-commercial use">https://www.goatcounter.com/) — GoatCounter is an open source web analytics platform available as a hosted service (free for non-commercial use</a> - GoatCounter is an open source web analytics platform available as a hosted service (free for non-commercial use) or self-hosted app. It aims to offer easy to use and meaningful privacy-friendly web analytics as an alternative to Google Analytics or Matomo. Free tier is for non-commerical use and includes unlimited number of sites, 6 months of data retention, and 100k pageviews/month.<br>
<a href="https://redirection.io/">https://redirection.io/</a> - SaaS tool for managing HTTP redirections for businesses, marketing and SEO.<br>
<a href="#other-free-resources">#other-free-resources</a> - Resources](#other-free-resources)<br>
<a href="https://mixpanel.com/">https://mixpanel.com/</a> - 100,000 monthly tracked users, unlimited data history and seats, US or EU data residency<br>
<a href="https://darklang.com/">https://darklang.com/</a> - Hosted language combined with editor and infrastructure. Free during the beta, generous free tier planned after beta.<br>
<a href="https://analytics.ao.gl/">https://analytics.ao.gl/</a> - — Forever FREE Customer Analytics for ALL your websites, with Unlimited Events per month<br>
<a href="https://workspaces.openshift.com/">https://workspaces.openshift.com/</a> - - Web based and Kubernetes-Native IDE for Developer Teams with multi-language support. Open Source and community driven. A online instance hosted by Red Hat is available at [workspaces.openshift.com](https://workspaces.openshift.com/).<br>
<a href="https://newsapi.org">https://newsapi.org</a> - — Search news on the web with code, get JSON results. Developers get 3,000 queries free each month.<br>
<a href="https://smartcar.com">https://smartcar.com</a> - - An API for cars to locate, get fuel tank, battery levels, odometer, unlock/lock doors, etc.<br>
<a href="https://PhantomJsCloud.com">https://PhantomJsCloud.com</a> - Browser automation and page rendering. Free Tier offers up to 500 pages/day. Free Tier since 2017.<br>
<a href="https://pagure.io">https://pagure.io</a> - Pagure.io is a free and open source software code collaboration platform for FOSS-licensed projects, Git-based<br>
<a href="https://issueembed.dev/">https://issueembed.dev/</a> - - A bug reporting tool for websites to go directly into your Github Issues. Free plan for personal repositories with up to 500 issues/month and 10,000 page views/month.<br>
<a href="https://simplelocalize.io/">https://simplelocalize.io/</a> - Free up to 100 translation keys, unlimited strings, unlimited languages, startup deals<br>
<a href="https://efemarai.com">https://efemarai.com</a> - Testing and debugging platform for ML models and data. Visualize any computational graph. Free 30 debugging sessions per month for developers.<br>
<a href="https://cmd.com/">https://cmd.com/</a> - Security platform providing real-time access control and dynamic policy enforcement on every Linux instance in your cloud or datacenter<br>
<a href="https://www.logrocket.com">https://www.logrocket.com</a> - 1,000 sessions/month with 30 day retention, error tracking, live mode<br>
<a href="https://www.wormhol.org/">https://www.wormhol.org/</a> - Straightforward file sharing service. Share unlimited files up to 5GB to as many peers as you want.<br>
<a href="https://cloudinary.com/">https://cloudinary.com/</a> - Image upload, powerful manipulations, storage and delivery for sites and apps, with libraries for Ruby, Python, Java, PHP, Objective-C and more. Free tier includes 25 monthly credits. 1 credit is equal to 1,000 image transformations, 1 GB of storage, or 1 GB of CDN usage.<br>
<a href="https://www.newrelic.com">https://www.newrelic.com</a> - New Relic observability platform built to help engineers create more perfect software. From monoliths to serverless, you can instrument everything, then analyze, troubleshoot, and optimize your entire software stack. Free tier offers 100GB/month of free data ingest, 1 free full access user, and unlimited free basic users.<br>
<a href="https://developers.arcgis.com">https://developers.arcgis.com</a> - APIs and SDKs for maps, geospatial data storage, analysis, geocoding, routing, and more across web, desktop, and mobile. 2,000,000 free basemap tiles, 20,000 non-stored geocodes, 20,000 simple routes, 5,000 drive time calculations, 5GB free tile+data storage per month.<br>
<a href="https://ipapi.co/) - IP Address Location API by Kloudend, Inc - A reliable geolocation API, built on AWS, trusted by Fortune 500. Free tier offers 30k lookups/month (1k/day">https://ipapi.co/) - IP Address Location API by Kloudend, Inc - A reliable geolocation API, built on AWS, trusted by Fortune 500. Free tier offers 30k lookups/month (1k/day</a> - IP Address Location API by Kloudend, Inc - A reliable geolocation API, built on AWS, trusted by Fortune 500. Free tier offers 30k lookups/month (1k/day) without signup. Contact us for a higher limit trial plan.<br>
<a href="https://doppler.com/">https://doppler.com/</a> - Universal Secrets Manager for application secrets and config, with support for syncing to various cloud providers. Free for unlimited users with basic access controls.<br>
<a href="https://octopus.com">https://octopus.com</a> - - Automated deployment and release-management. Free for <= 10 deployment targets.<br>
<a href="https://www.thundra.io/apm">https://www.thundra.io/apm</a> - Application monitoring and debugging. Has a free tier up to 250k monthly invocations.<br>
<a href="https://ploi.io/">https://ploi.io/</a> - Server management tool to easily manage and deploy your servers & sites. Free for 1 server.<br>
<a href="https://updrafts.app">https://updrafts.app</a> - WYSIWYG web site builder for tailwindcss based designs. Free for non-commercial usage.<br>
<a href="https://3v4l.org/">https://3v4l.org/</a> - Free online PHP shell and snippet sharing site, runs your code in 300+ PHP versions<br>
<a href="https://avo.app/">https://avo.app/</a> - Simplified analytics release workflow. Single-source-of-truth tracking plan, type safe analytics tracking library, in-app debuggers, data observability to catch all data issues before you release. Free for 2 workspace members and 1 hour data observability lookback.<br>
<a href="https://holistic.dev/">https://holistic.dev/</a> - The #1 static code analyzer for Postgresql optimization. Performance, security, and architect database issues automatic detection service<br>
<a href="https://parsers.dev/">https://parsers.dev/</a> - Abstract syntax tree parsers and intermediate representation compilers as a service<br>
<a href="https://seatable.io/">https://seatable.io/</a> - Flexible, Spreadsheet-like Database built by Seafile team. unlimited tables, 2,000 lines, 1-month versioning, up to 25 team members.<br>
<a href="https://linear.app/) — Issue tracker with streamlined interface. Free for unlimited members, up to 10MB file upload size, 250 issues (excluding Archive">https://linear.app/) — Issue tracker with streamlined interface. Free for unlimited members, up to 10MB file upload size, 250 issues (excluding Archive</a> - Issue tracker with streamlined interface. Free for unlimited members, up to 10MB file upload size, 250 issues (excluding Archive)<br>
<a href="https://tara.ai/">https://tara.ai/</a> - — Simple sprint management service. Free plan has unlimited tasks, sprints and workspaces, with no user limits.<br>
<a href="https://fibery.io/">https://fibery.io/</a> - Connected workspace platform. Free for single user, up to 2 GB disk space.<br>
<a href="https://www.yodiz.com/">https://www.yodiz.com/</a> - Agile development and issue tracking. Free up to 3 users, unlimited projects.<br>
<a href="https://teamwork.com/">https://teamwork.com/</a> - Project management & Team Chat. Free for 5 users and 2 projects. Premium plans available.<br>
<a href="https://foss.heptapod.net/">https://foss.heptapod.net/</a> - Heptapod is a friendly fork of GitLab Community Edition providing support for Mercurial<br>
<a href="https://zulip.com/">https://zulip.com/</a> - Real-time chat with unique email-like threading model. Free plan includes 10,000 messages of search history and File storage up to 5 GB. also it provides self-hostable open-source version.<br>
<a href="https://www.braidchat.com/">https://www.braidchat.com/</a> - Chat app designed for teams. Free for public access group, unlimited users, history, and integrations. also it provide self-hostable open-source version.<br>
<a href="https://www.meistertask.com/">https://www.meistertask.com/</a> - Online task management for teams. Free up to 3 projects, unlimited project members.<br>
<a href="https://www.honeybadger.io) - Exception, uptime, and cron monitoring. Free for small teams and open-source projects (12,000 errors/month">https://www.honeybadger.io) - Exception, uptime, and cron monitoring. Free for small teams and open-source projects (12,000 errors/month</a> - Exception, uptime, and cron monitoring. Free for small teams and open-source projects (12,000 errors/month).<br>
<a href="https://www.hookrelay.dev/">https://www.hookrelay.dev/</a> - - Add webhook support to your app without the hassles: done-for-you queueing, retries with backoff, and logging.<br>
<a href="https://www.hookrelay.dev/">https://www.hookrelay.dev/</a> - - Add webhook support to your app without the hassles: done-for-you queueing, retries with backoff, and logging. The free plan has 100 deliveries per day, 14-day retention, and 3 hook endpoints.<br>
<a href="https://kreya.app">https://kreya.app</a> - Free gRPC GUI client to call and test gRPC APIs. Can import gRPC APIs via server reflection.<br>
<a href="https://www.revenuecat.com/) — Hosted backend for in-app purchases and subscriptions (iOS and Android">https://www.revenuecat.com/) — Hosted backend for in-app purchases and subscriptions (iOS and Android</a> - Hosted backend for in-app purchases and subscriptions (iOS and Android). Free up to $10k/mo in tracked revenue.<br>
<a href="https://upstash.com/">https://upstash.com/</a> - Serverless Redis with free tier up to 10,000 requests per day, 256MB max database size, and 20 concurrent connections<br>
<a href="https://www.borgbase.com/">https://www.borgbase.com/</a> - Simple and secure offsite backup hosting for Borg Backup. 10 GB free backup space and 2 repositories.<br>
<a href="https://efemarai.com">https://efemarai.com</a> - Testing and debugging platform for ML models and data. Visualize any computational graph. Free 30 debugging sessions per month for developers.<br>
<a href="https://newsapi.org">https://newsapi.org</a> - — Search news on the web with code, get JSON results. Developers get 3,000 queries free each month.<br>
<a href="https://applitools.com/) — Smart visual validation for web, native mobile and desktop apps. Integrates with almost all automation solutions (like Selenium and Karma) and remote runners (Sauce Labs, Browser Stack">https://applitools.com/) — Smart visual validation for web, native mobile and desktop apps. Integrates with almost all automation solutions (like Selenium and Karma) and remote runners (Sauce Labs, Browser Stack</a> - Smart visual validation for web, native mobile and desktop apps. Integrates with almost all automation solutions (like Selenium and Karma) and remote runners (Sauce Labs, Browser Stack). free for open source. A free tier for a single user with limited checkpoints per week.<br>
<a href="https://webhook.site">https://webhook.site</a> - Verify webhooks, outbound HTTP requests, or emails with a custom URL. Temporary URL and email address is always free.<br>
<a href="https://www.tiny.cloud">https://www.tiny.cloud</a> - rich text editing API. Core features free for unlimited usage.<br>
<a href="https://hostman.com">https://hostman.com</a> - Deploy up to 3 static sites from your GitHub repository for free.<br>
<a href="https://translation.io">https://translation.io</a> - Free for Open Source<br>
<a href="https://www.plasmic.app/">https://www.plasmic.app/</a> - A fast, easy to use, powerful web design tool and page builder that integrates into your codebase. Build responsive pages or complex components; optionally extend with code; and publish to production sites and apps.<br>
<a href="https://www.netlify.com/">https://www.netlify.com/</a> - Builds, deploy and hosts static site/app free for, 100 GB data and 100 GB/month bandwidth.<br>
<a href="https://checklyhq.com">https://checklyhq.com</a> - Open source E2E / Synthetic monitoring and deep API monitoring for developers. Free plan with 5 users and 50k+ check runs.<br>
<a href="https://updrafts.app">https://updrafts.app</a> - WYSIWYG web site builder for tailwindcss based designs. Free for non-commercial usage.<br>
<a href="https://www.contentful.com/">https://www.contentful.com/</a> - Headless CMS. Content management and delivery APIs in the cloud. Comes with one free Community space that includes 5 users, 25K records, 48 Content Types, 2 locales.<br>
<a href="https://www.qovery.com">https://www.qovery.com</a> - Qovery is the simplest way to deploy your full-stack apps on AWS, GCP and Azure. It is free web hosting for developers with Database, SSL, a global CDN, and auto deploys from Git.<br>
<a href="https://connectycube.com">https://connectycube.com</a> - Unlimited chat messages, p2p voice & video calls, files attachments and push notifications. Free for apps up to 20K MAU.<br>
<a href="https://connectycube.com">https://connectycube.com</a> - APIs for realtime messaging, voice & video calling, push notifications, files storage and users management. Free for apps up to 20K MAU.<br>
<a href="https://www.xirsys.com">https://www.xirsys.com</a> - Global network of STUN / TURN servers with a generous free tier.<br>
<a href="https://www.cloudmailin.com/">https://www.cloudmailin.com/</a> - Incoming email via HTTP POST and transactional outbound - 10,000 free emails/month<br>
<a href="https://authy.com) - Two-factor authentication (2FA">https://authy.com) - Two-factor authentication (2FA</a> - Two-factor authentication (2FA) on multiple devices, with backups. Drop-in replacement for Google Authenticator.<br>
<a href="https://authy.com) - Two-factor authentication (2FA">https://authy.com) - Two-factor authentication (2FA</a> - Two-factor authentication (2FA) on multiple devices, with backups. Drop-in replacement for Google Authenticator. Free for up to 100 successful authentications.<br>
<a href="https://www.20i.com/">https://www.20i.com/</a> - Free global CDN with no restrictions and 1 Tbps+ DDoS protection available on all web hosting, including free hosting.<br>
<a href="https://www.20i.com/">https://www.20i.com/</a> - Free web hosting with no ads, on the same platform as paid plans. Includes a free CDN, 100 email addresses, SSL and over 80 one-click installs.<br>
<a href="https://updrafts.app">https://updrafts.app</a> - WYSIWYG web site builder for tailwindcss based designs. Free for non-commercial usage.<br>
<a href="https://products.office.com/microsoft-teams/free">https://products.office.com/microsoft-teams/free</a> - — Microsoft Teams is a chat-based digital hub that brings conversations, content, and apps together in one place all from a single experience. Free for up to 50k users.<br>
<a href="https://drv.tw">https://drv.tw</a> - Web](https://drv.tw) — Host directly to the web from Google Drive & OneDrive. Static sites only. Free forever. One site per Google/Microsoft account.<br>
<a href="https://discordapp.com/">https://discordapp.com/</a> - Chat with public/private rooms. Markdown text, voice, video, and screen sharing capabilities. Free for unlimited users.<br>
<a href="https://products.office.com/microsoft-teams/free">https://products.office.com/microsoft-teams/free</a> - — Microsoft Teams is a chat-based digital hub that brings conversations, content, and apps together in one place all from a single experience. Free for up to 500k users.<br>
<a href="https://esper.io">https://esper.io</a> - MDM and MAM for Android Devices with DevOps. 100 devices free with 1 user license and 25 MB Application Storage.<br>
<a href="https://openode.io">https://openode.io</a> - Free Node.js hosting for Open Source projects. 100 GB Bandwidth/month with 100 MB memory & 1000 MB storage. Deploy using CLI or existing Git repository.<br>
<a href="https://github.com/tvvocold/FOSS-for-Dev">https://github.com/tvvocold/FOSS-for-Dev</a> - FOSS for Dev](https://github.com/tvvocold/FOSS-for-Dev) — A hub of free and Open Source software for developers.<br>
<a href="https://developers.redhat.com">https://developers.redhat.com</a> - Developers](https://developers.redhat.com) — Free access to Red Hat products including RHEL,OpenShift,CodeReady etc exclusively for developers. Individual plan only. Free e-Books also offered for reference.<br>
<a href="https://encore.dev/">https://encore.dev/</a> - Backend framework using static analysis to provide automatic infrastructure, boilerplate free code, and more. Includes free cloud hosting for hobby projects.<br>
<a href="https://gitgud.io">https://gitgud.io</a> - Unlimited private and public repositories. Free forever. Powered by GitLab & Sapphire. CI/CD not provided.<br>
<a href="https://getjsonip.com">https://getjsonip.com</a> - — Returns the Public IP address of the client it is requested from. No registration required for free tier. Using CORS data can be requested using client side JS directly from browser. Useful for services monitoring change in client and server IPs.<br>
<a href="https://getjsonip.com">https://getjsonip.com</a> - — Returns the Public IP address of the client it is requested from. No registration required for free tier. Using CORS data can be requested using client side JS directly from browser. Useful for services monitoring change in client and server IPs. Unlimited Requests.<br>
<a href="https://appetize.io">https://appetize.io</a> - Test your Android & iOS apps on this Cloud Based service. Free tier includes 1 concurrent session with 100 minutes usage per month. No app size limit.<br>
<a href="https://appetize.io">https://appetize.io</a> - Test your Android & iOS apps on this Cloud Based Android Phone/Tablets emulators and iPhone/iPad simulators directly in your browser. Free tier includes 1 concurrent session with 100 minutes usage per month. No limit on app size.<br>
<a href="https://d.android.com/studio">https://d.android.com/studio</a> - — Android Studio provides the fastest tools for building apps on every type of Android device. Open Source IDE and the best to develop Android apps. Available for Windows,Mac,Linux and even ChromeOS!<br>
<a href="https://d.android.com/studio">https://d.android.com/studio</a> - — Android Studio provides the fastest tools for building apps on every type of Android device. Open Source IDE, free for everyone and the best to develop Android apps. Available for Windows,Mac,Linux and even ChromeOS!<br>
<a href="https://0hi.me/">https://0hi.me/</a> - Free PHP & MySQL Web Hosting for your small project. SSL/TLS and CDN also available for free.<br>
<a href="https://www.microsoft.com/microsoft-365/enterprise/e5) (Windows excluded) which is renewable. It is renewed if you're active in development(measured using telemetry data & algorithms">https://www.microsoft.com/microsoft-365/enterprise/e5) (Windows excluded) which is renewable. It is renewed if you're active in development(measured using telemetry data & algorithms</a> - Developer Program](https://developer.microsoft.com/microsoft-365/dev-program) — Get a free sandbox, tools, and other resources you need to build solutions for the Microsoft 365 platform. The subscription is a 90-day [Microsoft 365 E5 Subscription](https://www.microsoft.com/microsoft-365/enterprise/e5) (Windows excluded) which is renewable. It is renewed if you're active in development(measured using telemetry data & algorithms).<br>
<a href="https://code.sololearn.com">https://code.sololearn.com</a> - A cloud programming playground well-suited for running code snippets. Supports various programming languages. No registration required for running code but required when you need to save code on their platform. Also offers free courses for begginers and intermediate level coders.<br>
<a href="https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev">https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev</a> - the result of Pull Requests, reviews, ideas and work done by 900+ people. You too can help by sending [Pull Requests](https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev) to add more services or by remove ones whose offerings have changed or been retired.<br>
<a href="https://protectumus.com) - Free website security check, site antivirus and server firewall (WAF">https://protectumus.com) - Free website security check, site antivirus and server firewall (WAF</a> - Free website security check, site antivirus and server firewall (WAF) for PHP. Email notifications for registered users in free tier.<br>
<a href="https://www.mendix.com/">https://www.mendix.com/</a> - Rapid Application Development for Enterprises, unlimited number of free sandbox environments supporting unlimited users, 0.5 GB storage and 1 GB RAM per app. Also Studio and Studio Pro IDEs are allowed in free tier.<br>
<a href="https://qualtrics.com/free-account">https://qualtrics.com/free-account</a> - — Create professional forms & survey using this first class tool. 50+ expert-designed survey templates. Free Account has limit of 1 active survey, 100 responses/survey & 8 response types.<br>
<a href="https://curlhub.io">https://curlhub.io</a> - Proxy service for inspecting and debugging API calls. Free plan includes 10,000 requests per month.<br>
<a href="https://hookbin.com/) - Create unique (public or private">https://hookbin.com/) - Create unique (public or private</a> - Create unique (public or private) endpoints to collect, parse, and inspect HTTP requests. Inspect headers, body, query strings, cookies, uploaded files, etc. Useful for testing/inspecting webhook. Similar to RequestBin, and Webhook.site.<br>
<a href="https://freedns.afraid.org/domain/registry/">https://freedns.afraid.org/domain/registry/</a> - Free DNS hosting. Also provide free subdomain based on numerous public user [contributed domains](https://freedns.afraid.org/domain/registry/). Get free subdomains from "Subdomains" menu after signing up.<br>
<a href="https://www.tableau.com/developer">https://www.tableau.com/developer</a> - Program](https://www.tableau.com/developer) — Innovate, create, and make Tableau work perfectly for your organization. Free developer program gives a personal development sandbox license for Tableau Online. The version is the latest pre-release version so Data Devs can test each & every feature of this superb platform.<br>
<a href="https://continuousphp.com/">https://continuousphp.com/</a> - — continuousphp is the first and only PHP-centric Platform to build, package, test and deploy applications in the same workflow. Free for Community Projects i.e. OSS, Public & Educational projects.<br>
<a href="#file-converters">#file-converters</a> - <br>
<a href="https://conversiontools.io/) - Online File Converter for documents, images, video, audio, eBooks. REST API is available. Libraries for Node.js, PHP, Python. Support files up to 50 GB (for paid plans">https://conversiontools.io/) - Online File Converter for documents, images, video, audio, eBooks. REST API is available. Libraries for Node.js, PHP, Python. Support files up to 50 GB (for paid plans</a> - - Online File Converter for documents, images, video, audio, eBooks. REST API is available. Libraries for Node.js, PHP, Python. Support files up to 50 GB (for paid plans). Free tier is limited by file size and number of conversions per day.<br>
<a href="https://conversiontools.io/) - Online File Converter for documents, images, video, audio, eBooks. REST API is available. Libraries for Node.js, PHP, Python. Support files up to 50 GB (for paid plans">https://conversiontools.io/) - Online File Converter for documents, images, video, audio, eBooks. REST API is available. Libraries for Node.js, PHP, Python. Support files up to 50 GB (for paid plans</a> - - Online File Converter for documents, images, video, audio, eBooks. REST API is available. Libraries for Node.js, PHP, Python. Support files up to 50 GB (for paid plans). Free tier is limited by file size and number of conversions per day.<br>
<a href="https://conversiontools.io/) - Online File Converter for documents, images, video, audio, eBooks. REST API is available. Libraries for Node.js, PHP, Python. Support files up to 50 GB (for paid plans">https://conversiontools.io/) - Online File Converter for documents, images, video, audio, eBooks. REST API is available. Libraries for Node.js, PHP, Python. Support files up to 50 GB (for paid plans</a> - - Online File Converter for documents, images, video, audio, eBooks. REST API is available. Libraries for Node.js, PHP, Python. Support files up to 50 GB (for paid plans). Free tier is limited by file size and number of conversions per day.<br>
<a href="https://continuousphp.com/">https://continuousphp.com/</a> - — continuousphp is the first and only PHP-centric Platform to build, package, test and deploy applications in the same workflow. Free for Community Projects i.e. OSS/Public/Educational projects.<br>
<a href="https://imagekit.io">https://imagekit.io</a> - Image CDN with automatic optimization, real-time transformation, and storage that you can integrate with existing setup in minutes. Free plan includes up to 20GB bandwidth per month.<br>
<a href="https://github.com/) — Unlimited public repositories and unlimited private repositories (with unlimited collaborators). Apart from this some other free services(there are much more but we list the main ones here">https://github.com/) — Unlimited public repositories and unlimited private repositories (with unlimited collaborators). Apart from this some other free services(there are much more but we list the main ones here</a> - Unlimited public repositories and unlimited private repositories (with unlimited collaborators). Apart from this some other free services(there are much more but we list the main ones here) provided are :<br>
<a href="https://github.com/features/actions)(Free for Public Repos, 2000 min/month for private repos free">https://github.com/features/actions)(Free for Public Repos, 2000 min/month for private repos free</a> - Public Repos, 2000 min/month for private repos free)<br>
<a href="https://pages.github.com) (Free for Public Repos">https://pages.github.com) (Free for Public Repos</a> - Hosting](https://pages.github.com) (Free for Public Repos)<br>
<a href="https://github.com/features/packages) (Free for public repos,500 MB storage & 1GB bandwidth outside CI/CD free for private repos">https://github.com/features/packages) (Free for public repos,500 MB storage & 1GB bandwidth outside CI/CD free for private repos</a> - & Container Registry](https://github.com/features/packages) (Free for public repos,500 MB storage & 1GB bandwidth outside CI/CD free for private repos)<br>
<a href="https://about.gitlab.com/">https://about.gitlab.com/</a> - Unlimited public and private Git repos with unlimited collaborators. Also offers the following features :<br>
<a href="https://appflux.io">https://appflux.io</a> - Project Management tool with Log Management & Issues. Take your team onboard & forget management through emails.<br>
<a href="https://about.gitlab.com/product/continuous-integration) (Free for Public Repos, 400 mins/month for private repos">https://about.gitlab.com/product/continuous-integration) (Free for Public Repos, 400 mins/month for private repos</a> - for Public Repos, 400 mins/month for private repos)<br>
<a href="https://about.gitlab.com/product/pages">https://about.gitlab.com/product/pages</a> - with [GitLab Pages](https://about.gitlab.com/product/pages).<br>
<a href="https://penpot.app">https://penpot.app</a> - Web based, open source design and prototyping tool. Supports SVG. Completely free.<br>
<a href="https://apitemplate.io">https://apitemplate.io</a> - Auto-generate social images and PDF documents with a simple API or automation tools like Zapier & Airtable. No CSS/HTML required.<br>
<a href="https://webshrinker.com">https://webshrinker.com</a> - Web Shrinker provides web site screenshot and domain intelligence API services. Free 100 requests/month.<br>
<a href="https://catchjs.com/">https://catchjs.com/</a> - JavaScript error tracking with screenshots and click trails. Free for open source projects.<br>
<a href="https://apitemplate.io">https://apitemplate.io</a> - Auto-generate images and PDF documents with a simple API or automation tools like Zapier & Airtable. No CSS/HTML required. Free plan comes with 50 images/month and 3 templates.<br>
<a href="https://sider.review">https://sider.review</a> - Code review platform for many languages. Supports integration with GitHub. Free for public repositories with unlimited users.<br>
<a href="https://formspark.io/">https://formspark.io/</a> - Form to Email service, free plan allows unlimited forms, 250 submissions per month, support by Customer assistance team.<br>
<a href="https://getform.io/">https://getform.io/</a> - Form backend platform for designers and developers, 1 form, 50 submissions, Single file upload, 100MB file storage.<br>
<a href="https://pageclip.co/">https://pageclip.co/</a> - Free plan allows one site, one form, 1,000 submissions per month.<br>
<a href="https://smartforms.dev/">https://smartforms.dev/</a> - Powerful and easy form backend for your website, forever free plan allows 50 submissions per month, 250MB file storage, Zapier integration, CSV/JSON export, custom redirect, custom response page, Telegram & Slack bot, single email notifications.<br>
<a href="https://www.zoho.com/forms/">https://www.zoho.com/forms/</a> - - with 40+ field types, customizable themes, situation-specific templates, and a simple user interface, helps you create beautiful, functional forms for all your needs. Free plan allows 3 forms, 500 submissions/month, 200 MB File storage.<br>
<a href="https://layerci.com">https://layerci.com</a> - CI for full stack projects. 1 full stack preview environment with 5GB memory & 3 CPUs .<br>
<a href="https://developer.suse.com">https://developer.suse.com</a> - Program](https://developer.suse.com) — Experience cloud native productivity for free. Get hands-on with the SUSE Cloud Application Platform with your own Developer Sandbox. 1 Free Application. Free subdomain provided along with API for CLI. Storage & Memory Quota of 1 GB.<br>
<a href="https://developer.salesforce.com/signup">https://developer.salesforce.com/signup</a> - Program](https://developer.salesforce.com/signup) — Build apps Lightning fast with drag and drop tools. Customize your data model with clicks. Go further with Apex code. Integrate with anything using powerful APIs. Stay protected with enterprise-grade security. Customize UI with clicks or any leading-edge web framework. Free Developer Program gives access to the full Lightining Platform.<br>
<a href="https://developers.bmc.com/site/global/bmc_helix_platform/program/overview/index.gsp">https://developers.bmc.com/site/global/bmc_helix_platform/program/overview/index.gsp</a> - Program](https://developers.bmc.com/site/global/bmc_helix_platform/program/overview/index.gsp) — The BMC Developer Program provides documentation and resources to build and deploy digital innovations for your enterprise. Access to a comprehensive, personal sandbox which includes the platform, SDK, and a library of components that can be used to build and tailor apps.<br>
<a href="https://developer.servicenow.com/">https://developer.servicenow.com/</a> - Program](https://developer.servicenow.com/) — Rapidly build, test, and deploy applications that make work better for your organization. Free Instance & access early previews.<br>
<a href="https://pinata.cloud">https://pinata.cloud</a> - — Pinata is the simplest way to upload and manage files on IPFS. Our friendly user interface combined with our IPFS API makes Pinata the easiest IPFS pinning service for platforms, creators, and collectors. 1 GB storage free along with access to API.<br>
<a href="https://kritika.io/">https://kritika.io/</a> - Static Code Analysis for Perl with integration for GitHub. Free for unlimited public repositories.<br>
<a href="https://vaadin.com">https://vaadin.com</a> - Build scalable UIs in Java or TypeScript, and use the integrated tooling, components and design system to iterate faster, design better and simplify the development process. Unlimited Projects with 5 years free maintenance.<br>
<a href="https://codebeat.co">https://codebeat.co</a> - Automated Code Review Platform available for many languages. Free forever for public repositories with Slack & E-mail integration.<br>
<a href="https://icons8.com">https://icons8.com</a> - Icons, illustrations, photos, music, and design tools. Free Plan offers Limited formats in lower resolution. Link to Icons8 when you use our assets.<br>
<a href="https://rive.app">https://rive.app</a> - Create and ship beautiful animations to any platform. Free forever for Individuals. The service is a editor which hosts all the graphics on their servers as well. They also provide runtimes for many platforms to run graphics made using Rive.<br>
<a href="https://smartmockups.com/">https://smartmockups.com/</a> - Create product mockups, 200 free mockups.<br>
<a href="https://percy.io">https://percy.io</a> - Add visual testing to any web app, static site, style guide, or component library. Unlimited team members, Demo app and unlimited projects, 5,000 snapshots / month.<br>
<a href="https://www.zoho.com">https://www.zoho.com</a> - Started as an e-mail provider but now provides a suite of services out of which some of them have free plans. List of services having free plans :<br>
<a href="https://zoho.com/mail">https://zoho.com/mail</a> - for 5 users. 5GB/user & 25 MB attachment limit, 1 domain.<br>
<a href="https://zoho.com/sprints">https://zoho.com/sprints</a> - for 5 users,5 Projects & 500MB storage.<br>
<a href="https://zoho.com/docs) — Free for 5 users with 1 GB upload limit & 5GB storage. Zoho Office Suite (Writer,Sheets & Show">https://zoho.com/docs) — Free for 5 users with 1 GB upload limit & 5GB storage. Zoho Office Suite (Writer,Sheets & Show</a> - Free for 5 users with 1 GB upload limit & 5GB storage. Zoho Office Suite (Writer,Sheets & Show) comes bundled with it.<br>
<a href="https://zoho.com/bugtracker">https://zoho.com/bugtracker</a> - Free for 3 users, 2 projects & 10 MB attachment limit. Same plan applies to [Bugtracker](https://zoho.com/bugtracker).<br>
<a href="https://zoho.com/connect">https://zoho.com/connect</a> - Team Collaboration free for 25 users with 3 groups, 3 custom apps, 3 Boards, 3 Manuals, 10 Integrations along with channels,events & forums.<br>
<a href="https://zoho.com/meeting">https://zoho.com/meeting</a> - Meetings with upto 3 meeting participants & 10 Webinar attendees.<br>
<a href="https://zoho.com/vault">https://zoho.com/vault</a> - Password Management free for Individuals.<br>
<a href="https://zoho.com/showtime">https://zoho.com/showtime</a> - Yet another Meeting software for training for a remote session upto 5 attendees.<br>
<a href="https://zoho.com/notebook">https://zoho.com/notebook</a> - A free alternative to Evernote.<br>
<a href="https://zoho.com/wiki">https://zoho.com/wiki</a> - Free for 3 users with 50 MB storage, unlimited pages, zip backups, RSS & Atom feed, access controls & customisable CSS.<br>
<a href="https://zoho.com/subscriptions">https://zoho.com/subscriptions</a> - Recurring Billing management free for 20 customers/subscriptions & 1 user with all the payment hosting done by Zoho themselves. Last 40 subscription metrics are stored<br>
<a href="https://zoho.com/checkout">https://zoho.com/checkout</a> - Product Billing management with 3 pages & up to 50 payments.<br>
<a href="https://zoho.com/assist">https://zoho.com/assist</a> - Customer Support management with 3 agents and private knowledge base, email tickets. Integrates with [Assist](https://zoho.com/assist) for 1 remote technician & 5 unattended computers.<br>
<a href="https://zoho.com/cliq">https://zoho.com/cliq</a> - Team chat software with 100 GB storage, unlimited users, 100 users per channel & SSO.<br>
<a href="https://zoho.com/campaigns">https://zoho.com/campaigns</a> - <br>
<a href="https://zoho.com/forms">https://zoho.com/forms</a> - <br>
<a href="https:/zoho.com/sign">https:/zoho.com/sign</a> - <br>
<a href="https://zoho.com/surveys">https://zoho.com/surveys</a> - <br>
<a href="https://zoho.com/bookings">https://zoho.com/bookings</a> - <br>
<a href="https://zoho.com/analytics">https://zoho.com/analytics</a> - <br>
<a href="https://zube.io">https://zube.io</a> - Project management with free plan for 4 Projects & 4 users. GitHub integration available.<br>
<a href="https://codeblocks.org">https://codeblocks.org</a> - Free Fortran & C/C++ IDE. Open Source and runs on Windows,macOS & Linux.<br>
<a href="https://elementor.com">https://elementor.com</a> - WordPress website builder. Free plan available with 40+ Basic Widgets.<br>
<a href="https://www.birdeatsbug.com/) — Report bugs faster (and better">https://www.birdeatsbug.com/) — Report bugs faster (and better</a> - Bug](https://www.birdeatsbug.com/) — Report bugs faster (and better). Record your screen with Bird browser extension, it will auto-capture technical data that engineers need to debug. Free tier suitable for small teams.<br>
<a href="https://stackby.com/">https://stackby.com/</a> - One tool that brings together flexibility of spreadsheets, power of databases and built-in integrations with your favorite business apps. Free plan includes unlimited users, 10 stacks, 2GB attachment per stack.<br>
<a href="https://clicky.com">https://clicky.com</a> - Website Analytics Platform. Free Plan for 1 website with 3000 views analytics.<br>
<a href="https://blynk.io">https://blynk.io</a> - A SaaS with API to control, build & evaluate IoT devices. Free Developer Plan with 5 devices,Free Cloud & data storage. Mobile Apps also available.<br>
<a href="https://clicky.com">https://clicky.com</a> - Website Analytics Platform. Free Plan for 1 website with 3000 views analytics.<br>
<a href="https://blynk.io">https://blynk.io</a> - A SaaS with API to control, build & evaluate IoT devices. Free Developer Plan with 5 devices,Free Cloud & data storage. Mobile Apps also available.<br>
<a href="https://mergify.io">https://mergify.io</a> - workflow automation and merge queue for GitHub — Free for public GitHub repositories<br>
<a href="https://www.namiml.com/">https://www.namiml.com/</a> - Complete platform for in-app purchases and subscriptions on iOS and Android, including no-code paywalls, CRM, and analytics. Free for all base features to run an IAP business.<br>
<a href="https://analytics.google.com/">https://analytics.google.com/</a> - — Google Analytics<br>
<a href="https://hotjar.com) — Website Analytics and Reports . Free Plan allows 2000 pageviews/day. 100 snapshots/day (max capacity: 300">https://hotjar.com) — Website Analytics and Reports . Free Plan allows 2000 pageviews/day. 100 snapshots/day (max capacity: 300</a> - Website Analytics and Reports . Free Plan allows 2000 pageviews/day. 100 snapshots/day (max capacity: 300). 3 snapshot heatmaps which can be stored for 365 days. Unlimited Team Members.<br>
<a href="https://statcounter.com/">https://statcounter.com/</a> - Website Viewer Analytics. Free plan for analytics of 500 most recent visitors.<br>
<a href="https://www.abstractapi.com/ip-geolocation-api">https://www.abstractapi.com/ip-geolocation-api</a> - API](https://www.abstractapi.com/ip-geolocation-api) — IP Geolocation API from Abstract - Extensive free plan allowing 200,000 requests per month.<br>
<a href="https://codegiant.io">https://codegiant.io</a> - Project Management with Repository hosting & CI/CD. Free Plan Offers Unlimited Repositories,Projects & Documents with 5 Team Members. 500 CI/CD minutes per month. 30000 Serverless Code Run minutes per month.1GB repository storage.<br>
<a href="https://powerbi.com">https://powerbi.com</a> - — Business Insights & Analytics by Microsoft. Free Plan offers limited use with 1 Million User licenses.<br>
<a href="https://www.manageengine.com/cloud-log-management">https://www.manageengine.com/cloud-log-management</a> - Cloud](https://www.manageengine.com/cloud-log-management) — Log Management service powered by Manage Engine. Free Plan offers 50 GB storage with 1 Month retention.<br>
<a href="https://arvancloud.com/) — Offers cloud related services (CDN,Cloud DNS, PaaS, Security etc.">https://arvancloud.com/) — Offers cloud related services (CDN,Cloud DNS, PaaS, Security etc.</a> - — Offers cloud related services (CDN,Cloud DNS, PaaS, Security etc.). Free plan offers :<br>
<a href="https://rocketgit.com">https://rocketgit.com</a> - Repository Hosting based on Git. Unlimited Public & Private repositories.<br>
<a href="https://similarweb.com">https://similarweb.com</a> - — Analytics for Web & Mobile Apps. Free Plan offers 5 results per metric, 1 month of mobile app data & 3 months of website data.<br>
<a href="https://snapshooter.com/">https://snapshooter.com/</a> - Backup solution for DigitalOcean, AWS, LightSail, Hetzner and Exoscale, with support for direct database, file system and application backups to s3 based storage. Provides a free plan with daily backups for one resource.<br>
<a href="https://miradore.com">https://miradore.com</a> - Management service. Stay up-to-date with your device fleet and secure an unlimited number of devices for free. Free plan offers basic features.<br>
<a href="https://bluej.org">https://bluej.org</a> - A free Java Development Environment designed for beginners, used by millions worldwide. Powered by Oracle & simple GUI to help beginners.<br>
<a href="https://automate.io">https://automate.io</a> - Simple and complex automation workflow tool with over 200+ app integrations. 300 monthly actions and 5 bots are free<br>
<a href="https://developer.deepar.ai) — Augmented reality face filters for any platform with one SDK. Free plan provides up to 10 monthly active users (MAU">https://developer.deepar.ai) — Augmented reality face filters for any platform with one SDK. Free plan provides up to 10 monthly active users (MAU</a> - Augmented reality face filters for any platform with one SDK. Free plan provides up to 10 monthly active users (MAU) and tracking up to 4 faces<br>
<a href="https://miradore.com">https://miradore.com</a> - Device Management service. Stay up-to-date with your device fleet and secure an unlimited number of devices for free. Free plan offers basic features.<br>
<a href="https://branch.io">https://branch.io</a> - Mobile Analytics Platform. Free Tier offers upto 10K Mobile App Users with deep-linking & other services.<br>
<a href="https://www.koyeb.com">https://www.koyeb.com</a> - Koyeb is a developer-friendly serverless platform to deploy apps globally. Seamlessly run Docker containers, web apps, and APIs with git-based deployment, native autoscaling, a global edge network, and built-in service mesh and discovery. Koyeb provides two nano services to run your apps with its forever-free tier and also sponsors open-source projects with free resources.<br>
<a href="https://freecurrencyapi.net/">https://freecurrencyapi.net/</a> - Free currency conversion and exchange rate data API. 10 requests/hour without an API key, 50 000 requests per month when you register for free.<br>
<a href="https://duo.com/) — Two-factor authentication (2FA">https://duo.com/) — Two-factor authentication (2FA</a> - Two-factor authentication (2FA) for website or app. Free for 10 users, all authentication methods, unlimited, integrations, hardware tokens.<br>
<a href="https://firebase.com">https://firebase.com</a> - Firebase helps you build and run successful apps. Offers a variety of services in the Free Spark Plan listed here :<br>
<a href="http://maps.stamen.com/">http://maps.stamen.com/</a> - Free map tiles and tile hosting.<br>
<a href="https://www.acunote.com/">https://www.acunote.com/</a> - Free project management and SCRUM software for up to 5 team members<br>
<a href="https://backlog.com">https://backlog.com</a> - Everything your team needs to release great projects in one platform. Free plan offers 1 Project with 10 users & 100MB storage.<br>
<a href="https://wikifactory.com/">https://wikifactory.com/</a> - Product designing Service with Projects,VCS & Issues. Free plan offers unlimited projects & collaborators and 3GB storage.<br>
<a href="https://databox.com">https://databox.com</a> - Business Insights & Analytics by combining other analytics & BI platforms. Free Plan offers 3 users, dashboards & data sources. 11M historical data records.<br>
<a href="https://robocorp.com">https://robocorp.com</a> - Open-source stack for powering Automation Ops. Try out Cloud features and implement simple automations for free. Robot work 240 min/month, 10 Assistant runs, Storage of 100 MB.<br>
<a href="https://treescale.com/">https://treescale.com/</a> - Host and manage container images with group permissions. Free tier offers 1 GB storage for private repositories.<br>
<a href="https://www.lazarus-ide.org/">https://www.lazarus-ide.org/</a> - Lazarus is a Delphi compatible cross-platform IDE for Rapid Application Development.<br>
<a href="https://www.lazarus-ide.org/">https://www.lazarus-ide.org/</a> - Lazarus is a Delphi compatible cross-platform IDE for Rapid Application Development.<br>
<a href="https://nextdns.io">https://nextdns.io</a> - DNS based firewall, 300K free queries monthly<br>
<a href="https://datelist.io">https://datelist.io</a> - Online booking / appointment scheduling system. Free up to 5 bookings per month, includes 1 calendar<br>
<a href="https://www.zdoo.co">https://www.zdoo.co</a> - With CRM, OA, and Project management suites, zdoo is so powerful for team collaboration. Free cloud version with limited users and space offered, one-month free trial for premium versions.<br>
<a href="https://www.zentao.jp">https://www.zentao.jp</a> - An application lifecycle management tool involves issue tracking, free Saas version available for basic plan. Premium versions on-premise is also offered.<br>
<a href="https://freedcamp.com/">https://freedcamp.com/</a> - tasks, discussions, milestones, time tracking, calendar, files and password manager. Free plan with unlimited projects, users and files storage.<br>
<a href="https://glitterly.app/">https://glitterly.app/</a> - Programatically generate dynamic images from base templates. Restful API and nocode integrations. Free tier comes with 50 images/month and 5 templates.<br>
<a href="https://pages.cloudflare.com/) — Free web hosting (JAMstack platform">https://pages.cloudflare.com/) — Free web hosting (JAMstack platform</a> - — Free web hosting (JAMstack platform) for frontend developers to collaborate and deploy websites. 1 build at a time, 500 builds/month, unlimited sites, unlimited requests, unlimited bandwidth.<br>
<a href="https://streamdata.io/">https://streamdata.io/</a> - Turns any REST API into an event-driven streaming API. Free plan up to 1 million messages and 10 concurrent connections.<br>
<a href="https://supabase.io">https://supabase.io</a> - The Open Source Firebase Alternative to build backends. Free Plan offers the following :<br>
<a href="https://firebase.com) — Firebase helps you build and run successful apps. Free Spark Plan offers Authentication, Hosting, Firebase ML , Realtime Database,Cloud Storage,Testlab. A/B Testing, Analytics, App Distribution, App Indexing, Cloud Messaging (FCM">https://firebase.com) — Firebase helps you build and run successful apps. Free Spark Plan offers Authentication, Hosting, Firebase ML , Realtime Database,Cloud Storage,Testlab. A/B Testing, Analytics, App Distribution, App Indexing, Cloud Messaging (FCM</a> - Firebase helps you build and run successful apps. Free Spark Plan offers Authentication, Hosting, Firebase ML , Realtime Database,Cloud Storage,Testlab. A/B Testing, Analytics, App Distribution, App Indexing, Cloud Messaging (FCM), Crashlytics, Dynamic Links, In-App Messaging, Performance Monitoring, Predictions, and Remote Config are always-free.<br>
<a href="https://supabase.io">https://supabase.io</a> - The Open Source Firebase Alternative to build backends. Free Plan offers Authentication, Realtime Database & Object Storage.<br>
<a href="https://www.uxtweak.com/">https://www.uxtweak.com/</a> - Record and watch how visitors use your web site or app. Free unlimited time for small projects<br>
<a href="https://saas.zentao.pm/">https://saas.zentao.pm/</a> - An Application Lifecycle Management solution for Issue Tracking and Project Management, on-premise and open source version are available as well.<br>
<a href="https://vabotu.com/">https://vabotu.com/</a> - A collaborative tool for project management. Free and other plans are available. The Freelance plan is for 10 users, include messaging, task-boards, 5GB online storage, workspaces, export data.<br>
<a href="https://wikifactory.com/">https://wikifactory.com/</a> - Product designing Service with Projects, VCS & Issues. Free plan offers unlimited projects & collaborators and 3GB storage.<br>
<a href="https://www.shakebugs.com/">https://www.shakebugs.com/</a> - In-app bug reporting and feedback tool for mobile apps. Free plan.<br>
<a href="https://www.shakebugs.com/">https://www.shakebugs.com/</a> - In-app bug reporting and feedback tool for mobile apps. Free plan, 10 bug reports per app/per month.<br>
<a href="https://www.format-express.dev">https://www.format-express.dev</a> - - Instant online formatter for JSON / XML / SQL.<br>
<a href="https://mocki.io">https://mocki.io</a> - A tool that lets you create mock GraphQL and REST APIs synced to a GitHub repository. Simple REST APIs are free to create and use without signup.<br>
<a href="#privacy-management">#privacy-management</a> - <br>
<a href="https://www.bearer.sh/">https://www.bearer.sh/</a> - Helps implement privacy by design via audits and continuous workflows so that organizations comply with GDPR and other regulations. Free tier is limited to smaller teams and SaaS version only.<br>
<a href="https://www.osano.com/">https://www.osano.com/</a> - Consent management and compliance platform with everything from GDPR representation to cookie banners. Free tier offers basic features.<br>
<a href="https://www.iubenda.com/">https://www.iubenda.com/</a> - Privacy and cookie policies along with consent management. Free tier offers limited privacy and cookie policy as well as cookie banners.<br>
<a href="https://cookiefirst.com/">https://cookiefirst.com/</a> - Cookie banners, auditing, and multi-language consent management solution. Free tier offers a one-time scan and a single banner.<br>
<a href="https://www.ketch.com/">https://www.ketch.com/</a> - Consent management and privacy framework tool. Free tier offers most features with a limited visitor count.<br>
<a href="https://onlineornot.com/">https://onlineornot.com/</a> - 10 uptime monitors with a 5 minute interval, 10 page speed monitors with a 12 hour interval. Free alerts via Slack and Email.<br>
<a href="https://workers.cloudflare.com/">https://workers.cloudflare.com/</a> - - Deploy serverless code for free on Cloudflare's global network. 100,000 free requests per day with a workers.dev subdomain.<br>
<a href="https://workers.cloudflare.com/">https://workers.cloudflare.com/</a> - - Deploy serverless code for free on Cloudflare's global network. 100,000 free requests per day with a workers.dev subdomain.<br>
<a href="https://railway.app">https://railway.app</a> - Railway is an infrastructure platform where you can provision infrastructure, develop with that infrastructure locally, and then deploy to the cloud. 3 Projects, 2 Plugins / Project, 2 Evironments / Project, 3 Live Deploys / Environment available for free.<br>
<a href="https://onlineornot.com/">https://onlineornot.com/</a> - 10 uptime monitors with a 5 minute interval, 1 page speed monitors with a 12 hour interval. Free alerts via Slack and Email.<br>
<a href="https://frontaid.io/">https://frontaid.io/</a> - Headless CMS that stores JSON content directly in your own Git repository. No restrictions.<br>
<a href="https://www.softacheck.com/">https://www.softacheck.com/</a> - An online tool that performs static analysis for C/C++ code using open source tools such as cppcheck and clang-tidy and automatically generates code documentation for users using doxygen. This tool is free for use.<br>
<a href="https://glitch.com/">https://glitch.com/</a> - Free public hosting with features such as code sharing and real-time collaboration. Free plan has 1000 hours/month limit.<br>
<a href="https://deta.sh/?ref=freedev">https://deta.sh/?ref=freedev</a> - a 100% free cloud provider from Germany 🇩🇪. Deta offers friendly & fast support on Slack & Discord as well.<br>
<a href="https://hey.space">https://hey.space</a> - Task management tool with chat, calendar, timeline and video calls. Free for up to 5 users.<br>
<a href="https://www.timecamp.com/">https://www.timecamp.com/</a> - Free time tracking software for unlimited users. Easily integrates with PM tools like Jira, Trello, Asana, etc.<br>
<a href="https://shrtco.de/docs">https://shrtco.de/docs</a> - - Free URL Shortening API without authorization and no request limits.<br>
<a href="https://stormkit.io/">https://stormkit.io/</a> - Integrate building, deploying and hosting seamlessly with your git flow of your JAMStack or Node.JS app. 50 GB bandwith and 10m requests for free per month including free SSL.<br>
<a href="https://redirect.pizza/">https://redirect.pizza/</a> - Easily manage redirects with HTTPS support. Free plan includes 10 sources and 100.000 hits per month.<br>
<a href="https://landing.ant.design/">https://landing.ant.design/</a> - Landing Page](https://landing.ant.design/) - Ant Design Landing Page provides a template built by Ant Motion's motion components. It has a rich homepage template, downloads the template code package, and can be used quickly. You can also use the editor to quickly build your own dedicated page.<br>
<a href="https://updrafts.app">https://updrafts.app</a> - WYSIWYG web site builder for tailwindcss based designs. Free for non-commercial usage.<br>
<a href="#table-of-contents">#table-of-contents</a> - top](#table-of-contents)**<br>
<a href="#table-of-contents">#table-of-contents</a> - top](#table-of-contents)**<br>
<a href="#table-of-contents">#table-of-contents</a> - top](#table-of-contents)**<br>
<a href="#table-of-contents">#table-of-contents</a> - top](#table-of-contents)**<br>
<a href="#table-of-contents">#table-of-contents</a> - top](#table-of-contents)**<br>
<a href="#table-of-contents">#table-of-contents</a> - top](#table-of-contents)**<br>
<a href="#table-of-contents">#table-of-contents</a> - top](#table-of-contents)**<br>
<a href="#table-of-contents">#table-of-contents</a> - top](#table-of-contents)**<br>
<a href="#table-of-contents">#table-of-contents</a> - top](#table-of-contents)**<br>
<a href="#table-of-contents">#table-of-contents</a> - top](#table-of-contents)**<br>
<a href="#table-of-contents">#table-of-contents</a> - top](#table-of-contents)**<br>
<a href="#table-of-contents">#table-of-contents</a> - top](#table-of-contents)**<br>
<a href="#table-of-contents">#table-of-contents</a> - top](#table-of-contents)**<br>
<a href="#table-of-contents">#table-of-contents</a> - top](#table-of-contents)**<br>
<a href="#table-of-contents">#table-of-contents</a> - top](#table-of-contents)**<br>
<a href="#table-of-contents">#table-of-contents</a> - top](#table-of-contents)**<br>
<a href="#table-of-contents">#table-of-contents</a> - top](#table-of-contents)**<br>
<a href="#table-of-contents">#table-of-contents</a> - top](#table-of-contents)**<br>
<a href="#table-of-contents">#table-of-contents</a> - top](#table-of-contents)**<br>
<a href="#table-of-contents">#table-of-contents</a> - top](#table-of-contents)**<br>
<a href="#table-of-contents">#table-of-contents</a> - top](#table-of-contents)**<br>
<a href="#table-of-contents">#table-of-contents</a> - top](#table-of-contents)**<br>
<a href="#table-of-contents">#table-of-contents</a> - top](#table-of-contents)**<br>
<a href="#table-of-contents">#table-of-contents</a> - top](#table-of-contents)**<br>
<a href="#table-of-contents">#table-of-contents</a> - top](#table-of-contents)**<br>
<a href="#table-of-contents">#table-of-contents</a> - top](#table-of-contents)**<br>
<a href="#table-of-contents">#table-of-contents</a> - top](#table-of-contents)**<br>
<a href="#table-of-contents">#table-of-contents</a> - top](#table-of-contents)**<br>
<a href="#table-of-contents">#table-of-contents</a> - top](#table-of-contents)**<br>
<a href="#table-of-contents">#table-of-contents</a> - top](#table-of-contents)**<br>
<a href="#table-of-contents">#table-of-contents</a> - top](#table-of-contents)**<br>
<a href="#table-of-contents">#table-of-contents</a> - top](#table-of-contents)**<br>
<a href="#table-of-contents">#table-of-contents</a> - top](#table-of-contents)**<br>
<a href="#table-of-contents">#table-of-contents</a> - top](#table-of-contents)**<br>
<a href="#table-of-contents">#table-of-contents</a> - top](#table-of-contents)**<br>
<a href="#table-of-contents">#table-of-contents</a> - top](#table-of-contents)**<br>
<a href="#table-of-contents">#table-of-contents</a> - top](#table-of-contents)**<br>
<a href="#table-of-contents">#table-of-contents</a> - top](#table-of-contents)**<br>
<a href="#table-of-contents">#table-of-contents</a> - top](#table-of-contents)**<br>
<a href="#table-of-contents">#table-of-contents</a> - top](#table-of-contents)**<br>
<a href="#table-of-contents">#table-of-contents</a> - top](#table-of-contents)**<br>
<a href="#table-of-contents">#table-of-contents</a> - top](#table-of-contents)**<br>
<a href="#table-of-contents">#table-of-contents</a> - top](#table-of-contents)**<br>
<a href="#table-of-contents">#table-of-contents</a> - top](#table-of-contents)**<br>
<a href="#table-of-contents">#table-of-contents</a> - top](#table-of-contents)**<br>
<a href="#table-of-contents">#table-of-contents</a> - top](#table-of-contents)**<br>
<a href="#table-of-contents">#table-of-contents</a> - top](#table-of-contents)**<br>
<a href="#table-of-contents">#table-of-contents</a> - top](#table-of-contents)**<br>
<a href="https://pingpong.one/">https://pingpong.one/</a> - Advanced status page platform with monitoring. Free tier includes one public customizable status page with SSL subdomain.<br>
<a href="https://pingpong.one/">https://pingpong.one/</a> - Advanced status page platform with monitoring. Free tier includes one public customizable status page with SSL subdomain. Pro plan is offered to open-source projects and non-profits free of charge.<br>
<a href="https://webscraping.ai">https://webscraping.ai</a> - Simple Web Scraping API with built-in parsing, Chrome rendering and proxies. 2000 free API calls per month.<br>
<a href="https://recaptchame.com/">https://recaptchame.com/</a> - free reCAPTCHA and hCAPTCHA backend service. No Server-Side coding needed. Works for static websites.<br>
<a href="https://okteto.com">https://okteto.com</a> - - Managed Kubernetes service designed for remote development. Free developer accounts come with 5 Kubernetes namespaces, 3Gi/pod with a maximum of 8Gi/namespace, 1CPU/pod with a maximum of 4CPUs/namespace and 5GB Disk space. The apps sleep after 24 hours of inactivity.<br>
<a href="https://mastershot.app">https://mastershot.app</a> - Completely free browser-based video editor. No watermark, up to 1080p export options.<br>
<a href="https://operous.dev/">https://operous.dev/</a> - Cloud instance testing tool with a comprehensive and automated set of test-suites of best practices, performance, and security. Free tier offers 100 testing minutes, 10 Test Suites, and up to 5 instances to 1 user.<br>
<a href="https://devpal.co/base64-decode/">https://devpal.co/base64-decode/</a> - — Online free tool for decoding & encoding data.<br>
<a href="https://codeberg.org/">https://codeberg.org/</a> - Unlimited public and private Git repos for free and open-source projects.<br>
<a href="https://codeberg.page/">https://codeberg.page/</a> - hosting with [Codeberg Pages](https://codeberg.page/).<br>
<a href="https://codeberg.page/">https://codeberg.page/</a> - Unlimited public and private Git repos for free and open-source projects. Static website hosting with [Codeberg Pages](https://codeberg.page/).<br>
<a href="https://scrapersproxy.com) — Simple HTTP proxy API made for scraping. Scrape anonymously without having to worry about restrictions, blocks or captchas. First 100 successfully scrape's per month free including javascript rendering (more available if you contact support">https://scrapersproxy.com) — Simple HTTP proxy API made for scraping. Scrape anonymously without having to worry about restrictions, blocks or captchas. First 100 successfully scrape's per month free including javascript rendering (more available if you contact support</a> - — Simple HTTP proxy API made for scraping. Scrape anonymously without having to worry about restrictions, blocks or captchas. First 100 successfully scrape's per month free including javascript rendering (more available if you contact support).<br>
<a href="https://www.ntaskmanager.com/">https://www.ntaskmanager.com/</a> - Project management software that enables your teams tn collaborate, plan, analyze and manage everyday tasks. Basic Plan free forever with 100 MB storage, 5 users/team. Unlimited workspaces, meetings,tasks, timesheets and issue tracking.<br>
<a href="https://storj.io">https://storj.io</a> - Decentralised Private Cloud Storage for Apps and Developers. Free plan provides 3 Projects, 50 GB storage per project/month , 50 GB bandwidth per project/month.<br>
<a href="https://gforge.com">https://gforge.com</a> - Project Management & Issue Tracking toolset for complex projects with self-premises and SaaS options. SaaS free plan offers first 5 users free & free for Open Source Projects.<br>
<a href="https://paiza.cloud/en/">https://paiza.cloud/en/</a> - Develop Web apps in Browser without having the need to setup anything. Free Plan offers 1 server with 24 hours lifetime and 4 hours running time per day with 2 CPU cores, 2 GB RAM and 1 GB storage.<br>
<a href="https://jfrog.com/start-free/)] - JFrog Artifactory offers a universal solution supporting all major package formats including Alpine, Maven, Gradle, Docker, Cargo, Conda, Conan, Debian, Go, Helm, Vagrant, YUM, P2, Ivy, NuGet, PHP, NPM, RubyGems, PyPI, Bower, CocoaPods, GitLFS, Opkg, SBT, and more. Free tier of JFrog Platform incudes Artifactory, XRay (a universal software composition analysis solution), and Pipelines (CI/CD, workflow, and tool orchestration tool.">https://jfrog.com/start-free/)] - JFrog Artifactory offers a universal solution supporting all major package formats including Alpine, Maven, Gradle, Docker, Cargo, Conda, Conan, Debian, Go, Helm, Vagrant, YUM, P2, Ivy, NuGet, PHP, NPM, RubyGems, PyPI, Bower, CocoaPods, GitLFS, Opkg, SBT, and more. Free tier of JFrog Platform incudes Artifactory, XRay (a universal software composition analysis solution), and Pipelines (CI/CD, workflow, and tool orchestration tool.</a> - JFrog Artifactory offers a universal solution supporting all major package formats including Alpine, Maven, Gradle, Docker, Cargo, Conda, Conan, Debian, Go, Helm, Vagrant, YUM, P2, Ivy, NuGet, PHP, NPM, RubyGems, PyPI, Bower, CocoaPods, GitLFS, Opkg, SBT, and more. Free tier of JFrog Platform incudes Artifactory, XRay (a universal software composition analysis solution), and Pipelines (CI/CD, workflow, and tool orchestration tool.)<br>
<a href="https://central.sonatype.org">https://central.sonatype.org</a> - default artifact repository for Apache Maven, SBT and other build systems.<br>
<a href="https://central.sonatype.org">https://central.sonatype.org</a> - The default artifact repository for Apache Maven, SBT and other build systems.<br>
<a href="https://jfrog.com/start-free/)] - A universal artifact repository that supports all major package formats including Alpine, Maven, Gradle, Docker, Cargo, Conda, Conan, Debian, Go, Helm, Vagrant, YUM, P2, Ivy, NuGet, PHP, NPM, RubyGems, PyPI, Bower, CocoaPods, GitLFS, Opkg, SBT, and more. Free tier of JFrog Platform incudes Artifactory, XRay (a universal software composition analysis solution), and Pipelines (CI/CD, workflow, and tool orchestration tool.">https://jfrog.com/start-free/)] - A universal artifact repository that supports all major package formats including Alpine, Maven, Gradle, Docker, Cargo, Conda, Conan, Debian, Go, Helm, Vagrant, YUM, P2, Ivy, NuGet, PHP, NPM, RubyGems, PyPI, Bower, CocoaPods, GitLFS, Opkg, SBT, and more. Free tier of JFrog Platform incudes Artifactory, XRay (a universal software composition analysis solution), and Pipelines (CI/CD, workflow, and tool orchestration tool.</a> - A universal artifact repository that supports all major package formats including Alpine, Maven, Gradle, Docker, Cargo, Conda, Conan, Debian, Go, Helm, Vagrant, YUM, P2, Ivy, NuGet, PHP, NPM, RubyGems, PyPI, Bower, CocoaPods, GitLFS, Opkg, SBT, and more. Free tier of JFrog Platform incudes Artifactory, XRay (a universal software composition analysis solution), and Pipelines (CI/CD, workflow, and tool orchestration tool.)<br>
<a href="https://jfrog.com/start-free/">https://jfrog.com/start-free/</a> - An artifact repository that supports package formats including Alpine, Maven, Gradle, Docker, Cargo, Conda, Conan, Debian, Go, Helm, Vagrant, YUM, P2, Ivy, NuGet, PHP, NPM, RubyGems, PyPI, Bower, CocoaPods, GitLFS, Opkg, SBT, and more.<br>
<a href="https://jfrog.com/start-free">https://jfrog.com/start-free</a> - (formerly Shippable)](https://jfrog.com/start-free) — The free tier offers 2,000 CI/CD minutes per month at no cost.<br>
<a href="https://jfrog.com/start-free/)] - An artifact repository that supports numerous package formats like Maven, Docker, Cargo, Helm, PyPI, CocoaPods, and GitLFS. Incudes package scanning tool XRay and CI/CD tool Pipelines (formerly Shippable">https://jfrog.com/start-free/)] - An artifact repository that supports numerous package formats like Maven, Docker, Cargo, Helm, PyPI, CocoaPods, and GitLFS. Incudes package scanning tool XRay and CI/CD tool Pipelines (formerly Shippable</a> - An artifact repository that supports numerous package formats like Maven, Docker, Cargo, Helm, PyPI, CocoaPods, and GitLFS. Incudes package scanning tool XRay and CI/CD tool Pipelines (formerly Shippable) with a free tier of 2,000 CI/CD minutes per month.<br>
<a href="https://harperdb.io/">https://harperdb.io/</a> - Serverless cloud database, with dynamic schema based on JSON, 3000 IOPS with 1GB storage<br>
<a href="https://jfrog.com/start-free/) - An artifact repository that supports numerous package formats like Maven, Docker, Cargo, Helm, PyPI, CocoaPods, and GitLFS. Incudes package scanning tool XRay and CI/CD tool Pipelines (formerly Shippable">https://jfrog.com/start-free/) - An artifact repository that supports numerous package formats like Maven, Docker, Cargo, Helm, PyPI, CocoaPods, and GitLFS. Incudes package scanning tool XRay and CI/CD tool Pipelines (formerly Shippable</a> - An artifact repository that supports numerous package formats like Maven, Docker, Cargo, Helm, PyPI, CocoaPods, and GitLFS. Incudes package scanning tool XRay and CI/CD tool Pipelines (formerly Shippable) with a free tier of 2,000 CI/CD minutes per month.<br>
<a href="https://packagecloud.io/users/new?plan=free_usage_plan) — Easy to use repository hosting for: Maven, RPM, DEB, PyPi, NPM, and RubyGem packages (has free tier">https://packagecloud.io/users/new?plan=free_usage_plan) — Easy to use repository hosting for: Maven, RPM, DEB, PyPi, NPM, and RubyGem packages (has free tier</a> - Easy to use repository hosting for: Maven, RPM, DEB, PyPi, NPM, and RubyGem packages (has free tier).<br>
<a href="https://www.netlify.com/">https://www.netlify.com/</a> - An intuitive Git-based workflow and powerful serverless platform to build, deploy, and collaborate on web apps. Free tier available. Pro version free for Open Source teams.<br>
<a href="https://mailvalidator.io/">https://mailvalidator.io/</a> - Verify 300 emails/month for free, real-time API with bulk processing available<br>
<a href="https://iploka.com/">https://iploka.com/</a> - IP to Geolocation API - Forever free plan for developers with 10k requests per month limit.<br>
<a href="https://statically.io/) — CDN for Git repos (GitHub, GitLab, Bitbucket">https://statically.io/) — CDN for Git repos (GitHub, GitLab, Bitbucket</a> - CDN for Git repos (GitHub, GitLab, Bitbucket), WordPress-related assets and images<br>
<a href="https://thedev.id">https://thedev.id</a> - A free domain for developers.<br>
<a href="https://statically.io/docs/using-screenshot/">https://statically.io/docs/using-screenshot/</a> - — A free screenshot API to convert web to image or PDF. Supports desktop and mobile view.<br>
<a href="https://thedev.id">https://thedev.id</a> - A free thedev.id subdomain for developers.<br>
<a href="https://calendly.com">https://calendly.com</a> - Calendly is the tool for connecting and scheduling meetings. Free plan provides 1 Calendar connection per user and Unlimited meetings. Desktop and Mobile apps also provided.<br>
<a href="https://flutterflow.io">https://flutterflow.io</a> - — Build your Flutter App UI without writing a single line of code. Also has a Firebase integration. Free plan includes full access to UI Builder and Free templates.<br>
<a href="https://cdnjs.com/">https://cdnjs.com/</a> - Simple. Fast. Reliable. Content delivery at its finest. cdnjs is a free and open-source CDN service trusted by over 11% of all websites, powered by Cloudflare.<br>
<a href="https://www.jsdelivr.com/">https://www.jsdelivr.com/</a> - A free, fast, and reliable CDN for open source. Supports npm, GitHub, WordPress, Deno, and more.<br>
<a href="https://directus.io">https://directus.io</a> - Automatically generates a dynamic REST and GraphQL API for any SQL database.<br>
<a href="https://directus.io">https://directus.io</a> - Headless CMS. A completely free and open-source platform for managing assets and database content on-prem or in the Cloud. No limitations or paywalls.<br>
<a href="https://directus.io">https://directus.io</a> - — Directus as a service. An open-source data platform that automatically generates a dynamic REST and GraphQL API for pure SQL databases.<br>
<a href="https://duckly.com/">https://duckly.com/</a> - Talk and collaborate in real-time with your team. Pair programming with any IDE, terminal sharing, voice, video and screen sharing. Free for small teams.<br>
<a href="https://bookmarkos.com">https://bookmarkos.com</a> - Free all-on-one bookmark manager, tab manager, and task manager in a customizable online desktop with folder collaboration.<br>
<a href="https://nic.eu.org">https://nic.eu.org</a> - Free eu.org domain. Request is usually approved in 14 days.<br>
<a href="https://nic.eu.org">https://nic.eu.org</a> - Free eu.org domain. Request is usually approved in 14 days.<br>
<a href="https://fakermail.com/">https://fakermail.com/</a> - Free, temporary email for testing with last 100 email accounts stored.<br>
<a href="https://deepnote.com">https://deepnote.com</a> - A new kind of data science notebook. Jupyter-compatible with real-time collaboration and running in the cloud. Free tier includes unlimited personal projects, up to 750 hours of standard hardware and teams with up to 3 editors.<br>
<a href="https://getstream.io/">https://getstream.io/</a> - Build scalable newsfeeds, activity streams, chat and messaging in a few hours instead of weeks<br>
<a href="https://github.com/features/actions)(Free for Public Repos, 2000 min/month for private repos free">https://github.com/features/actions)(Free for Public Repos, 2000 min/month for private repos free</a> - Public Repos, 2000 min/month for private repos free)<br>
<a href="https://deepnote.com">https://deepnote.com</a> - A new kind of data science notebook. Jupyter-compatible with real-time collaboration and running in the cloud. Free tier includes unlimited personal projects, up to 750 hours of standard hardware and teams with up to 3 editors.<br>
<a href="https://reqres.in">https://reqres.in</a> - A Free hosted REST-API ready to respond to your AJAX requests.<br>
<a href="https://duckly.com/">https://duckly.com/</a> - Talk and collaborate in real-time with your team. Pair programming with any IDE, terminal sharing, voice, video and screen sharing. Free for small teams.<br>
<a href="https://robocorp.com">https://robocorp.com</a> - Open-source stack for powering Automation Ops. Try out Cloud features and implement simple automations for free. Robot work 240 min/month, 10 Assistant runs, Storage of 100 MB.<br>
<a href="https://www.softacheck.com/">https://www.softacheck.com/</a> - An online tool that performs static analysis for C/C++ code using open source tools such as cppcheck and clang-tidy and automatically generates code documentation for users using doxygen. This tool is free for use.<br>
<a href="https://recaptchame.com/">https://recaptchame.com/</a> - free reCAPTCHA and hCAPTCHA backend service. No Server-Side coding needed. Works for static websites.<br>
<a href="https://zoho.com/subscriptions">https://zoho.com/subscriptions</a> - Recurring Billing management free for 20 customers/subscriptions & 1 user with all the payment hosting done by Zoho themselves. Last 40 subscription metrics are stored<br>
<a href="https://www.shakebugs.com/">https://www.shakebugs.com/</a> - In-app bug reporting and feedback tool for mobile apps. Free plan, 10 bug reports per app/per month.<br>
<a href="https://smartmockups.com/">https://smartmockups.com/</a> - Create product mockups, 200 free mockups.<br>
<a href="https://updrafts.app">https://updrafts.app</a> - WYSIWYG web site builder for tailwindcss based designs. Free for non-commercial usage.<br>
<a href="https://www.bearer.sh/">https://www.bearer.sh/</a> - Helps implement privacy by design via audits and continuous workflows so that organizations comply with GDPR and other regulations. Free tier is limited to smaller teams and SaaS version only.<br>
<a href="https://herotofu.com/">https://herotofu.com/</a> - Forms backend with bot detection and encrypted archive. Forward submissions via UI to email, Slack, or Zapier. Use your own frontend, no server code required. Free plan gives unlimited forms and 50 submissions per month.<br>
<a href="https://railway.app">https://railway.app</a> - Railway is an infrastructure platform where you can provision infrastructure, develop with that infrastructure locally, and then deploy to the cloud. 3 Projects, 2 Plugins / Project, 2 Environments / Project, 3 Live Deploys / Environment available for free.<br>
<a href="https://www.trackawesomelist.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev">https://www.trackawesomelist.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev</a> - Awesome List](https://www.trackawesomelist.com/badge.svg)](https://www.trackawesomelist.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev)<br>
<a href="https://www.trackawesomelist.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev">https://www.trackawesomelist.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev</a> - <br>
<a href="https://docs.datastax.com/en/astra/docs/datastax-astra-database-limits.html">https://docs.datastax.com/en/astra/docs/datastax-astra-database-limits.html</a> - Cloud Native Cassandra as a Service with [40GB free tier](https://docs.datastax.com/en/astra/docs/datastax-astra-database-limits.html)<br>
<a href="https://clarity.microsoft.com/">https://clarity.microsoft.com/</a> - - Session recording completely free with "no traffic limits", no project limits, and no sampling<br>
<a href="https://squidex.io/) - Offers free tier for small projects. API / GraphQL first. Open source, and based on event sourcing (versing every changes automatically">https://squidex.io/) - Offers free tier for small projects. API / GraphQL first. Open source, and based on event sourcing (versing every changes automatically</a> - Offers free tier for small projects. API / GraphQL first. Open source, and based on event sourcing (versing every changes automatically).<br>
<a href="https://api.ksoft.si/">https://api.ksoft.si/</a> - Free lyrics api chiefly aimed for discord bots.Also provides an extensive library of images and user data<br>
<a href="https://replit.com/">https://replit.com/</a> - A cloud coding environment for various program languages.<br>
<a href="https://www.datastax.com/products/datastax-astra/pricing">https://www.datastax.com/products/datastax-astra/pricing</a> - Cloud Native Cassandra as a Service with [40GB free tier](https://www.datastax.com/products/datastax-astra/pricing)<br>
<a href="https://formsubmit.co/">https://formsubmit.co/</a> - Easy form endpoints for your HTML forms. Free Forever. No registration required.<br>
<a href="https://formsubmit.co/">https://formsubmit.co/</a> - Easy form endpoints for your HTML forms. Free Forever. No registration required.<br>
<a href="https://mailtie.com/">https://mailtie.com/</a> - Free Email Forwarding for Your Domain. No registration required. Free Forever.<br>
<a href="https://www.lightly.ai/">https://www.lightly.ai/</a> - Improve your machine learning models by using the right data. Use datasets of up to 1'000 samples for free.<br>
<a href="https://flashdrive.io">https://flashdrive.io</a> - PaaS service similar to Heroku with a Developer-centric approach and all inclusive features. Dev Tier is free and perfect to host static assets and staging projects.<br>
<a href="https://flashdrive.io">https://flashdrive.io</a> - PaaS service similar to Heroku with a developer-centric approach and all inclusive features. Free tier for static assets, staging and developer apps.<br>
<a href="https://localeum.com">https://localeum.com</a> - Free up to 1000 strings, 1 user, unlimited languages, unlimited projects<br>
<a href="https://mailazy.com/">https://mailazy.com/</a> - 500 emails/day free, 50,000 emails/month under the beta program!<br>
<a href="https://mailazy.com/">https://mailazy.com/</a> - Mailazy is the only simple transactional email service you’ll need. 500 emails/day free forever.<br>
<a href="https://mailazy.com/) — Mailazy is the only simple transactional email service you’ll need. 15,000 emails/month free forever (500 emails/day sending limit">https://mailazy.com/) — Mailazy is the only simple transactional email service you’ll need. 15,000 emails/month free forever (500 emails/day sending limit</a> - Mailazy is the only simple transactional email service you’ll need. 15,000 emails/month free forever (500 emails/day sending limit).<br>
<a href="https://www.scrumfast.com">https://www.scrumfast.com</a> - Free Scrum board with a very intuitive interface.<br>
<a href="https://mocko.dev/">https://mocko.dev/</a> - Proxy your API, choose which endpoints to mock in the cloud and inspect traffic, for free. Speed up your development and integrations tests.<br>
<a href="https://inboxkitten.com/">https://inboxkitten.com/</a> - Free temporary/disposable email inbox, with up-to 3 day email auto-deletes. Open sourced, and can be self-hosted.<br>
<a href="https://unicornplatform.com/">https://unicornplatform.com/</a> - - Effortless landing page builder with hosting. 1 website for free.<br>
<a href="https://pages.github.com) (Free for Public Repos">https://pages.github.com) (Free for Public Repos</a> - Hosting](https://pages.github.com) (Free for Public Repos)<br>
<a href="https://www.scrumfast.com">https://www.scrumfast.com</a> - Scrum board with a very intuitive interface, free up to 5 users.<br>
<a href="https://www.emailjs.com/">https://www.emailjs.com/</a> - This is not a full email server, this is just email client which you can use to send emails right from client send without exposing your credentials, the free tier has: 200 monthly requests, 2 email templates, Requests up to 50Kb, Limited contacts history.<br>
<a href="https://serpapi.com/">https://serpapi.com/</a> - Real-time search engine scraping API. Returns structured JSON results for Google, Youtube, Bing, Baidu, Walmart and many other engines. Free plan includes 100 successful API calls per month.<br>
<a href="https://internxt.com">https://internxt.com</a> - Internxt Drive is a zero-knowledge file storage service that's based on absolute privacy and uncompromising security. Sign up and get 10 GB for free, forever!<br>
<a href="https://www.datastax.com/products/datastax-astra/pricing">https://www.datastax.com/products/datastax-astra/pricing</a> - Cloud Native Cassandra as a Service with [40GB free tier](https://www.datastax.com/products/datastax-astra/pricing)<br>
<a href="https://deploynow.space">https://deploynow.space</a> - — Deploy smarter. Deploy faster. Deploy Now. - Deploy up to 3 web projects from your GitHub repository for free.<br>
<a href="https://herotofu.com/">https://herotofu.com/</a> - Forms backend with bot detection and encrypted archive. Forward submissions via UI to email, Slack, or Zapier. Use your own frontend, no server code required. Free plan gives unlimited forms and 100 submissions per month.<br>
<a href="https://mail.tm">https://mail.tm</a> - Disposable e-mail with user friendly interface. No registration needed.<br>
<a href="https://mailazy.com/) — Mailazy is the only simple transactional email service you’ll need. 15,000 emails/month free forever (500 emails/day sending limit">https://mailazy.com/) — Mailazy is the only simple transactional email service you’ll need. 15,000 emails/month free forever (500 emails/day sending limit</a> - Mailazy is the only simple transactional email service you’ll need. 15,000 emails/month free forever (500 emails/day sending limit).<br>
<a href="https://internxt.com">https://internxt.com</a> - Internxt Drive is a zero-knowledge file storage service that's based on absolute privacy and uncompromising security. Sign up and get 2 GB for free, forever!<br>
<a href="https://www.cockroachlabs.com/free-tier/">https://www.cockroachlabs.com/free-tier/</a> - Free CockroachDB up to 5GB and 1vCPU.<br>
<a href="https://nic.ua/">https://nic.ua/</a> - Free pp.ua domain.<br>
<a href="https://efemarai.com">https://efemarai.com</a> - Testing and debugging platform for ML models and data. Visualize any computational graph. Free 30 debugging sessions per month for developers.<br>
<a href="https://efemarai.com">https://efemarai.com</a> - Testing and debugging platform for ML models and data. Visualize any computational graph. Free 30 debugging sessions per month for developers.<br>
<a href="https://nic.ua/">https://nic.ua/</a> - Free pp.ua domain.<br>
<a href="https://www.deta.sh">https://www.deta.sh</a> - Deploy unlimited number of Node.js and Python apps for free. Includes free DBs, Auth and email.<br>
<a href="https://github.com/bridgecrewio/checkov">https://github.com/bridgecrewio/checkov</a> - Infrastructure as code (IaC) security powered by the open source tool - [Checkov](https://github.com/bridgecrewio/checkov). The core Bridgecrew platform is free for up to 50 IaC resources.<br>
<a href="https://sia.tech/">https://sia.tech/</a> - An open protocol for hosting data and web applications on the decentralized web using [Sia](https://sia.tech/). Free tier provides storage upto 100GB.<br>
<a href="https://vadoo.tv/">https://vadoo.tv/</a> - Video hosting and marketing made simple. Upload videos with a single click. Record, manage, share & more. Free tier provides unlimited videos, 10 GB bandwidth/month<br>
<a href="https://vadoo.tv/">https://vadoo.tv/</a> - Video hosting and marketing made simple. Upload videos with a single click. Record, manage, share & more. Free tier provides upto 10 videos, 1 GB storage/month, 10 GB bandwidth/month<br>
<a href="https://vadoo.tv/">https://vadoo.tv/</a> - Video hosting and marketing made simple. Upload videos with a single click. Record, manage, share & more. Free tier provides upto 10 videos, 1 GB storage, 10 GB bandwidth/month<br>
<a href="https://www.macrometa.com/">https://www.macrometa.com/</a> - a noSQL database, Pub/Sub, event processing, and serverless edge computing platform for building geo-distributed and real-time applications.<br>
<a href="https://www.macrometa.com/">https://www.macrometa.com/</a> - a noSQL database, Pub/Sub, event processing, and serverless edge computing platform for building geo-distributed and real-time applications. Free dev account gives access to 10,000 Operations/Day & 200MB Storage.<br>
<a href="https://geokeo.com">https://geokeo.com</a> - - Geocoding api with language correction and more. Worldwide coverage. 2,500 free daily queries<br>
<a href="https://gitlocalize.com">https://gitlocalize.com</a> - Free and unlimited for both private and public repositories<br>
<a href="https://www.apify.com/">https://www.apify.com/</a> - Web scraping and automation platform to create an API for any website and extract data. Ready-made scrapers, integrated proxies, and custom solutions. Free plan with $5 platform credits included every month.<br>
<a href="#remote-desktop-tools">#remote-desktop-tools</a> - Tools](#remote-desktop-tools)<br>
<a href="#remote-desktop-tools">#remote-desktop-tools</a> - Customer Support management with 3 agents and private knowledge base, email tickets. Integrates with [Zoho Assist](#remote-desktop-tools).<br>
<a href="https://zoho.com/assist">https://zoho.com/assist</a> - — Free for 1 remote technician & 5 unattended computers<br>
<a href="https://getscreen.me">https://getscreen.me</a> - Free for 2 devices, no limits on the number and duration of sessions<br>
<a href="#table-of-contents">#table-of-contents</a> - top](#table-of-contents)**<br>
<a href="https://hygger.io">https://hygger.io</a> - Project management platform. Free plan offers unlimited users,projects & boards with 100 MB Storage.<br>
<a href="https://zoho.com/assist">https://zoho.com/assist</a> - Customer Support management with 3 agents and private knowledge base, email tickets. Integrates with [Assist](https://zoho.com/assist) for 1 remote technician & 5 unattended computers.<br>
<a href="https://guacamole.apache.org/">https://guacamole.apache.org/</a> - — Open source clientless remote desktop gateway<br>
<a href="https://hottempmail.com/">https://hottempmail.com/</a> - Unlimited free temp email or disposable temporary email addresses. Autoexpire in one days.<br>
<a href="https://chpokify.com/">https://chpokify.com/</a> - Teams based Planning Poker that saves time of sprint estimation. Free up to 5 users, free Jira integrations, unlimited video calls, unlimited teams, unlimited sessions.<br>
<a href="https://planetscale.com/">https://planetscale.com/</a> - PlanetScale is a MySQL compatible, serverless database platform powered by Vitess, 3 databases for free with 10GB storage, 100 Million rows read/mo per database, and 10 Million rows written/mo per database.<br>
<a href="https://texterify.com/">https://texterify.com/</a> - Free for a single user<br>
<a href="#translation-management">#translation-management</a> - <br>
<a href="https://smalldev.tools/">https://smalldev.tools/</a> - A free tool for developers that allows you to Encode/Decode various formats, Minify HTML/CSS/Javascript, Beautify, Generate Fake/Testing real like dataset in JSON/CSV & multiple other formats and many more features. With a delightful interface.<br>
<a href="https://asayer.io/pricing.html) — Hosted version of openreplay, an open-source session replay (alternative to FullStory and LogRocket">https://asayer.io/pricing.html) — Hosted version of openreplay, an open-source session replay (alternative to FullStory and LogRocket</a> - Hosted version of openreplay, an open-source session replay (alternative to FullStory and LogRocket). Free 1k sessions/month with 14 days retention<br>
<a href="https://github.com/marketplace/testspace-com">https://github.com/marketplace/testspace-com</a> - Dashboard for publishing automated test results and a Framework for implementing manual tests as code using GitHub. [Free for Open Source](https://github.com/marketplace/testspace-com).<br>
<a href="https://discord.com/">https://discord.com/</a> - Chat with public/private rooms. Markdown text, voice, video, and screen sharing capabilities. Free for unlimited users.<br>
<a href="https://telegram.org/">https://telegram.org/</a> - Telegram is for everyone who wants fast and reliable messaging and calls. Business users and small teams may like the large groups, usernames, desktop apps and powerful file sharing options.<br>
<a href="https://github.com/marketplace/testspace-com">https://github.com/marketplace/testspace-com</a> - A Dashboard for publishing automated test results and a Framework for implementing manual tests as code using GitHub. The service is [free for Open Source](https://github.com/marketplace/testspace-com) accounts for 450 results per month.<br>
<a href="https://www.antideo.com">https://www.antideo.com</a> - 10 API requests per hour for email verification, IP and phone number validation in free tier. No Credit Cards required.<br>
<a href="https://eva.pingutil.com">https://eva.pingutil.com</a> - — Verify 5 million emails per day for free using REST API. No sign-ups required.<br>
<a href="https://quickemailverification.com">https://quickemailverification.com</a> - Verify 100 emails daily for free on a free tier along with other free APIs like DEA Detector, DNS Lookup, SPF Detector and more.<br>
<a href="https://hottempmail.com/">https://hottempmail.com/</a> - Unlimited free temp email or disposable temporary email addresses. Autoexpires in one day.<br>
<a href="https://temp-mail.org">https://temp-mail.org</a> - Temporary, secure, anonymous, free, disposable email address with REST API for fetching 100 emails from its disposable mailbox per day for free.<br>
<a href="https://mojoauth.com/">https://mojoauth.com/</a> - MojoAuth makes it easy to implement Passwordless on your web, mobile or any application in minutes.<br>
<a href="https://eva.pingutil.com">https://eva.pingutil.com</a> - Verify 5 million emails per day for free using REST API. No sign-ups required.<br>
<a href="https://lean20.com">https://lean20.com</a> - Public status pages for incident reporting. 100% free.<br>
<a href="https://lean20.com/product/status/">https://lean20.com/product/status/</a> - Public status pages for incident reporting. 100% free.<br>
<a href="https://mojoauth.com/">https://mojoauth.com/</a> - MojoAuth makes it easy to implement Passwordless authentication on your web, mobile or any application in minutes.<br>
<a href="https://viezly.com/">https://viezly.com/</a> - Enhanced code review tool for easier code reading and navigation. Free for Open Source and free for personal usage.<br>
<a href="https://www.geoapify.com/">https://www.geoapify.com/</a> - Vector and raster map tiles, geocoding, places, routing, isolines APIs. 3000 free requests / day.<br>
<a href="https://gitdailies.com">https://gitdailies.com</a> - Daily reports of your team's Commit and Pull Request activity on GitHub. Includes Push visualizer, peer recognition system, custom alert builder. Free tier has unlimited users, 3 repos, 3 alert configs.<br>
<a href="https://emailoctopus.com">https://emailoctopus.com</a> - Up to 2,500 subscribers and 10,000 emails per month free<br>
<a href="https://node.new">https://node.new</a> - Online/Cloud Code IDE to create, edit, & deploy fullstack apps. Support any popular NodeJs based frontend & backend frameworks. Shortlink to create new project: [https://node.new](https://node.new).<br>
<a href="https://www.molasses.app">https://www.molasses.app</a> - Release features with confidence; manage feature flags across web, mobile, and server side applications. Use our hosted API, deploy to your own private cloud, or run on-premise<br>
<a href="https://icon.horse">https://icon.horse</a> - – Get the highest resolution favicon for any website from our simple API.<br>
<a href="https://uploadcare.com/hub/developers/">https://uploadcare.com/hub/developers/</a> - Uploadcare provides media pipeline with ultimate toolkit based on cutting-edge algorithms. All features are available for developers absolutely for free: File Uploading API and UI, Image CDN and Origin Services, Adaptive Delivery and Smart Compression. Limit free tier has 3000 uploads, 3 GB traffic and 3 GB storage.<br>
<a href="https://degoo.com/) – AI based cloud storage with free up to 100 Gb, 5 devices, 500 Gb referral bonus (365 days account inactivity">https://degoo.com/) – AI based cloud storage with free up to 100 Gb, 5 devices, 500 Gb referral bonus (365 days account inactivity</a> - AI based cloud storage with free up to 100 Gb, 5 devices, 500 Gb referral bonus (365 days account inactivity).<br>
<a href="http://supportivekoala.com/">http://supportivekoala.com/</a> - Allows you to autogenerate images by your input via templates. Free plan allows you to create up to 100 images per week.<br>
<a href="http://cloud.yugabyte.com">http://cloud.yugabyte.com</a> - YugabyteDB is a distributed SQL database compatible with PostgresSQL. The cloud free tier is a 2 vCPU, 4GB RAM, 10GB Disk.<br>
<a href="https://www.fontshare.com/">https://www.fontshare.com/</a> - is a free fonts service. It’s a growing collection of professional grade fonts that are 100% free for personal and commercial use.<br>
<a href="https://graphcdn.io/">https://graphcdn.io/</a> - Scale, inspect & protect your GraphQL API. 5m requests per month for free.<br>
<a href="https://logflare.app/">https://logflare.app/</a> - Free for upto 12,960,000 enteries per app per month, 3 days retention<br>
<a href="https://economize.cloud">https://economize.cloud</a> - Economize helps demystify cloud infrastructure costs by organizing cloud resources, optimize and report the same. Free for up to $5000 spends on Google Cloud Platform every month.<br>
<a href="https://www.framer.com/">https://www.framer.com/</a> - Framer helps you iterate and animate interface ideas for your next app, website, or product—starting with powerful layouts. For anyone validating Framer as a professional prototyping tool: unlimited viewers, up to 2 editors, up to 3 projects.<br>
<a href="https://www.integromat.com">https://www.integromat.com</a> - Workflow automation tool which lets you connect apps and automate workflows using UI, it supports many apps and most popular APIs. Free for public GitHub repositories, and free tier with 100 Mb, 1000 Operations and 15 minutes of minimum interval.<br>
<a href="#cloud-management-solutions">#cloud-management-solutions</a> - solutions](#cloud-management-solutions)<br>
<a href="https://www.brainboard.co">https://www.brainboard.co</a> - visually build and manage cloud infrastructures from end-to-end:<br>
<a href="#table-of-contents">#table-of-contents</a> - top](#table-of-contents)**<br>
<a href="https://dynapictures.com">https://dynapictures.com</a> - Design automation tool which lets you dynamically generate images from the template. Change colors, texts, logos and images on the fly.<br>
<a href="https://dynapictures.com">https://dynapictures.com</a> - Design automation tool which lets you dynamically generate images over REST API. Change colors, texts, logos and images on the fly.<br>
<a href="https://www.terraform.io/">https://www.terraform.io/</a> - Terraform Cloud. Free remote state management and team collaboration for teams up to 5 users.<br>
<a href="https://www.brainboard.co">https://www.brainboard.co</a> - Collaborative solution to visually build and manage cloud infrastructures from end-to-end.<br>
<a href="https://themeselection.com/">https://themeselection.com/</a> - Selected high quality, modern design, professional and easy-to-use Free Admin Dashboard Template,<br>
<a href="https://dynapictures.com">https://dynapictures.com</a> - Design automation tool which lets you dynamically generate images over REST API. Change colors, texts, logos and images on the fly. Free plan includes 30 generated images per month and 3 image templates.<br>
<a href="https://meercode.io/">https://meercode.io/</a> - Meercode is the ultimate monitoring dashboard for your CI/CD builds.<br>
<a href="https://meercode.io/">https://meercode.io/</a> - Meercode is the ultimate monitoring dashboard for your CI/CD builds. Free for open-source and 1 private repository.<br>
<a href="https://www.markup.io/">https://www.markup.io/</a> - MarkUp lets you collect feedback directly on top of your websites, PDFs and images.<br>
<a href="https://neptune.ai/">https://neptune.ai/</a> - Log, store, display, organize, compare and query all your MLOps metadata. Free for individuals: 1 member, 100 GB of metadata storage, 200h of monitoring/month<br>
<a href="https://sawolabs.com/">https://sawolabs.com/</a> - Simplify login and improve user experience by integrating passwordless authentication in your app. Circumvent your bounce rates by 30%.<br>
<a href="https://instatus.com">https://instatus.com</a> - Get a beautiful status page in 10 seconds. Free forever with unlimited subs and unlimited teams.<br>
<a href="https://backlight.dev/">https://backlight.dev/</a> - With collaboration between developers and designers at heart, Backlight is a very complete coding platform where teams build, document, publish, scale and maintain Design Systems.<br>
<a href="https://www.mockplus.com/idoc">https://www.mockplus.com/idoc</a> - - Mockplus iDoc is a powerful design collaboration & handoff tool. Free Plan includes 3 users and 5 projects with all features available.<br>
<a href="https://webcomponents.dev/">https://webcomponents.dev/</a> - Code components in isolation, visualize them in stories, test them and publish them on npm.<br>
<a href="https://webcomponents.dev/">https://webcomponents.dev/</a> - In-browser IDE to code web components in isolation with 58 templates available, supporting stories and tests.<br>
<a href="https://sawolabs.com/">https://sawolabs.com/</a> - Simplify login and improve user experience by integrating passwordless authentication in your app. 5000 free authentications per month.<br>
<a href="https://backlight.dev/">https://backlight.dev/</a> - With collaboration between developers and designers at heart, Backlight is a very complete coding platform where teams build, document, publish, scale and maintain Design Systems.Free plan allows up to 3 editors working on 1 design system with unlimited viewers.<br>
<a href="https://duply.co">https://duply.co</a> - Create dynamic images from API & URL, design template once and reuse it. Free tier offers 70 images/month creation from API & URL and Up to 100 through Form.<br>
<a href="https://hasura.io/">https://hasura.io/</a> - Hasura extends your existing databases wherever it is hosted and provides an instant GraphQL API that can be securely accessed for web, mobile, and data integration workloads.<br>
<a href="https://hasura.io/">https://hasura.io/</a> - Hasura extends your existing databases wherever it is hosted and provides an instant GraphQL API that can be securely accessed for web, mobile, and data integration workloads. Free for 1GB/month of data pass-through.<br>
<a href="https://www.tigergraph.com/cloud/) — Managed native Graph DBMS / analytics platform with a SQL-like graph query language and a REST API. 1 TG.Free instance on AWS (4 vCPU, 7.5 GB memory, 50 GB disk) or on GCP(2 vCPU, 8 GB memory, 128 GB disk">https://www.tigergraph.com/cloud/) — Managed native Graph DBMS / analytics platform with a SQL-like graph query language and a REST API. 1 TG.Free instance on AWS (4 vCPU, 7.5 GB memory, 50 GB disk) or on GCP(2 vCPU, 8 GB memory, 128 GB disk</a> - — Managed native Graph DBMS / analytics platform with a SQL-like graph query language and a REST API. 1 TG.Free instance on AWS (4 vCPU, 7.5 GB memory, 50 GB disk) or on GCP(2 vCPU, 8 GB memory, 128 GB disk). Free instance sleeps after 1 hour of inactivity.<br>
<a href="https://neo4j.com/cloud/aura/) — Managed native Graph DBMS / analytics platform with a Cypher query language and a REST API. Limits on graph size (50k nodes, 175k relationships">https://neo4j.com/cloud/aura/) — Managed native Graph DBMS / analytics platform with a Cypher query language and a REST API. Limits on graph size (50k nodes, 175k relationships</a> - — Managed native Graph DBMS / analytics platform with a Cypher query language and a REST API. Limits on graph size (50k nodes, 175k relationships).<br>
<a href="https://cloud.dgraph.io/pricing?type=free">https://cloud.dgraph.io/pricing?type=free</a> - — Managed native Graph DBMS with a GraphQL API. Limited to 1 MB data trasnfer per day.<br>
<a href="https://js.org">https://js.org</a> - Free js.org domains for GitHub Pages<br>
<a href="https://syagent.com/">https://syagent.com/</a> - Non commercial free server monitoring service, alerts and metrics.<br>
<a href="https://logtail.com/">https://logtail.com/</a> - ClickHouse-based SQL-compatible log management. Free up to 1 GB per month, 3 days retention.<br>
<a href="https://huggingface.co">https://huggingface.co</a> - Build, train and deploy NLP models for Pytorch, TensorFlow, and JAX. Free up to 30k input characters/mo.<br>
<a href="https://railway.app">https://railway.app</a> - Railway is an infrastructure platform where you can provision infrastructure, develop with that infrastructure locally, and then deploy to the cloud. 1GB Disk, 512 MB RAM, limited to $5 of usage monthly available for free.<br>
<a href="https://dkimvalidator.com/">https://dkimvalidator.com/</a> - Test if email's dns/spf/dkim/dmarc settings are correct, free service by roundsphere.com<br>
<a href="https://counter.dev">https://counter.dev</a> - Web analytics made simple and therefore privacy friendly. Free or pay what you want by donation.<br>
<a href="https://craftmypdf.com">https://craftmypdf.com</a> - Auto-Generate PDF documents from reusable templates with a drop-and-drop editor and a simple API. Free plan comes with 100 PDFs/month and 3 templates.<br>
<a href="https://tailscale.com/">https://tailscale.com/</a> - Zero config VPN. Installs on any device, manages firewall rules. Run on MacOS, iOS, Windows, Linux, and Android. Free plan for personal use with 20 devices.<br>
<a href="https://tailscale.com/">https://tailscale.com/</a> - Zero config VPN, using the open source WireGuard protocol. Installs on MacOS, iOS, Windows, Linux, and Android devices. Free plan for personal use with 20 devices.<br>
<a href="https://analytics.statvoo.com/">https://analytics.statvoo.com/</a> - — Forever FREE Customer Analytics for ALL your websites, with Unlimited Events per month<br>
<a href="https://carbon.now.sh">https://carbon.now.sh</a> - create and share code snippet in an aesthetic screenshot-like image format. Usually used to aesthetically share/show-off code snippet on Twitter or blog posts.<br>
<a href="https://github.com/localtunnel/localtunnel">https://github.com/localtunnel/localtunnel</a> - Easily share a web service on your local development machine to a public internet URL without messing with DNS and firewall settings. Similar to Ngrok. In addition to the free hosted version, it is also [open source](https://github.com/localtunnel/localtunnel).<br>
<a href="https://github.com/localtunnel/localtunnel">https://github.com/localtunnel/localtunnel</a> - Easily share a web service on your local development machine to a public internet URL without messing with DNS and firewall settings. Similar to Ngrok. In addition to the free hosted version, it is also [open source](https://github.com/localtunnel/localtunnel).<br>
<a href="https://quicktype.io/">https://quicktype.io/</a> - Quickly auto generate models/class/type/interface and serializers from JSON, schema, and GraphQL for working with data quickly & safely in any programming language. Convert JSON into gorgeous, typesafe code in any language.<br>
<a href="https://github.com/julien-lafont/Mocky">https://github.com/julien-lafont/Mocky</a> - A simple web app to generate custom HTTP responses for mocking HTTP request. Also available as [open source](https://github.com/julien-lafont/Mocky).<br>
<a href="https://ray.so/">https://ray.so/</a> - Create beautiful images of your code snippets.<br>
<a href="https://about.ipaddress.sh/">https://about.ipaddress.sh/</a> - Simple service to get public IP address in different [formats](https://about.ipaddress.sh/).<br>
<a href="https://freeflarum.com/) - Community powered free Flarum hosting for up to 250 users (donate to remove watermark from footer">https://freeflarum.com/) - Community powered free Flarum hosting for up to 250 users (donate to remove watermark from footer</a> - Community powered free Flarum hosting for up to 250 users (donate to remove watermark from footer).<br>
<a href="https://combinatronics.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/master/index.html">https://combinatronics.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/master/index.html</a> - Convert your Github hosted assets (images, CSS, JS, etc.) into CDN assets. Can even render HTML files, for [example from this repo](https://combinatronics.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/master/index.html). Similar to rawgit.com and raw.githack.com.<br>
<a href="https://ui-avatars.com/">https://ui-avatars.com/</a> - - Generate avatars with initials from names. Which the urls can be directly hotlinked in your web/app. Support config parameters via the url.<br>
<a href="https://pravatar.cc/">https://pravatar.cc/</a> - Generate random/placeholder fake avatar, which url can be directly hotlinked in your web/app.<br>
<a href="https://developers.cloudflare.com/1.1.1.1/encrypted-dns/dns-over-https/make-api-requests">https://developers.cloudflare.com/1.1.1.1/encrypted-dns/dns-over-https/make-api-requests</a> - Free public DNS Resolver which is fast and secure (encrypt your DNS query), provided by CloudFlare. Useful to bypass your internet provider's DNS blocking, prevent DNS query spying, and [to block adult & malware content](https://developers.cloudflare.com/1.1.1.1/1.1.1.1-for-families). Can also be used [via API](https://developers.cloudflare.com/1.1.1.1/encrypted-dns/dns-over-https/make-api-requests). Note: Just a DNS resolver, not a DNS hoster.<br>
<a href="https://www.napkin.io/">https://www.napkin.io/</a> - FaaS with 1Gb of memory, a default timeout of 15 seconds and 1,000,000 free API calls/month.<br>
<a href="https://vatcheckapi.com">https://vatcheckapi.com</a> - Simple and free VAT number validation API. 500 free requests per month.<br>
<a href="https://fleep.io/">https://fleep.io/</a> - Fleep an alternative to Slack. It has a free plan for small teams with full message history, unlimited 1:1 conversations, 1 group conversation and 1 GB file storage.<br>
<a href="https://chanty.com/) — Chanty is another alternative to Slack. It has a free forever plan for small teams (up to 10">https://chanty.com/) — Chanty is another alternative to Slack. It has a free forever plan for small teams (up to 10</a> - Chanty is another alternative to Slack. It has a free forever plan for small teams (up to 10) with unlimited public and private conversations, searchable history, unlimited 1:1 audio calls, unlimited voice messages, 10 integrations and 20 GB storage per team.<br>
<a href="https://track.toggl.com/">https://track.toggl.com/</a> - — Task management and tracking app with a free plan provides seamless time tracking and reporting designed with freelancers in mind. It has unlimited tracking records, projects, clients, tags, reporting and more.<br>
<a href="https://plan.toggl.com/">https://plan.toggl.com/</a> - — Task planning tool that has a free plan for solo developers with unlimited tasks, milestones and timelines.<br>
<a href="https://hybiscus.dev/">https://hybiscus.dev/</a> - Build pdf reports using a simple declarative API. Free tier includes upto 100 single page reports per month with the ability to customise color pallet and fonts.<br>
<a href="https://docs.travis-ci.com/user/billing-faq/#what-if-i-am-building-open-source">https://docs.travis-ci.com/user/billing-faq/#what-if-i-am-building-open-source</a> - [Free for public GitHub repositories](https://docs.travis-ci.com/user/billing-faq/#what-if-i-am-building-open-source)<br>
<a href="https://platform9.com/">https://platform9.com/</a> - Managed Kubernetes plane. Free plan offers management capabilities up to 3 clusters & 20 nodes. Note: you must provide cluster infrastructure by yourself.<br>
<a href="https://www.cockroachlabs.com/docs/cockroachcloud/serverless-faqs.html#what-are-the-usage-limits-of-cockroachdb-serverless-beta)">https://www.cockroachlabs.com/docs/cockroachcloud/serverless-faqs.html#what-are-the-usage-limits-of-cockroachdb-serverless-beta)</a> - Free CockroachDB up to 5GB and 1vCPU (limited [request units](https://www.cockroachlabs.com/docs/cockroachcloud/serverless-faqs.html#what-are-the-usage-limits-of-cockroachdb-serverless-beta))<br>
<a href="https://about.ipaddress.sh/">https://about.ipaddress.sh/</a> - Simple service to get public IP address in different [formats](https://about.ipaddress.sh/).<br>
<a href="https://cloud.dgraph.io/pricing?type=free">https://cloud.dgraph.io/pricing?type=free</a> - — Managed native Graph DBMS with a GraphQL API. Limited to 1 MB data trasnfer per day.<br>
<a href="https://plan.toggl.com/">https://plan.toggl.com/</a> - Provides 2 free productivity tools. [Toggl Track](https://track.toggl.com/) for time management and tracking app with a free plan provides seamless time tracking and reporting designed for freelancers in mind. It has unlimited tracking records, projects, clients, tags, reporting and more. And [Toggl Plan](https://plan.toggl.com/) for task planning that comes with a free plan for solo developers with unlimited tasks, milestones and timelines.<br>
<a href="https://counter.dev">https://counter.dev</a> - Web analytics made simple and therefore privacy friendly. Free or pay what you want by donation.<br>
<a href="https://toggl.com/plan/">https://toggl.com/plan/</a> - Provides 2 free productivity tools. [Toggl Track](https://toggl.com/track/) for time management and tracking app with a free plan provides seamless time tracking and reporting designed for freelancers in mind. It has unlimited tracking records, projects, clients, tags, reporting and more. And [Toggl Plan](https://toggl.com/plan/) for task planning that comes with a free plan for solo developers with unlimited tasks, milestones and timelines.<br>
<a href="https://vvv.space/">https://vvv.space/</a> - Free links manager with private/public spaces, includes slack and google docs integration and chrome plugin.<br>
<a href="https://numlookupapi.com">https://numlookupapi.com</a> - Free phone number validation API - 100k free requests / month.<br>
<a href="https://pofile.net/free-po-editor">https://pofile.net/free-po-editor</a> - editor](https://pofile.net/free-po-editor) — Free for everybody<br>
<a href="https://parsio.io) — Free email parser (Forward email, extract the data, send it to your server">https://parsio.io) — Free email parser (Forward email, extract the data, send it to your server</a> - Free email parser (Forward email, extract the data, send it to your server)<br>
<a href="https://flowdash.com/">https://flowdash.com/</a> - Automate business workflows. Free tier for up to 3 users, 1000 tasks, and 3 workflows.<br>
<a href="https://exportsdk.com">https://exportsdk.com</a> - - PDF generator API with drag and drop template editor that also provides an SDK and no-code integrations. Free plan comes with 250 pages per month, unlimited users and three templates.<br>
<a href="https://www.zenrows.com/">https://www.zenrows.com/</a> - Web Scraping API & proxy server that bypasses any anti-bot solution while offering javascript rendering, rotating proxies, and geotargeting. Free tier of 1000 API calls.<br>
<a href="https://hyperforms.app/">https://hyperforms.app/</a> - Create form to email and more in seconds and without backend code. The Personal account gives you up to 50 form submissions per month for free.<br>
<a href="https://www.netdata.cloud/">https://www.netdata.cloud/</a> - Real-time performance monitoring, done right! Netdata is high-fidelity infrastructure monitoring and troubleshooting.<br>
<a href="https://www.netdata.cloud/">https://www.netdata.cloud/</a> - Netdata is an open source tool designed to collect real-time metrics.Great fast growing product. It can also be found in github!<br>
<a href="https://www.magicpattern.design/tools/blob-generator">https://www.magicpattern.design/tools/blob-generator</a> - — Create random organic-shaped blobs with solid colors, linear/radial gradients, and pattern fills.<br>
<a href="https://www.magicpattern.design/tools/gradient-generator">https://www.magicpattern.design/tools/gradient-generator</a> - Generator](https://www.magicpattern.design/tools/gradient-generator) — Create, save & share beautiful CSS linear, radial, and conic gradients for your backgrounds.<br>
<a href="https://www.magicpattern.design/tools">https://www.magicpattern.design/tools</a> - A collection of CSS & SVG background generators & tools for gradients, patterns, and blobs.<br>
<a href="https://shortcut.com/">https://shortcut.com/</a> - Project management platform. Free for up to 10 users forever.<br>
<a href="https://www.prefect.io/cloud/">https://www.prefect.io/cloud/</a> - A complete platform for dataflow automation. All plans include 20,000 free runs every month. That's enough to power ETL for most small businesses.<br>
<a href="https://selectel.com/services/dns/">https://selectel.com/services/dns/</a> - Free DNS hosting with unlimited records, anycast<br>
<a href="https://mybinder.org/">https://mybinder.org/</a> - Turn a Git repo into a collection of interactive notebooks. It is a free, public service.<br>
<a href="https://www.icedrive.net/">https://www.icedrive.net/</a> - Simple cloud storage service. 10 GB free storage<br>
<a href="https://www.sync.com/">https://www.sync.com/</a> - End-to-End cloud storage service. 5 GB free storage<br>
<a href="https://www.pcloud.com/">https://www.pcloud.com/</a> - Cloud storage service. Up to 10 GB free storage<br>
<a href="https://ipinfo.io/) — Fast, accurate, and free (up to 50k/month">https://ipinfo.io/) — Fast, accurate, and free (up to 50k/month</a> - Fast, accurate, and free (up to 50k/month) IP address data API. Offers APIs with details on geolocation, companies, carriers, IP ranges, domains, abuse contacts, and more. All paid APIs can be trialed for free.<br>
<a href="https://www.alwaysdata.com/">https://www.alwaysdata.com/</a> - 1000 MB free web hosting with support for MySQL, PostgreSQL, CouchDB, MongoDB, PHP, Python, Ruby, Node.js, Elixir, Java, Deno, custom web servers, access via FTP, WebDAV and SSH; mailbox, mailing list and app installer included.<br>
<a href="https://www.heliohost.org) — Community powered free hosting for everyone(Unable to register at this time">https://www.heliohost.org) — Community powered free hosting for everyone(Unable to register at this time</a> - Community powered free hosting for everyone(Unable to register at this time).<br>
<a href="https://www.datastax.com/products/datastax-astra/pricing)(using free $25/mo credit">https://www.datastax.com/products/datastax-astra/pricing)(using free $25/mo credit</a> - Cloud Native Cassandra as a Service with [80GB free tier](https://www.datastax.com/products/datastax-astra/pricing)(using free $25/mo credit)<br>
<a href="https://valine.js.org/">https://valine.js.org/</a> - a fast, simple & efficient Leancloud based no back end comment system.<br>
<a href="https://ip-fast.com/">https://ip-fast.com/</a> - Find out your IP Address and related detailed information using the free, fastest and simple lookup tool.<br>
<a href="https://www.datocms.com/">https://www.datocms.com/</a> - Offers free tier for small projects. DatoCMS is a GraphQL based CMS. On the lower tier you have 100k/month calls.<br>
<a href="https://ipinfo.io/) — Fast, accurate, and free (up to 100k/month">https://ipinfo.io/) — Fast, accurate, and free (up to 100k/month</a> - Fast, accurate, and free (up to 100k/month) IP address data API. Offers APIs with details on geolocation, companies, carriers, IP ranges, domains, abuse contacts, and more. All paid APIs can be trialed for free.<br>
<a href="https://www.alwaysdata.com/">https://www.alwaysdata.com/</a> - 100 MB free web hosting with support for MySQL, PostgreSQL, CouchDB, MongoDB, PHP, Python, Ruby, Node.js, Elixir, Java, Deno, custom web servers, access via FTP, WebDAV and SSH; mailbox, mailing list and app installer included.<br>
<a href="https://www.heliohost.org">https://www.heliohost.org</a> - Community powered free hosting for everyone.<br>
<a href="https://commons.host/) - Static web hosting and CDN.100% free and open source software (FOSS). With a commercially sustainable software as a service (SaaS">https://commons.host/) - Static web hosting and CDN.100% free and open source software (FOSS). With a commercially sustainable software as a service (SaaS</a> - Static web hosting and CDN.100% free and open source software (FOSS). With a commercially sustainable software as a service (SaaS) to fund R&D.<br>
<a href="https://www.datastax.com/products/datastax-astra/pricing">https://www.datastax.com/products/datastax-astra/pricing</a> - Cloud Native Cassandra as a Service with [40GB free tier](https://www.datastax.com/products/datastax-astra/pricing)<br>
<a href="https://ipinfo.io/) — Fast, accurate, and free (up to 50k/month">https://ipinfo.io/) — Fast, accurate, and free (up to 50k/month</a> - Fast, accurate, and free (up to 50k/month) IP address data API. Offers APIs with details on geolocation, companies, carriers, IP ranges, domains, abuse contacts, and more. All paid APIs can be trialed for free.<br>
<a href="https://www.alwaysdata.com/">https://www.alwaysdata.com/</a> - 1000 MB free web hosting with support for MySQL, PostgreSQL, CouchDB, MongoDB, PHP, Python, Ruby, Node.js, Elixir, Java, Deno, custom web servers, access via FTP, WebDAV and SSH; mailbox, mailing list and app installer included.<br>
<a href="https://www.datastax.com/products/datastax-astra/pricing">https://www.datastax.com/products/datastax-astra/pricing</a> - Cloud Native Cassandra as a Service with [80GB free tier](https://www.datastax.com/products/datastax-astra/pricing)<br>
<a href="https://www.codepng.app">https://www.codepng.app</a> - Create awesome snapshots from your source code that you can share on social media.<br>
<a href="https://bit.io">https://bit.io</a> - PostgreSQL managed database service. Unlimited repos, 10GB storage, 10M queried rows/month.<br>
<a href="https://www.nsupdate.info/">https://www.nsupdate.info/</a> - Free and open-source Dynamic DNS service<br>
<a href="http://maps.stamen.com/">http://maps.stamen.com/</a> - Free map tiles and tile hosting.<br>
<a href="https://dribbble.com/">https://dribbble.com/</a> - Unique design inspiration, generally not from real applications.<br>
<a href="https://mobbin.design/">https://mobbin.design/</a> - Save hours of UI & UX research with our library of 50,000+ fully searchable mobile app screenshots.<br>
<a href="https://www.mobile-patterns.com/) - A design inspirational library featuring finest UI UX Patterns (iOS and Android">https://www.mobile-patterns.com/) - A design inspirational library featuring finest UI UX Patterns (iOS and Android</a> - - A design inspirational library featuring finest UI UX Patterns (iOS and Android) for designers, developers, and product makers to reference.<br>
<a href="https://scrnshts.club/">https://scrnshts.club/</a> - A hand-picked collection of the finest app store design screenshots<br>
<a href="https://uigarage.net/">https://uigarage.net/</a> - - Daily UI inspiration & patterns for designers, developers to find inspiration, tools and the best resources for your project.<br>
<a href="https://www.alwaysdata.com/">https://www.alwaysdata.com/</a> - 100 MB free web hosting with support for MySQL, PostgreSQL, CouchDB, MongoDB, PHP, Python, Ruby, Node.js, Elixir, Java, Deno, custom web servers, access via FTP, WebDAV and SSH; mailbox, mailing list and app installer included.<br>
<a href="https://emailtemporanee.com/) - Easy to use free Unlimited disposable temporary email addresses (temp email">https://emailtemporanee.com/) - Easy to use free Unlimited disposable temporary email addresses (temp email</a> - - Easy to use free Unlimited disposable temporary email addresses (temp email). Autoexpires even you can set it day.<br>
<a href="https://qoddi.com">https://qoddi.com</a> - PaaS service similar to Heroku with a developer-centric approach and all inclusive features. Free tier for static assets, staging and developer apps.<br>
<a href="https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev">https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev</a> - the result of Pull Requests, reviews, ideas and work done by 1000+ people. You too can help by sending [Pull Requests](https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev) to add more services or by remove ones whose offerings have changed or been retired.<br>
<a href="https://www.twicpics.com">https://www.twicpics.com</a> - Responsive images as a service. It provides an image CDN, a media processing API and frontend library to automate image optimization. The service is free up to 3GB trafic/month.<br>
<a href="https://www.twicpics.com">https://www.twicpics.com</a> - Responsive images as a service. It provides an image CDN, a media processing API and frontend library to automate image optimization. The service is free up to 3GB trafic/month.<br>
<a href="https://www.twicpics.com">https://www.twicpics.com</a> - Responsive images as a service. It provides an image CDN, a media processing API and frontend library to automate image optimization. The service is free up to 3GB trafic/month.<br>
<a href="https://www.gooddata.com/">https://www.gooddata.com/</a> - Data as a Service - Create interactive and insightful dashboards. Free tier comes with 5 workspaces and 100 MB/workspace.<br>
<a href="https://lottiefiles.com/">https://lottiefiles.com/</a> - The world’s largest online platform for the world’s smallest animation format for designers, developers, and more. Access Lottie animation tools and plugins for Android, iOS, and Web.<br>
<a href="https://coolors.co/">https://coolors.co/</a> - Color palette generator. Free.<br>
<a href="#design-inspiration">#design-inspiration</a> - <br>
<a href="https://www.awwwards.com/) - [Top websites] A showcases of all the best designed websites (voted on by designers">https://www.awwwards.com/) - [Top websites] A showcases of all the best designed websites (voted on by designers</a> - [Top websites] A showcases of all the best designed websites (voted on by designers).<br>
<a href="https://www.behance.net/">https://www.behance.net/</a> - [Desing showcase] A place where designers showcase their work. Filterable with categories for UI/UX projects.<br>
<a href="https://dribbble.com/">https://dribbble.com/</a> - [Design showcase] Unique design inspiration, generally not from real applications.<br>
<a href="https://mobbin.design/">https://mobbin.design/</a> - [Mobile screenshots] Save hours of UI & UX research with our library of 50,000+ fully searchable mobile app screenshots.<br>
<a href="https://www.mobile-patterns.com/) - [Mobile screenshots] A design inspirational library featuring finest UI UX Patterns (iOS and Android">https://www.mobile-patterns.com/) - [Mobile screenshots] A design inspirational library featuring finest UI UX Patterns (iOS and Android</a> - - [Mobile screenshots] A design inspirational library featuring finest UI UX Patterns (iOS and Android) for designers, developers, and product makers to reference.<br>
<a href="https://screenlane.com/">https://screenlane.com/</a> - [Mobile screenshots] Get inspired and keep up with the latest web & mobile app UI design trends. Filterable by pattern and app.<br>
<a href="https://scrnshts.club/">https://scrnshts.club/</a> - [Mobile screenshots] A hand-picked collection of the finest app store design screenshots.<br>
<a href="https://uigarage.net/">https://uigarage.net/</a> - - [Mobile and web screenshots] Daily UI inspiration & patterns for designers, developers to find inspiration, tools and the best resources for your project.<br>
<a href="#table-of-contents">#table-of-contents</a> - top](#table-of-contents)**<br>
<a href="https://render.com">https://render.com</a> - Unified cloud to build and run apps and sites with free SSL, a global CDN, private networks, auto-deploys from Git, and completely free plans for web services, databases, and static web pages.<br>
<a href="https://www.lambdatest.com/open-source-cross-browser-testing-tool">https://www.lambdatest.com/open-source-cross-browser-testing-tool</a> - Manual, visual, screenshot and automated browser testing on selenium and cypress, [free for Open Source](https://www.lambdatest.com/open-source-cross-browser-testing-tool)<br>
<a href="https://meetslack.com">https://meetslack.com</a> - Slack](https://meetslack.com) - Start Google Meetings directly from Slack by using /meet in any channel, group or DM. Free without any limitations.<br>
<a href="https://www.jitbit.com/imgen/">https://www.jitbit.com/imgen/</a> - Free unlimited social cover image generation API, no watermark<br>
<a href="https://squadcast.com">https://squadcast.com</a> - Squadcast is an end-to-end incident management software that's designed to help you promote SRE best practices. Free forever plan available for upto 10 users.<br>
<a href="https://www.goatcounter.com/) — GoatCounter is an open source web analytics platform available as a hosted service (free for non-commercial use">https://www.goatcounter.com/) — GoatCounter is an open source web analytics platform available as a hosted service (free for non-commercial use</a> - GoatCounter is an open source web analytics platform available as a hosted service (free for non-commercial use) or self-hosted app. It aims to offer easy to use and meaningful privacy-friendly web analytics as an alternative to Google Analytics or Matomo. Free tier is for non-commerical use and includes unlimited number of sites, 6 months of data retention, and 100k pageviews/month.<br>
<a href="https://www.expensify.com/">https://www.expensify.com/</a> - Expense reporting, free personal reporting approval workflow<br>
<a href="https://keen.io/">https://keen.io/</a> - Custom Analytics for data collection, analysis and visualization. 50,000 events/month free<br>
<a href="https://metrica.yandex.com/">https://metrica.yandex.com/</a> - Unlimited free analytics<br>
<a href="https://mixpanel.com/">https://mixpanel.com/</a> - 100,000 monthly tracked users, unlimited data history and seats, US or EU data residency<br>
<a href="https://cognalys.com/">https://cognalys.com/</a> - Freemium mobile number verification through an innovative and reliable method than using SMS gateway. Free 10 tries and 15 verifications/day<br>
<a href="https://numverify.com/">https://numverify.com/</a> - Global phone number validation and lookup JSON API. 250 API requests/month<br>
<a href="https://veriphone.io/">https://veriphone.io/</a> - Global phone number verification in a free, fast, reliable JSON API. 1000 requests/month<br>
<a href="https://currencyapi.net/">https://currencyapi.net/</a> - Live Currency Rates for Physical and Crypto currencies, delivered in JSON and XML. Free tier offers 1,250 API requests/month.<br>
<a href="https://currencylayer.com/">https://currencylayer.com/</a> - Reliable Exchange Rates and Currency Conversion for your Business, 1,000 API requests/month free<br>
<a href="https://www.fraudlabspro.com">https://www.fraudlabspro.com</a> - Help merchants to prevent payment fraud and chargebacks. Free Micro Plan available with 500 queries/month.<br>
<a href="https://mailpop.in">https://mailpop.in</a> - Get the most of your Stripe notifications with contextualized information.<br>
<a href="https://www.namiml.com/">https://www.namiml.com/</a> - - Complete platform for in-app purchases and subscriptions on iOS and Android, including no-code paywalls, CRM, and analytics. Free for all base features to run an IAP business.<br>
<a href="https://www.revenuecat.com/) — Hosted backend for in-app purchases and subscriptions (iOS and Android">https://www.revenuecat.com/) — Hosted backend for in-app purchases and subscriptions (iOS and Android</a> - Hosted backend for in-app purchases and subscriptions (iOS and Android). Free up to $10k/mo in tracked revenue.<br>
<a href="https://vatlayer.com/">https://vatlayer.com/</a> - Instant VAT number validation and EU VAT rates API, free 100 API requests/month<br>
<a href="https://freecurrencyapi.net/">https://freecurrencyapi.net/</a> - Free currency conversion and exchange rate data API. 10 requests/hour without an API key, 50 000 requests per month when you register for free.<br>
<a href="https://app.vagrantup.com">https://app.vagrantup.com</a> - - HashiCorp Vagrant Cloud. Vagrant box hosting.<br>
<a href="https://www.vagrantbox.es/">https://www.vagrantbox.es/</a> - An alternative public box index<br>
<a href="https://bearblog.dev/">https://bearblog.dev/</a> - Minimalist, and Markdown powered blog and website builder.<br>
<a href="https://dev.to/">https://dev.to/</a> - Where programmers share ideas and help each other grow.<br>
<a href="https://hashnode.com/">https://hashnode.com/</a> - Hassle-free Blogging Software for Developers!.<br>
<a href="https://medium.com/">https://medium.com/</a> - Get smarter about what matters to you.<br>
<a href="https://giscus.app/">https://giscus.app/</a> - A lightweight comments widget built arround GitHub Discussions.<br>
<a href="https://gitalk.github.io/">https://gitalk.github.io/</a> - A little comments widget built on GitHub Issues.<br>
<a href="https://js.org">https://js.org</a> - Free js.org subdomains for GitHub Pages for the JavaScript community.<br>
<a href="https://nic.ua/">https://nic.ua/</a> - Free pp.ua subdomains.<br>
<a href="https://freedns.afraid.org">https://freedns.afraid.org</a> - Free subdomains powered by the community and free DNS hosting. Until 5 free DNS records.<br>
<a href="https://education.github.com/pack">https://education.github.com/pack</a> - — Collection of free services for students. Registration required.<br>
<a href="https://is-a.dev">https://is-a.dev</a> - Free `*.is-a.dev` subdomain for developers.<br>
<a href="https://bitbucket.org/">https://bitbucket.org/</a> - Unlimited public and private Git repos for up to 5 users with Pipelines for CI/CD<br>
<a href="https://codeberg.page/">https://codeberg.page/</a> - Unlimited public and private Git repos for free and open-source projects. Static website hosting with [Codeberg Pages](https://codeberg.page/).<br>
<a href="https://www.gitea.com/">https://www.gitea.com/</a> - Unlimited public and private Git repos<br>
<a href="https://github.com/) — Unlimited public repositories and unlimited private repositories (with unlimited collaborators). Apart from this some other free services(there are much more but we list the main ones here">https://github.com/) — Unlimited public repositories and unlimited private repositories (with unlimited collaborators). Apart from this some other free services(there are much more but we list the main ones here</a> - Unlimited public repositories and unlimited private repositories (with unlimited collaborators). Apart from this some other free services(there are much more but we list the main ones here) provided are :<br>
<a href="https://www.deepcode.ai">https://www.deepcode.ai</a> - DeepCode finds bugs, security vulnerabilities, performance and API issues based on AI. DeepCode's speed of analysis allow us to analyse your code in real time and deliver results when you hit the save button in your IDE. Supported languages are Java, C/C++, JavaScript, Python, and TypeScript. Integrations with GitHub, BitBucket and GitLab. Free for open source and private repos, free up to 30 developers.<br>
<a href="https://unpkg.com/">https://unpkg.com/</a> - CDN for everything on npm<br>
<a href="https://glitch.com/">https://glitch.com/</a> - Free public hosting with features such as code sharing and real-time collaboration. Free plan has 1000 hours/month limit.<br>
<a href="https://www.heroku.com/">https://www.heroku.com/</a> - Host your apps in the cloud, free for single process apps<br>
<a href="https://neocities.org">https://neocities.org</a> - Static, 1 GB free storage with 200 GB Bandwidth.<br>
<a href="https://www.netlify.com/">https://www.netlify.com/</a> - Builds, deploy and hosts static site/app free for, 100 GB data and 100 GB/month bandwidth.<br>
<a href="https://sourceforge.net/">https://sourceforge.net/</a> - Find, Create and Publish Open Source software for free<br>
<a href="https://developers.cloudflare.com/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-apps/run-tunnel/trycloudflare">https://developers.cloudflare.com/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-apps/run-tunnel/trycloudflare</a> - — Create a tunnel from your server to a publically accessible, randomly-generated trycloudflare.com domain. No account required.<br>
<a href="https://developers.cloudflare.com/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-apps/run-tunnel/trycloudflare">https://developers.cloudflare.com/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-apps/run-tunnel/trycloudflare</a> - — Create a tunnel from your server to a publically accessible, randomly-generated trycloudflare.com domain. No account required.<br>
<a href="https://workers.cloudflare.com/">https://workers.cloudflare.com/</a> - — Deploy serverless code for free on Cloudflare's global network. 100,000 free requests per day with a workers.dev subdomain.<br>
<a href="stun:global.stun.twilio.com:3478?transport=udp">stun:global.stun.twilio.com:3478?transport=udp</a> - -- [stun:global.stun.twilio.com:3478?transport=udp](stun:global.stun.twilio.com:3478?transport=udp)<br>
<a href="stun:stun.l.google.com:19302">stun:stun.l.google.com:19302</a> - -- [stun:stun.l.google.com:19302](stun:stun.l.google.com:19302)<br>
<a href="https://localhost.run/">https://localhost.run/</a> - Expose locally running servers over a tunnel to a public URL.<br>
<a href="https://github.com/localtunnel/localtunnel">https://github.com/localtunnel/localtunnel</a> - Expose locally running servers over a tunnel to a public URL. Free hosted version, and [open source](https://github.com/localtunnel/localtunnel).<br>
<a href="https://github.com/localtunnel/localtunnel">https://github.com/localtunnel/localtunnel</a> - Expose locally running servers over a tunnel to a public URL. Free hosted version, and [open source](https://github.com/localtunnel/localtunnel).<br>
<a href="https://www.radmin-vpn.com/) — Connect multiple computers together via a VPN enabling LAN-like networks. Unlimited peers. (Hamachi alternative">https://www.radmin-vpn.com/) — Connect multiple computers together via a VPN enabling LAN-like networks. Unlimited peers. (Hamachi alternative</a> - — Connect multiple computers together via a VPN enabling LAN-like networks. Unlimited peers. (Hamachi alternative)<br>
<a href="stun:stun.l.google.com:19302">stun:stun.l.google.com:19302</a> - — [stun:stun.l.google.com:19302](stun:stun.l.google.com:19302)<br>
<a href="stun:global.stun.twilio.com:3478?transport=udp">stun:global.stun.twilio.com:3478?transport=udp</a> - — [stun:global.stun.twilio.com:3478?transport=udp](stun:global.stun.twilio.com:3478?transport=udp)<br>
<a href="https://tailscale.com/">https://tailscale.com/</a> - Zero config VPN, using the open source WireGuard protocol. Installs on MacOS, iOS, Windows, Linux, and Android devices. Free plan for personal use with 20 devices.<br>
<a href="#tunneling-webrtc-web-socket-servers-and-other-routers">#tunneling-webrtc-web-socket-servers-and-other-routers</a> - Web Socket Servers and Other Routers](#tunneling-webrtc-web-socket-servers-and-other-routers)<br>
<a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/STUN) — Session Traversal of User Datagram Protocol [UDP] Through Network Address Translators [NATs]">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/STUN) — Session Traversal of User Datagram Protocol [UDP] Through Network Address Translators [NATs]</a> - Session Traversal of User Datagram Protocol [UDP] Through Network Address Translators [NATs])<br>
<a href="https://github.com/public-apis/public-apis">https://github.com/public-apis/public-apis</a> - Repo](https://github.com/public-apis/public-apis) — A list of free public APIs.<br>
<a href="https://cronhooks.io/">https://cronhooks.io/</a> - Replace your cron jobs with webhooks. Invoke any webhook at a given date time or repeatedly using cron expressions. Free plan allows 1 webhook schedule.<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>chore(): update cronhooks description</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/2b986006675cf0b8343a856db6f0076f3461116f</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://cronhooks.io/">https://cronhooks.io/</a> - Schedule on time or recurring webhooks. Free plan allows 5 ad-hoc schedules.<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Add Uptrace</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/e7dad250fd6fe38f1ce7865f36298ce5bbd7f584</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://uptrace.dev">https://uptrace.dev</a> - Distributed Tracing Tool that helps developers pinpoint failures and find performance bottlenecks. Has a free plan, offers a free Personal subscription for open source projects, and has an open source version.<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Added clarification for free version limitations</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/5a453962c28af3998abc48adda7c35769daab2dd</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://teamhood.com/">https://teamhood.com/</a> - Free Project, Task and Issue tracking software. Supports Kanban with Swimlanes and full Scrum implementation. Has integrated time tracking. Free for 5 users and 3 project portfolios.<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Add lucidchart</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/96cab17893a5e5d7ac2c0d9083be976d42dad9e1</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.lucidchart.com/">https://www.lucidchart.com/</a> - A online diagram tools with collaboration features. Free plan with 3 editable documents, 100 professional templates and basic collaboration features.<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Add dataminer.io</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/1f0714a786d5e6cf4424bdfa6e814890781be1a8</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://dataminer.io/) - A browser extension (Google Chrome, MS Edge">https://dataminer.io/) - A browser extension (Google Chrome, MS Edge</a> - - A browser extension (Google Chrome, MS Edge) for data extraction from web pages CSV or Excel. The free plan gives you 500 pages/month.<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Added Teamhood to collaboration category</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/83b6cb143b74b90def0b3fab49a6af90e97f7695</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://teamhood.com/">https://teamhood.com/</a> - Free Project, Task and Issue tracking software. Supports Kanban with Swimlanes and full Scrum implementation. Has integrated time tracking.<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Fix alphabetic order</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/127145e9914863257c87bf690ab79f34a6d742cd</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.terraform.io/">https://www.terraform.io/</a> - Terraform Cloud. Free remote state management and team collaboration for teams up to 5 users.<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>

</channel>
</rss>
