<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel>
<title>New Free-For-Dev</title>
<description>New Free Resources</description>
<link></link>
<item>
	<title>Merge branch 'master' into master</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/73e70b212e92c39fac51778af8f940a45aaec930</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://frontaid.io/">https://frontaid.io/</a> - Headless CMS that stores JSON content directly in your own Git repository. No restrictions.<br>
<a href="https://calendly.com">https://calendly.com</a> - Calendly is the tool for connecting and scheduling meetings. Free plan provides 1 Calendar connection per user and Unlimited meetings. Desktop and Mobile apps also provided.<br>
<a href="https://flutterflow.io">https://flutterflow.io</a> - — Build your Flutter App UI without writing a single line of code. Also has a Firebase integration. Free plan includes full access to UI Builder and Free templates.<br>
<a href="https://cdnjs.com/">https://cdnjs.com/</a> - Simple. Fast. Reliable. Content delivery at its finest. cdnjs is a free and open-source CDN service trusted by over 11% of all websites, powered by Cloudflare.<br>
<a href="https://www.jsdelivr.com/">https://www.jsdelivr.com/</a> - A free, fast, and reliable CDN for open source. Supports npm, GitHub, WordPress, Deno, and more.<br>
<a href="https://directus.io">https://directus.io</a> - Automatically generates a dynamic REST and GraphQL API for any SQL database.<br>
<a href="https://directus.io">https://directus.io</a> - Headless CMS. A completely free and open-source platform for managing assets and database content on-prem or in the Cloud. No limitations or paywalls.<br>
<a href="https://directus.io">https://directus.io</a> - — Directus as a service. An open-source data platform that automatically generates a dynamic REST and GraphQL API for pure SQL databases.<br>
<a href="https://duckly.com/">https://duckly.com/</a> - Talk and collaborate in real-time with your team. Pair programming with any IDE, terminal sharing, voice, video and screen sharing. Free for small teams.<br>
<a href="https://bookmarkos.com">https://bookmarkos.com</a> - Free all-on-one bookmark manager, tab manager, and task manager in a customizable online desktop with folder collaboration.<br>
<a href="https://nic.eu.org">https://nic.eu.org</a> - Free eu.org domain. Request is usually approved in 14 days.<br>
<a href="https://nic.eu.org">https://nic.eu.org</a> - Free eu.org domain. Request is usually approved in 14 days.<br>
<a href="https://fakermail.com/">https://fakermail.com/</a> - Free, temporary email for testing with last 100 email accounts stored.<br>
<a href="https://deepnote.com">https://deepnote.com</a> - A new kind of data science notebook. Jupyter-compatible with real-time collaboration and running in the cloud. Free tier includes unlimited personal projects, up to 750 hours of standard hardware and teams with up to 3 editors.<br>
<a href="https://getstream.io/">https://getstream.io/</a> - Build scalable newsfeeds, activity streams, chat and messaging in a few hours instead of weeks<br>
<a href="https://github.com/features/actions)(Free for Public Repos, 2000 min/month for private repos free">https://github.com/features/actions)(Free for Public Repos, 2000 min/month for private repos free</a> - Public Repos, 2000 min/month for private repos free)<br>
<a href="https://deepnote.com">https://deepnote.com</a> - A new kind of data science notebook. Jupyter-compatible with real-time collaboration and running in the cloud. Free tier includes unlimited personal projects, up to 750 hours of standard hardware and teams with up to 3 editors.<br>
<a href="https://reqres.in">https://reqres.in</a> - A Free hosted REST-API ready to respond to your AJAX requests.<br>
<a href="https://duckly.com/">https://duckly.com/</a> - Talk and collaborate in real-time with your team. Pair programming with any IDE, terminal sharing, voice, video and screen sharing. Free for small teams.<br>
<a href="https://robocorp.com">https://robocorp.com</a> - Open-source stack for powering Automation Ops. Try out Cloud features and implement simple automations for free. Robot work 240 min/month, 10 Assistant runs, Storage of 100 MB.<br>
<a href="https://www.softacheck.com/">https://www.softacheck.com/</a> - An online tool that performs static analysis for C/C++ code using open source tools such as cppcheck and clang-tidy and automatically generates code documentation for users using doxygen. This tool is free for use.<br>
<a href="https://recaptchame.com/">https://recaptchame.com/</a> - free reCAPTCHA and hCAPTCHA backend service. No Server-Side coding needed. Works for static websites.<br>
<a href="https://zoho.com/subscriptions">https://zoho.com/subscriptions</a> - Recurring Billing management free for 20 customers/subscriptions & 1 user with all the payment hosting done by Zoho themselves. Last 40 subscription metrics are stored<br>
<a href="https://www.shakebugs.com/">https://www.shakebugs.com/</a> - In-app bug reporting and feedback tool for mobile apps. Free plan, 10 bug reports per app/per month.<br>
<a href="https://smartmockups.com/">https://smartmockups.com/</a> - Create product mockups, 200 free mockups.<br>
<a href="https://updrafts.app">https://updrafts.app</a> - WYSIWYG web site builder for tailwindcss based designs. Free for non-commercial usage.<br>
<a href="https://www.bearer.sh/">https://www.bearer.sh/</a> - Helps implement privacy by design via audits and continuous workflows so that organizations comply with GDPR and other regulations. Free tier is limited to smaller teams and SaaS version only.<br>
<a href="https://herotofu.com/">https://herotofu.com/</a> - Forms backend with bot detection and encrypted archive. Forward submissions via UI to email, Slack, or Zapier. Use your own frontend, no server code required. Free plan gives unlimited forms and 50 submissions per month.<br>
<a href="https://railway.app">https://railway.app</a> - Railway is an infrastructure platform where you can provision infrastructure, develop with that infrastructure locally, and then deploy to the cloud. 3 Projects, 2 Plugins / Project, 2 Environments / Project, 3 Live Deploys / Environment available for free.<br>
<a href="https://www.trackawesomelist.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev">https://www.trackawesomelist.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev</a> - Awesome List](https://www.trackawesomelist.com/badge.svg)](https://www.trackawesomelist.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev)<br>
<a href="https://www.trackawesomelist.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev">https://www.trackawesomelist.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev</a> - <br>
<a href="https://docs.datastax.com/en/astra/docs/datastax-astra-database-limits.html">https://docs.datastax.com/en/astra/docs/datastax-astra-database-limits.html</a> - Cloud Native Cassandra as a Service with [40GB free tier](https://docs.datastax.com/en/astra/docs/datastax-astra-database-limits.html)<br>
<a href="https://clarity.microsoft.com/">https://clarity.microsoft.com/</a> - - Session recording completely free with "no traffic limits", no project limits, and no sampling<br>
<a href="https://squidex.io/) - Offers free tier for small projects. API / GraphQL first. Open source, and based on event sourcing (versing every changes automatically">https://squidex.io/) - Offers free tier for small projects. API / GraphQL first. Open source, and based on event sourcing (versing every changes automatically</a> - Offers free tier for small projects. API / GraphQL first. Open source, and based on event sourcing (versing every changes automatically).<br>
<a href="https://api.ksoft.si/">https://api.ksoft.si/</a> - Free lyrics api chiefly aimed for discord bots.Also provides an extensive library of images and user data<br>
<a href="https://replit.com/">https://replit.com/</a> - A cloud coding environment for various program languages.<br>
<a href="https://www.datastax.com/products/datastax-astra/pricing">https://www.datastax.com/products/datastax-astra/pricing</a> - Cloud Native Cassandra as a Service with [40GB free tier](https://www.datastax.com/products/datastax-astra/pricing)<br>
<a href="https://formsubmit.co/">https://formsubmit.co/</a> - Easy form endpoints for your HTML forms. Free Forever. No registration required.<br>
<a href="https://formsubmit.co/">https://formsubmit.co/</a> - Easy form endpoints for your HTML forms. Free Forever. No registration required.<br>
<a href="https://mailtie.com/">https://mailtie.com/</a> - Free Email Forwarding for Your Domain. No registration required. Free Forever.<br>
<a href="https://www.lightly.ai/">https://www.lightly.ai/</a> - Improve your machine learning models by using the right data. Use datasets of up to 1'000 samples for free.<br>
<a href="https://localeum.com">https://localeum.com</a> - Free up to 1000 strings, 1 user, unlimited languages, unlimited projects<br>
<a href="https://mailazy.com/">https://mailazy.com/</a> - 500 emails/day free, 50,000 emails/month under the beta program!<br>
<a href="https://mailazy.com/">https://mailazy.com/</a> - Mailazy is the only simple transactional email service you’ll need. 500 emails/day free forever.<br>
<a href="https://mailazy.com/) — Mailazy is the only simple transactional email service you’ll need. 15,000 emails/month free forever (500 emails/day sending limit">https://mailazy.com/) — Mailazy is the only simple transactional email service you’ll need. 15,000 emails/month free forever (500 emails/day sending limit</a> - Mailazy is the only simple transactional email service you’ll need. 15,000 emails/month free forever (500 emails/day sending limit).<br>
<a href="https://www.scrumfast.com">https://www.scrumfast.com</a> - Free Scrum board with a very intuitive interface.<br>
<a href="https://mocko.dev/">https://mocko.dev/</a> - Proxy your API, choose which endpoints to mock in the cloud and inspect traffic, for free. Speed up your development and integrations tests.<br>
<a href="https://inboxkitten.com/">https://inboxkitten.com/</a> - Free temporary/disposable email inbox, with up-to 3 day email auto-deletes. Open sourced, and can be self-hosted.<br>
<a href="https://unicornplatform.com/">https://unicornplatform.com/</a> - - Effortless landing page builder with hosting. 1 website for free.<br>
<a href="https://pages.github.com) (Free for Public Repos">https://pages.github.com) (Free for Public Repos</a> - Hosting](https://pages.github.com) (Free for Public Repos)<br>
<a href="https://www.scrumfast.com">https://www.scrumfast.com</a> - Scrum board with a very intuitive interface, free up to 5 users.<br>
<a href="https://www.emailjs.com/">https://www.emailjs.com/</a> - This is not a full email server, this is just email client which you can use to send emails right from client send without exposing your credentials, the free tier has: 200 monthly requests, 2 email templates, Requests up to 50Kb, Limited contacts history.<br>
<a href="https://serpapi.com/">https://serpapi.com/</a> - Real-time search engine scraping API. Returns structured JSON results for Google, Youtube, Bing, Baidu, Walmart and many other engines. Free plan includes 100 successful API calls per month.<br>
<a href="https://internxt.com">https://internxt.com</a> - Internxt Drive is a zero-knowledge file storage service that's based on absolute privacy and uncompromising security. Sign up and get 10 GB for free, forever!<br>
<a href="https://www.datastax.com/products/datastax-astra/pricing">https://www.datastax.com/products/datastax-astra/pricing</a> - Cloud Native Cassandra as a Service with [40GB free tier](https://www.datastax.com/products/datastax-astra/pricing)<br>
<a href="https://deploynow.space">https://deploynow.space</a> - — Deploy smarter. Deploy faster. Deploy Now. - Deploy up to 3 web projects from your GitHub repository for free.<br>
<a href="https://herotofu.com/">https://herotofu.com/</a> - Forms backend with bot detection and encrypted archive. Forward submissions via UI to email, Slack, or Zapier. Use your own frontend, no server code required. Free plan gives unlimited forms and 100 submissions per month.<br>
<a href="https://mail.tm">https://mail.tm</a> - Disposable e-mail with user friendly interface. No registration needed.<br>
<a href="https://mailazy.com/) — Mailazy is the only simple transactional email service you’ll need. 15,000 emails/month free forever (500 emails/day sending limit">https://mailazy.com/) — Mailazy is the only simple transactional email service you’ll need. 15,000 emails/month free forever (500 emails/day sending limit</a> - Mailazy is the only simple transactional email service you’ll need. 15,000 emails/month free forever (500 emails/day sending limit).<br>
<a href="https://internxt.com">https://internxt.com</a> - Internxt Drive is a zero-knowledge file storage service that's based on absolute privacy and uncompromising security. Sign up and get 2 GB for free, forever!<br>
<a href="https://www.cockroachlabs.com/free-tier/">https://www.cockroachlabs.com/free-tier/</a> - Free CockroachDB up to 5GB and 1vCPU.<br>
<a href="https://nic.ua/">https://nic.ua/</a> - Free pp.ua domain.<br>
<a href="https://efemarai.com">https://efemarai.com</a> - Testing and debugging platform for ML models and data. Visualize any computational graph. Free 30 debugging sessions per month for developers.<br>
<a href="https://efemarai.com">https://efemarai.com</a> - Testing and debugging platform for ML models and data. Visualize any computational graph. Free 30 debugging sessions per month for developers.<br>
<a href="https://nic.ua/">https://nic.ua/</a> - Free pp.ua domain.<br>
<a href="https://www.deta.sh">https://www.deta.sh</a> - Deploy unlimited number of Node.js and Python apps for free. Includes free DBs, Auth and email.<br>
<a href="https://github.com/bridgecrewio/checkov">https://github.com/bridgecrewio/checkov</a> - Infrastructure as code (IaC) security powered by the open source tool - [Checkov](https://github.com/bridgecrewio/checkov). The core Bridgecrew platform is free for up to 50 IaC resources.<br>
<a href="https://sia.tech/">https://sia.tech/</a> - An open protocol for hosting data and web applications on the decentralized web using [Sia](https://sia.tech/). Free tier provides storage upto 100GB.<br>
<a href="https://vadoo.tv/">https://vadoo.tv/</a> - Video hosting and marketing made simple. Upload videos with a single click. Record, manage, share & more. Free tier provides unlimited videos, 10 GB bandwidth/month<br>
<a href="https://vadoo.tv/">https://vadoo.tv/</a> - Video hosting and marketing made simple. Upload videos with a single click. Record, manage, share & more. Free tier provides upto 10 videos, 1 GB storage/month, 10 GB bandwidth/month<br>
<a href="https://vadoo.tv/">https://vadoo.tv/</a> - Video hosting and marketing made simple. Upload videos with a single click. Record, manage, share & more. Free tier provides upto 10 videos, 1 GB storage, 10 GB bandwidth/month<br>
<a href="https://www.macrometa.com/">https://www.macrometa.com/</a> - a noSQL database, Pub/Sub, event processing, and serverless edge computing platform for building geo-distributed and real-time applications.<br>
<a href="https://www.macrometa.com/">https://www.macrometa.com/</a> - a noSQL database, Pub/Sub, event processing, and serverless edge computing platform for building geo-distributed and real-time applications. Free dev account gives access to 10,000 Operations/Day & 200MB Storage.<br>
<a href="https://geokeo.com">https://geokeo.com</a> - - Geocoding api with language correction and more. Worldwide coverage. 2,500 free daily queries<br>
<a href="https://gitlocalize.com">https://gitlocalize.com</a> - Free and unlimited for both private and public repositories<br>
<a href="https://www.apify.com/">https://www.apify.com/</a> - Web scraping and automation platform to create an API for any website and extract data. Ready-made scrapers, integrated proxies, and custom solutions. Free plan with $5 platform credits included every month.<br>
<a href="#remote-desktop-tools">#remote-desktop-tools</a> - Tools](#remote-desktop-tools)<br>
<a href="#remote-desktop-tools">#remote-desktop-tools</a> - Customer Support management with 3 agents and private knowledge base, email tickets. Integrates with [Zoho Assist](#remote-desktop-tools).<br>
<a href="https://zoho.com/assist">https://zoho.com/assist</a> - — Free for 1 remote technician & 5 unattended computers<br>
<a href="https://getscreen.me">https://getscreen.me</a> - Free for 2 devices, no limits on the number and duration of sessions<br>
<a href="#table-of-contents">#table-of-contents</a> - top](#table-of-contents)**<br>
<a href="https://hygger.io">https://hygger.io</a> - Project management platform. Free plan offers unlimited users,projects & boards with 100 MB Storage.<br>
<a href="https://zoho.com/assist">https://zoho.com/assist</a> - Customer Support management with 3 agents and private knowledge base, email tickets. Integrates with [Assist](https://zoho.com/assist) for 1 remote technician & 5 unattended computers.<br>
<a href="https://guacamole.apache.org/">https://guacamole.apache.org/</a> - — Open source clientless remote desktop gateway<br>
<a href="https://hottempmail.com/">https://hottempmail.com/</a> - Unlimited free temp email or disposable temporary email addresses. Autoexpire in one days.<br>
<a href="https://chpokify.com/">https://chpokify.com/</a> - Teams based Planning Poker that saves time of sprint estimation. Free up to 5 users, free Jira integrations, unlimited video calls, unlimited teams, unlimited sessions.<br>
<a href="https://planetscale.com/">https://planetscale.com/</a> - PlanetScale is a MySQL compatible, serverless database platform powered by Vitess, 3 databases for free with 10GB storage, 100 Million rows read/mo per database, and 10 Million rows written/mo per database.<br>
<a href="https://texterify.com/">https://texterify.com/</a> - Free for a single user<br>
<a href="#translation-management">#translation-management</a> - <br>
<a href="https://smalldev.tools/">https://smalldev.tools/</a> - A free tool for developers that allows you to Encode/Decode various formats, Minify HTML/CSS/Javascript, Beautify, Generate Fake/Testing real like dataset in JSON/CSV & multiple other formats and many more features. With a delightful interface.<br>
<a href="https://asayer.io/pricing.html) — Hosted version of openreplay, an open-source session replay (alternative to FullStory and LogRocket">https://asayer.io/pricing.html) — Hosted version of openreplay, an open-source session replay (alternative to FullStory and LogRocket</a> - Hosted version of openreplay, an open-source session replay (alternative to FullStory and LogRocket). Free 1k sessions/month with 14 days retention<br>
<a href="https://github.com/marketplace/testspace-com">https://github.com/marketplace/testspace-com</a> - Dashboard for publishing automated test results and a Framework for implementing manual tests as code using GitHub. [Free for Open Source](https://github.com/marketplace/testspace-com).<br>
<a href="https://discord.com/">https://discord.com/</a> - Chat with public/private rooms. Markdown text, voice, video, and screen sharing capabilities. Free for unlimited users.<br>
<a href="https://telegram.org/">https://telegram.org/</a> - Telegram is for everyone who wants fast and reliable messaging and calls. Business users and small teams may like the large groups, usernames, desktop apps and powerful file sharing options.<br>
<a href="https://github.com/marketplace/testspace-com">https://github.com/marketplace/testspace-com</a> - A Dashboard for publishing automated test results and a Framework for implementing manual tests as code using GitHub. The service is [free for Open Source](https://github.com/marketplace/testspace-com) accounts for 450 results per month.<br>
<a href="https://www.antideo.com">https://www.antideo.com</a> - 10 API requests per hour for email verification, IP and phone number validation in free tier. No Credit Cards required.<br>
<a href="https://eva.pingutil.com">https://eva.pingutil.com</a> - — Verify 5 million emails per day for free using REST API. No sign-ups required.<br>
<a href="https://quickemailverification.com">https://quickemailverification.com</a> - Verify 100 emails daily for free on a free tier along with other free APIs like DEA Detector, DNS Lookup, SPF Detector and more.<br>
<a href="https://hottempmail.com/">https://hottempmail.com/</a> - Unlimited free temp email or disposable temporary email addresses. Autoexpires in one day.<br>
<a href="https://temp-mail.org">https://temp-mail.org</a> - Temporary, secure, anonymous, free, disposable email address with REST API for fetching 100 emails from its disposable mailbox per day for free.<br>
<a href="https://mojoauth.com/">https://mojoauth.com/</a> - MojoAuth makes it easy to implement Passwordless on your web, mobile or any application in minutes.<br>
<a href="https://eva.pingutil.com">https://eva.pingutil.com</a> - Verify 5 million emails per day for free using REST API. No sign-ups required.<br>
<a href="https://lean20.com">https://lean20.com</a> - Public status pages for incident reporting. 100% free.<br>
<a href="https://lean20.com/product/status/">https://lean20.com/product/status/</a> - Public status pages for incident reporting. 100% free.<br>
<a href="https://mojoauth.com/">https://mojoauth.com/</a> - MojoAuth makes it easy to implement Passwordless authentication on your web, mobile or any application in minutes.<br>
<a href="https://viezly.com/">https://viezly.com/</a> - Enhanced code review tool for easier code reading and navigation. Free for Open Source and free for personal usage.<br>
<a href="https://www.geoapify.com/">https://www.geoapify.com/</a> - Vector and raster map tiles, geocoding, places, routing, isolines APIs. 3000 free requests / day.<br>
<a href="https://gitdailies.com">https://gitdailies.com</a> - Daily reports of your team's Commit and Pull Request activity on GitHub. Includes Push visualizer, peer recognition system, custom alert builder. Free tier has unlimited users, 3 repos, 3 alert configs.<br>
<a href="https://emailoctopus.com">https://emailoctopus.com</a> - Up to 2,500 subscribers and 10,000 emails per month free<br>
<a href="https://node.new">https://node.new</a> - Online/Cloud Code IDE to create, edit, & deploy fullstack apps. Support any popular NodeJs based frontend & backend frameworks. Shortlink to create new project: [https://node.new](https://node.new).<br>
<a href="https://www.molasses.app">https://www.molasses.app</a> - Release features with confidence; manage feature flags across web, mobile, and server side applications. Use our hosted API, deploy to your own private cloud, or run on-premise<br>
<a href="https://icon.horse">https://icon.horse</a> - – Get the highest resolution favicon for any website from our simple API.<br>
<a href="https://uploadcare.com/hub/developers/">https://uploadcare.com/hub/developers/</a> - Uploadcare provides media pipeline with ultimate toolkit based on cutting-edge algorithms. All features are available for developers absolutely for free: File Uploading API and UI, Image CDN and Origin Services, Adaptive Delivery and Smart Compression. Limit free tier has 3000 uploads, 3 GB traffic and 3 GB storage.<br>
<a href="https://degoo.com/) – AI based cloud storage with free up to 100 Gb, 5 devices, 500 Gb referral bonus (365 days account inactivity">https://degoo.com/) – AI based cloud storage with free up to 100 Gb, 5 devices, 500 Gb referral bonus (365 days account inactivity</a> - AI based cloud storage with free up to 100 Gb, 5 devices, 500 Gb referral bonus (365 days account inactivity).<br>
<a href="http://supportivekoala.com/">http://supportivekoala.com/</a> - Allows you to autogenerate images by your input via templates. Free plan allows you to create up to 100 images per week.<br>
<a href="http://cloud.yugabyte.com">http://cloud.yugabyte.com</a> - YugabyteDB is a distributed SQL database compatible with PostgresSQL. The cloud free tier is a 2 vCPU, 4GB RAM, 10GB Disk.<br>
<a href="https://www.fontshare.com/">https://www.fontshare.com/</a> - is a free fonts service. It’s a growing collection of professional grade fonts that are 100% free for personal and commercial use.<br>
<a href="https://graphcdn.io/">https://graphcdn.io/</a> - Scale, inspect & protect your GraphQL API. 5m requests per month for free.<br>
<a href="https://logflare.app/">https://logflare.app/</a> - Free for upto 12,960,000 enteries per app per month, 3 days retention<br>
<a href="https://economize.cloud">https://economize.cloud</a> - Economize helps demystify cloud infrastructure costs by organizing cloud resources, optimize and report the same. Free for up to $5000 spends on Google Cloud Platform every month.<br>
<a href="https://www.framer.com/">https://www.framer.com/</a> - Framer helps you iterate and animate interface ideas for your next app, website, or product—starting with powerful layouts. For anyone validating Framer as a professional prototyping tool: unlimited viewers, up to 2 editors, up to 3 projects.<br>
<a href="https://www.integromat.com">https://www.integromat.com</a> - Workflow automation tool which lets you connect apps and automate workflows using UI, it supports many apps and most popular APIs. Free for public GitHub repositories, and free tier with 100 Mb, 1000 Operations and 15 minutes of minimum interval.<br>
<a href="#cloud-management-solutions">#cloud-management-solutions</a> - solutions](#cloud-management-solutions)<br>
<a href="https://www.brainboard.co">https://www.brainboard.co</a> - visually build and manage cloud infrastructures from end-to-end:<br>
<a href="#table-of-contents">#table-of-contents</a> - top](#table-of-contents)**<br>
<a href="https://dynapictures.com">https://dynapictures.com</a> - Design automation tool which lets you dynamically generate images from the template. Change colors, texts, logos and images on the fly.<br>
<a href="https://dynapictures.com">https://dynapictures.com</a> - Design automation tool which lets you dynamically generate images over REST API. Change colors, texts, logos and images on the fly.<br>
<a href="https://www.terraform.io/">https://www.terraform.io/</a> - Terraform Cloud. Free remote state management and team collaboration for teams up to 5 users.<br>
<a href="https://www.brainboard.co">https://www.brainboard.co</a> - Collaborative solution to visually build and manage cloud infrastructures from end-to-end.<br>
<a href="https://themeselection.com/">https://themeselection.com/</a> - Selected high quality, modern design, professional and easy-to-use Free Admin Dashboard Template,<br>
<a href="https://dynapictures.com">https://dynapictures.com</a> - Design automation tool which lets you dynamically generate images over REST API. Change colors, texts, logos and images on the fly. Free plan includes 30 generated images per month and 3 image templates.<br>
<a href="https://meercode.io/">https://meercode.io/</a> - Meercode is the ultimate monitoring dashboard for your CI/CD builds.<br>
<a href="https://meercode.io/">https://meercode.io/</a> - Meercode is the ultimate monitoring dashboard for your CI/CD builds. Free for open-source and 1 private repository.<br>
<a href="https://www.markup.io/">https://www.markup.io/</a> - MarkUp lets you collect feedback directly on top of your websites, PDFs and images.<br>
<a href="https://neptune.ai/">https://neptune.ai/</a> - Log, store, display, organize, compare and query all your MLOps metadata. Free for individuals: 1 member, 100 GB of metadata storage, 200h of monitoring/month<br>
<a href="https://sawolabs.com/">https://sawolabs.com/</a> - Simplify login and improve user experience by integrating passwordless authentication in your app. Circumvent your bounce rates by 30%.<br>
<a href="https://instatus.com">https://instatus.com</a> - Get a beautiful status page in 10 seconds. Free forever with unlimited subs and unlimited teams.<br>
<a href="https://backlight.dev/">https://backlight.dev/</a> - With collaboration between developers and designers at heart, Backlight is a very complete coding platform where teams build, document, publish, scale and maintain Design Systems.<br>
<a href="https://www.mockplus.com/idoc">https://www.mockplus.com/idoc</a> - - Mockplus iDoc is a powerful design collaboration & handoff tool. Free Plan includes 3 users and 5 projects with all features available.<br>
<a href="https://webcomponents.dev/">https://webcomponents.dev/</a> - Code components in isolation, visualize them in stories, test them and publish them on npm.<br>
<a href="https://webcomponents.dev/">https://webcomponents.dev/</a> - In-browser IDE to code web components in isolation with 58 templates available, supporting stories and tests.<br>
<a href="https://sawolabs.com/">https://sawolabs.com/</a> - Simplify login and improve user experience by integrating passwordless authentication in your app. 5000 free authentications per month.<br>
<a href="https://backlight.dev/">https://backlight.dev/</a> - With collaboration between developers and designers at heart, Backlight is a very complete coding platform where teams build, document, publish, scale and maintain Design Systems.Free plan allows up to 3 editors working on 1 design system with unlimited viewers.<br>
<a href="https://duply.co">https://duply.co</a> - Create dynamic images from API & URL, design template once and reuse it. Free tier offers 70 images/month creation from API & URL and Up to 100 through Form.<br>
<a href="https://hasura.io/">https://hasura.io/</a> - Hasura extends your existing databases wherever it is hosted and provides an instant GraphQL API that can be securely accessed for web, mobile, and data integration workloads.<br>
<a href="https://hasura.io/">https://hasura.io/</a> - Hasura extends your existing databases wherever it is hosted and provides an instant GraphQL API that can be securely accessed for web, mobile, and data integration workloads. Free for 1GB/month of data pass-through.<br>
<a href="https://www.tigergraph.com/cloud/) — Managed native Graph DBMS / analytics platform with a SQL-like graph query language and a REST API. 1 TG.Free instance on AWS (4 vCPU, 7.5 GB memory, 50 GB disk) or on GCP(2 vCPU, 8 GB memory, 128 GB disk">https://www.tigergraph.com/cloud/) — Managed native Graph DBMS / analytics platform with a SQL-like graph query language and a REST API. 1 TG.Free instance on AWS (4 vCPU, 7.5 GB memory, 50 GB disk) or on GCP(2 vCPU, 8 GB memory, 128 GB disk</a> - — Managed native Graph DBMS / analytics platform with a SQL-like graph query language and a REST API. 1 TG.Free instance on AWS (4 vCPU, 7.5 GB memory, 50 GB disk) or on GCP(2 vCPU, 8 GB memory, 128 GB disk). Free instance sleeps after 1 hour of inactivity.<br>
<a href="https://neo4j.com/cloud/aura/) — Managed native Graph DBMS / analytics platform with a Cypher query language and a REST API. Limits on graph size (50k nodes, 175k relationships">https://neo4j.com/cloud/aura/) — Managed native Graph DBMS / analytics platform with a Cypher query language and a REST API. Limits on graph size (50k nodes, 175k relationships</a> - — Managed native Graph DBMS / analytics platform with a Cypher query language and a REST API. Limits on graph size (50k nodes, 175k relationships).<br>
<a href="https://cloud.dgraph.io/pricing?type=free">https://cloud.dgraph.io/pricing?type=free</a> - — Managed native Graph DBMS with a GraphQL API. Limited to 1 MB data trasnfer per day.<br>
<a href="https://js.org">https://js.org</a> - Free js.org domains for GitHub Pages<br>
<a href="https://syagent.com/">https://syagent.com/</a> - Non commercial free server monitoring service, alerts and metrics.<br>
<a href="https://logtail.com/">https://logtail.com/</a> - ClickHouse-based SQL-compatible log management. Free up to 1 GB per month, 3 days retention.<br>
<a href="https://huggingface.co">https://huggingface.co</a> - Build, train and deploy NLP models for Pytorch, TensorFlow, and JAX. Free up to 30k input characters/mo.<br>
<a href="https://railway.app">https://railway.app</a> - Railway is an infrastructure platform where you can provision infrastructure, develop with that infrastructure locally, and then deploy to the cloud. 1GB Disk, 512 MB RAM, limited to $5 of usage monthly available for free.<br>
<a href="https://dkimvalidator.com/">https://dkimvalidator.com/</a> - Test if email's dns/spf/dkim/dmarc settings are correct, free service by roundsphere.com<br>
<a href="https://counter.dev">https://counter.dev</a> - Web analytics made simple and therefore privacy friendly. Free or pay what you want by donation.<br>
<a href="https://craftmypdf.com">https://craftmypdf.com</a> - Auto-Generate PDF documents from reusable templates with a drop-and-drop editor and a simple API. Free plan comes with 100 PDFs/month and 3 templates.<br>
<a href="https://tailscale.com/">https://tailscale.com/</a> - Zero config VPN. Installs on any device, manages firewall rules. Run on MacOS, iOS, Windows, Linux, and Android. Free plan for personal use with 20 devices.<br>
<a href="https://tailscale.com/">https://tailscale.com/</a> - Zero config VPN, using the open source WireGuard protocol. Installs on MacOS, iOS, Windows, Linux, and Android devices. Free plan for personal use with 20 devices.<br>
<a href="https://analytics.statvoo.com/">https://analytics.statvoo.com/</a> - — Forever FREE Customer Analytics for ALL your websites, with Unlimited Events per month<br>
<a href="https://carbon.now.sh">https://carbon.now.sh</a> - create and share code snippet in an aesthetic screenshot-like image format. Usually used to aesthetically share/show-off code snippet on Twitter or blog posts.<br>
<a href="https://github.com/localtunnel/localtunnel">https://github.com/localtunnel/localtunnel</a> - Easily share a web service on your local development machine to a public internet URL without messing with DNS and firewall settings. Similar to Ngrok. In addition to the free hosted version, it is also [open source](https://github.com/localtunnel/localtunnel).<br>
<a href="https://github.com/localtunnel/localtunnel">https://github.com/localtunnel/localtunnel</a> - Easily share a web service on your local development machine to a public internet URL without messing with DNS and firewall settings. Similar to Ngrok. In addition to the free hosted version, it is also [open source](https://github.com/localtunnel/localtunnel).<br>
<a href="https://quicktype.io/">https://quicktype.io/</a> - Quickly auto generate models/class/type/interface and serializers from JSON, schema, and GraphQL for working with data quickly & safely in any programming language. Convert JSON into gorgeous, typesafe code in any language.<br>
<a href="https://github.com/julien-lafont/Mocky">https://github.com/julien-lafont/Mocky</a> - A simple web app to generate custom HTTP responses for mocking HTTP request. Also available as [open source](https://github.com/julien-lafont/Mocky).<br>
<a href="https://ray.so/">https://ray.so/</a> - Create beautiful images of your code snippets.<br>
<a href="https://about.ipaddress.sh/">https://about.ipaddress.sh/</a> - Simple service to get public IP address in different [formats](https://about.ipaddress.sh/).<br>
<a href="https://freeflarum.com/) - Community powered free Flarum hosting for up to 250 users (donate to remove watermark from footer">https://freeflarum.com/) - Community powered free Flarum hosting for up to 250 users (donate to remove watermark from footer</a> - Community powered free Flarum hosting for up to 250 users (donate to remove watermark from footer).<br>
<a href="https://combinatronics.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/master/index.html">https://combinatronics.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/master/index.html</a> - Convert your Github hosted assets (images, CSS, JS, etc.) into CDN assets. Can even render HTML files, for [example from this repo](https://combinatronics.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/master/index.html). Similar to rawgit.com and raw.githack.com.<br>
<a href="https://ui-avatars.com/">https://ui-avatars.com/</a> - - Generate avatars with initials from names. Which the urls can be directly hotlinked in your web/app. Support config parameters via the url.<br>
<a href="https://pravatar.cc/">https://pravatar.cc/</a> - Generate random/placeholder fake avatar, which url can be directly hotlinked in your web/app.<br>
<a href="https://developers.cloudflare.com/1.1.1.1/encrypted-dns/dns-over-https/make-api-requests">https://developers.cloudflare.com/1.1.1.1/encrypted-dns/dns-over-https/make-api-requests</a> - Free public DNS Resolver which is fast and secure (encrypt your DNS query), provided by CloudFlare. Useful to bypass your internet provider's DNS blocking, prevent DNS query spying, and [to block adult & malware content](https://developers.cloudflare.com/1.1.1.1/1.1.1.1-for-families). Can also be used [via API](https://developers.cloudflare.com/1.1.1.1/encrypted-dns/dns-over-https/make-api-requests). Note: Just a DNS resolver, not a DNS hoster.<br>
<a href="https://www.napkin.io/">https://www.napkin.io/</a> - FaaS with 1Gb of memory, a default timeout of 15 seconds and 1,000,000 free API calls/month.<br>
<a href="https://vatcheckapi.com">https://vatcheckapi.com</a> - Simple and free VAT number validation API. 500 free requests per month.<br>
<a href="https://fleep.io/">https://fleep.io/</a> - Fleep an alternative to Slack. It has a free plan for small teams with full message history, unlimited 1:1 conversations, 1 group conversation and 1 GB file storage.<br>
<a href="https://chanty.com/) — Chanty is another alternative to Slack. It has a free forever plan for small teams (up to 10">https://chanty.com/) — Chanty is another alternative to Slack. It has a free forever plan for small teams (up to 10</a> - Chanty is another alternative to Slack. It has a free forever plan for small teams (up to 10) with unlimited public and private conversations, searchable history, unlimited 1:1 audio calls, unlimited voice messages, 10 integrations and 20 GB storage per team.<br>
<a href="https://track.toggl.com/">https://track.toggl.com/</a> - — Task management and tracking app with a free plan provides seamless time tracking and reporting designed with freelancers in mind. It has unlimited tracking records, projects, clients, tags, reporting and more.<br>
<a href="https://plan.toggl.com/">https://plan.toggl.com/</a> - — Task planning tool that has a free plan for solo developers with unlimited tasks, milestones and timelines.<br>
<a href="https://hybiscus.dev/">https://hybiscus.dev/</a> - Build pdf reports using a simple declarative API. Free tier includes upto 100 single page reports per month with the ability to customise color pallet and fonts.<br>
<a href="https://docs.travis-ci.com/user/billing-faq/#what-if-i-am-building-open-source">https://docs.travis-ci.com/user/billing-faq/#what-if-i-am-building-open-source</a> - [Free for public GitHub repositories](https://docs.travis-ci.com/user/billing-faq/#what-if-i-am-building-open-source)<br>
<a href="https://platform9.com/">https://platform9.com/</a> - Managed Kubernetes plane. Free plan offers management capabilities up to 3 clusters & 20 nodes. Note: you must provide cluster infrastructure by yourself.<br>
<a href="https://www.cockroachlabs.com/docs/cockroachcloud/serverless-faqs.html#what-are-the-usage-limits-of-cockroachdb-serverless-beta)">https://www.cockroachlabs.com/docs/cockroachcloud/serverless-faqs.html#what-are-the-usage-limits-of-cockroachdb-serverless-beta)</a> - Free CockroachDB up to 5GB and 1vCPU (limited [request units](https://www.cockroachlabs.com/docs/cockroachcloud/serverless-faqs.html#what-are-the-usage-limits-of-cockroachdb-serverless-beta))<br>
<a href="https://about.ipaddress.sh/">https://about.ipaddress.sh/</a> - Simple service to get public IP address in different [formats](https://about.ipaddress.sh/).<br>
<a href="https://cloud.dgraph.io/pricing?type=free">https://cloud.dgraph.io/pricing?type=free</a> - — Managed native Graph DBMS with a GraphQL API. Limited to 1 MB data trasnfer per day.<br>
<a href="https://plan.toggl.com/">https://plan.toggl.com/</a> - Provides 2 free productivity tools. [Toggl Track](https://track.toggl.com/) for time management and tracking app with a free plan provides seamless time tracking and reporting designed for freelancers in mind. It has unlimited tracking records, projects, clients, tags, reporting and more. And [Toggl Plan](https://plan.toggl.com/) for task planning that comes with a free plan for solo developers with unlimited tasks, milestones and timelines.<br>
<a href="https://counter.dev">https://counter.dev</a> - Web analytics made simple and therefore privacy friendly. Free or pay what you want by donation.<br>
<a href="https://toggl.com/plan/">https://toggl.com/plan/</a> - Provides 2 free productivity tools. [Toggl Track](https://toggl.com/track/) for time management and tracking app with a free plan provides seamless time tracking and reporting designed for freelancers in mind. It has unlimited tracking records, projects, clients, tags, reporting and more. And [Toggl Plan](https://toggl.com/plan/) for task planning that comes with a free plan for solo developers with unlimited tasks, milestones and timelines.<br>
<a href="https://vvv.space/">https://vvv.space/</a> - Free links manager with private/public spaces, includes slack and google docs integration and chrome plugin.<br>
<a href="https://numlookupapi.com">https://numlookupapi.com</a> - Free phone number validation API - 100k free requests / month.<br>
<a href="https://pofile.net/free-po-editor">https://pofile.net/free-po-editor</a> - editor](https://pofile.net/free-po-editor) — Free for everybody<br>
<a href="https://parsio.io) — Free email parser (Forward email, extract the data, send it to your server">https://parsio.io) — Free email parser (Forward email, extract the data, send it to your server</a> - Free email parser (Forward email, extract the data, send it to your server)<br>
<a href="https://flowdash.com/">https://flowdash.com/</a> - Automate business workflows. Free tier for up to 3 users, 1000 tasks, and 3 workflows.<br>
<a href="https://exportsdk.com">https://exportsdk.com</a> - - PDF generator API with drag and drop template editor that also provides an SDK and no-code integrations. Free plan comes with 250 pages per month, unlimited users and three templates.<br>
<a href="https://www.zenrows.com/">https://www.zenrows.com/</a> - Web Scraping API & proxy server that bypasses any anti-bot solution while offering javascript rendering, rotating proxies, and geotargeting. Free tier of 1000 API calls.<br>
<a href="https://hyperforms.app/">https://hyperforms.app/</a> - Create form to email and more in seconds and without backend code. The Personal account gives you up to 50 form submissions per month for free.<br>
<a href="https://www.netdata.cloud/">https://www.netdata.cloud/</a> - Real-time performance monitoring, done right! Netdata is high-fidelity infrastructure monitoring and troubleshooting.<br>
<a href="https://www.netdata.cloud/">https://www.netdata.cloud/</a> - Netdata is an open source tool designed to collect real-time metrics.Great fast growing product. It can also be found in github!<br>
<a href="https://www.magicpattern.design/tools/blob-generator">https://www.magicpattern.design/tools/blob-generator</a> - — Create random organic-shaped blobs with solid colors, linear/radial gradients, and pattern fills.<br>
<a href="https://www.magicpattern.design/tools/gradient-generator">https://www.magicpattern.design/tools/gradient-generator</a> - Generator](https://www.magicpattern.design/tools/gradient-generator) — Create, save & share beautiful CSS linear, radial, and conic gradients for your backgrounds.<br>
<a href="https://www.magicpattern.design/tools">https://www.magicpattern.design/tools</a> - A collection of CSS & SVG background generators & tools for gradients, patterns, and blobs.<br>
<a href="https://shortcut.com/">https://shortcut.com/</a> - Project management platform. Free for up to 10 users forever.<br>
<a href="https://www.prefect.io/cloud/">https://www.prefect.io/cloud/</a> - A complete platform for dataflow automation. All plans include 20,000 free runs every month. That's enough to power ETL for most small businesses.<br>
<a href="https://selectel.com/services/dns/">https://selectel.com/services/dns/</a> - Free DNS hosting with unlimited records, anycast<br>
<a href="https://mybinder.org/">https://mybinder.org/</a> - Turn a Git repo into a collection of interactive notebooks. It is a free, public service.<br>
<a href="https://www.icedrive.net/">https://www.icedrive.net/</a> - Simple cloud storage service. 10 GB free storage<br>
<a href="https://www.sync.com/">https://www.sync.com/</a> - End-to-End cloud storage service. 5 GB free storage<br>
<a href="https://www.pcloud.com/">https://www.pcloud.com/</a> - Cloud storage service. Up to 10 GB free storage<br>
<a href="https://ipinfo.io/) — Fast, accurate, and free (up to 50k/month">https://ipinfo.io/) — Fast, accurate, and free (up to 50k/month</a> - Fast, accurate, and free (up to 50k/month) IP address data API. Offers APIs with details on geolocation, companies, carriers, IP ranges, domains, abuse contacts, and more. All paid APIs can be trialed for free.<br>
<a href="https://www.alwaysdata.com/">https://www.alwaysdata.com/</a> - 1000 MB free web hosting with support for MySQL, PostgreSQL, CouchDB, MongoDB, PHP, Python, Ruby, Node.js, Elixir, Java, Deno, custom web servers, access via FTP, WebDAV and SSH; mailbox, mailing list and app installer included.<br>
<a href="https://www.heliohost.org) — Community powered free hosting for everyone(Unable to register at this time">https://www.heliohost.org) — Community powered free hosting for everyone(Unable to register at this time</a> - Community powered free hosting for everyone(Unable to register at this time).<br>
<a href="https://www.datastax.com/products/datastax-astra/pricing)(using free $25/mo credit">https://www.datastax.com/products/datastax-astra/pricing)(using free $25/mo credit</a> - Cloud Native Cassandra as a Service with [80GB free tier](https://www.datastax.com/products/datastax-astra/pricing)(using free $25/mo credit)<br>
<a href="https://valine.js.org/">https://valine.js.org/</a> - a fast, simple & efficient Leancloud based no back end comment system.<br>
<a href="https://ip-fast.com/">https://ip-fast.com/</a> - Find out your IP Address and related detailed information using the free, fastest and simple lookup tool.<br>
<a href="https://www.datocms.com/">https://www.datocms.com/</a> - Offers free tier for small projects. DatoCMS is a GraphQL based CMS. On the lower tier you have 100k/month calls.<br>
<a href="https://ipinfo.io/) — Fast, accurate, and free (up to 100k/month">https://ipinfo.io/) — Fast, accurate, and free (up to 100k/month</a> - Fast, accurate, and free (up to 100k/month) IP address data API. Offers APIs with details on geolocation, companies, carriers, IP ranges, domains, abuse contacts, and more. All paid APIs can be trialed for free.<br>
<a href="https://www.alwaysdata.com/">https://www.alwaysdata.com/</a> - 100 MB free web hosting with support for MySQL, PostgreSQL, CouchDB, MongoDB, PHP, Python, Ruby, Node.js, Elixir, Java, Deno, custom web servers, access via FTP, WebDAV and SSH; mailbox, mailing list and app installer included.<br>
<a href="https://www.heliohost.org">https://www.heliohost.org</a> - Community powered free hosting for everyone.<br>
<a href="https://commons.host/) - Static web hosting and CDN.100% free and open source software (FOSS). With a commercially sustainable software as a service (SaaS">https://commons.host/) - Static web hosting and CDN.100% free and open source software (FOSS). With a commercially sustainable software as a service (SaaS</a> - Static web hosting and CDN.100% free and open source software (FOSS). With a commercially sustainable software as a service (SaaS) to fund R&D.<br>
<a href="https://www.datastax.com/products/datastax-astra/pricing">https://www.datastax.com/products/datastax-astra/pricing</a> - Cloud Native Cassandra as a Service with [40GB free tier](https://www.datastax.com/products/datastax-astra/pricing)<br>
<a href="https://ipinfo.io/) — Fast, accurate, and free (up to 50k/month">https://ipinfo.io/) — Fast, accurate, and free (up to 50k/month</a> - Fast, accurate, and free (up to 50k/month) IP address data API. Offers APIs with details on geolocation, companies, carriers, IP ranges, domains, abuse contacts, and more. All paid APIs can be trialed for free.<br>
<a href="https://www.alwaysdata.com/">https://www.alwaysdata.com/</a> - 1000 MB free web hosting with support for MySQL, PostgreSQL, CouchDB, MongoDB, PHP, Python, Ruby, Node.js, Elixir, Java, Deno, custom web servers, access via FTP, WebDAV and SSH; mailbox, mailing list and app installer included.<br>
<a href="https://www.datastax.com/products/datastax-astra/pricing">https://www.datastax.com/products/datastax-astra/pricing</a> - Cloud Native Cassandra as a Service with [80GB free tier](https://www.datastax.com/products/datastax-astra/pricing)<br>
<a href="https://www.codepng.app">https://www.codepng.app</a> - Create awesome snapshots from your source code that you can share on social media.<br>
<a href="https://bit.io">https://bit.io</a> - PostgreSQL managed database service. Unlimited repos, 10GB storage, 10M queried rows/month.<br>
<a href="https://www.nsupdate.info/">https://www.nsupdate.info/</a> - Free and open-source Dynamic DNS service<br>
<a href="http://maps.stamen.com/">http://maps.stamen.com/</a> - Free map tiles and tile hosting.<br>
<a href="https://www.alwaysdata.com/">https://www.alwaysdata.com/</a> - 100 MB free web hosting with support for MySQL, PostgreSQL, CouchDB, MongoDB, PHP, Python, Ruby, Node.js, Elixir, Java, Deno, custom web servers, access via FTP, WebDAV and SSH; mailbox, mailing list and app installer included.<br>
<a href="https://emailtemporanee.com/) - Easy to use free Unlimited disposable temporary email addresses (temp email">https://emailtemporanee.com/) - Easy to use free Unlimited disposable temporary email addresses (temp email</a> - - Easy to use free Unlimited disposable temporary email addresses (temp email). Autoexpires even you can set it day.<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>replaced FlashDrive.io by Qoddi.com</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/b894238a92738a42f01d2830a3187ed05aa2a983</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://qoddi.com">https://qoddi.com</a> - PaaS service similar to Heroku with a developer-centric approach and all inclusive features. Free tier for static assets, staging and developer apps.<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>deprecate shrinkray.io</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/59ad0b02a001cd94e876c30d5ef6a959c258b228</link><description><![CDATA[ ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Update README.md</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/793770690c44240debd57876caef98d50bf457bb</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://emailtemporanee.com/) - Easy to use free Unlimited disposable temporary email addresses (temp email">https://emailtemporanee.com/) - Easy to use free Unlimited disposable temporary email addresses (temp email</a> - - Easy to use free Unlimited disposable temporary email addresses (temp email). Autoexpires even you can set it day.<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>update alwaysdata info</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/bc48f16765b49c1b152844861903ba8c81bd1a3d</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.alwaysdata.com/">https://www.alwaysdata.com/</a> - 100 MB free web hosting with support for MySQL, PostgreSQL, CouchDB, MongoDB, PHP, Python, Ruby, Node.js, Elixir, Java, Deno, custom web servers, access via FTP, WebDAV and SSH; mailbox, mailing list and app installer included.<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Fix maps.stamen.com name</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/fd6608593a73b5860a2747870cae473b1a116c16</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="http://maps.stamen.com/">http://maps.stamen.com/</a> - Free map tiles and tile hosting.<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Add nsupdate.info</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/27931abf445d808d55f8c1097f0b85177b812110</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.nsupdate.info/">https://www.nsupdate.info/</a> - Free and open-source Dynamic DNS service<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Add bit.io DBaaS</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/e03aed346646cf3ee2b95b5df2dc05e26e112d68</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://bit.io">https://bit.io</a> - PostgreSQL managed database service. Unlimited repos, 10GB storage, 10M queried rows/month.<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Add Codepng</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/fba5b979d121e8236717d0d72d2c8424c67f144a</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.codepng.app">https://www.codepng.app</a> - Create awesome snapshots from your source code that you can share on social media.<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Update obsolete information</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/0a3dbf3e9ed29228fc5f7c68e231de7ae864138b</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://ipinfo.io/) — Fast, accurate, and free (up to 50k/month">https://ipinfo.io/) — Fast, accurate, and free (up to 50k/month</a> - Fast, accurate, and free (up to 50k/month) IP address data API. Offers APIs with details on geolocation, companies, carriers, IP ranges, domains, abuse contacts, and more. All paid APIs can be trialed for free.<br>
<a href="https://www.alwaysdata.com/">https://www.alwaysdata.com/</a> - 1000 MB free web hosting with support for MySQL, PostgreSQL, CouchDB, MongoDB, PHP, Python, Ruby, Node.js, Elixir, Java, Deno, custom web servers, access via FTP, WebDAV and SSH; mailbox, mailing list and app installer included.<br>
<a href="https://www.datastax.com/products/datastax-astra/pricing">https://www.datastax.com/products/datastax-astra/pricing</a> - Cloud Native Cassandra as a Service with [80GB free tier](https://www.datastax.com/products/datastax-astra/pricing)<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Merge branch 'ripienaar:master' into master</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/d4d401d1b7e2f8b3866f948c09c8f1315078cb3c</link><description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.datocms.com/">https://www.datocms.com/</a> - Offers free tier for small projects. DatoCMS is a GraphQL based CMS. On the lower tier you have 100k/month calls.<br>
<a href="https://ipinfo.io/) — Fast, accurate, and free (up to 100k/month">https://ipinfo.io/) — Fast, accurate, and free (up to 100k/month</a> - Fast, accurate, and free (up to 100k/month) IP address data API. Offers APIs with details on geolocation, companies, carriers, IP ranges, domains, abuse contacts, and more. All paid APIs can be trialed for free.<br>
<a href="https://www.alwaysdata.com/">https://www.alwaysdata.com/</a> - 100 MB free web hosting with support for MySQL, PostgreSQL, CouchDB, MongoDB, PHP, Python, Ruby, Node.js, Elixir, Java, Deno, custom web servers, access via FTP, WebDAV and SSH; mailbox, mailing list and app installer included.<br>
<a href="https://www.heliohost.org">https://www.heliohost.org</a> - Community powered free hosting for everyone.<br>
<a href="https://commons.host/) - Static web hosting and CDN.100% free and open source software (FOSS). With a commercially sustainable software as a service (SaaS">https://commons.host/) - Static web hosting and CDN.100% free and open source software (FOSS). With a commercially sustainable software as a service (SaaS</a> - Static web hosting and CDN.100% free and open source software (FOSS). With a commercially sustainable software as a service (SaaS) to fund R&D.<br>
<a href="https://www.datastax.com/products/datastax-astra/pricing">https://www.datastax.com/products/datastax-astra/pricing</a> - Cloud Native Cassandra as a Service with [40GB free tier](https://www.datastax.com/products/datastax-astra/pricing)<br>
 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Update README.md</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ripienaar/free-for-dev/commit/4c5f32f6ca6a334d8d447365d2f9246a3572127b</link><description><![CDATA[ ]]></description>
</item>

</channel>
</rss>
